Chapter 316 – Hurdles

The host finally announced the final guest and the audience sighed in disappointment. Everyone wanted to go up onto the stage, but unfortunately, the spots would only go to the few lucky ones.

Chen Guo was one such person who sighed in disappointment.

As soon as the numbers started rolling, her eyes would grow wide. When Zhou Zekai said the final seat number himself, she listened intently. But among the ten thousand spectators there, only four would be chosen. With a 0.04% chance, Chen Guo was unfortunately not chosen.

Though for these types of lottery events, not being chosen wouldn’t make her too depressed.

After a short moment of lament, Chen Guo immediately brought out her newly bought binoculars to look.

“AH!!!” Chen Guo suddenly shouted in astonishment.

“What is it?” Ye Xiu and Tang Rou asked.

“Su Mucheng also brought binoculars!” Chen Guo was very excited at the thought of doing the same thing as her idol.

“Really? Let me look!” Ye Xiu hastily said.

“Look!” Chen Guo gave the binoculars to Ye Xiu, “Over there.”

Ye Xiu took it and looked through them towards the pro players’ seats and quickly found Su Mucheng. Sure enough, she really had brought binoculars. Right now, they were raised up, searching around.

‘Right, right, right!!” Chen Guo continued to chatter in Ye Xiu’s ears. Ye Xiu saw Su Mucheng’s binoculars turn and turn, until finally it turned towards his direction, where it quickly stopped.

They were a bit far…… though they could at least see each other. Ye Xiu stared through them some more, but Chen Guo already wanted the binoculars back. Ye Xiu handed them back to her. Chen Guo raised them up and immediately cried out: “Ah!”

Chen Guo quickly put down the binoculars. Her expression was somewhat dumbstruck: “She seems to be looking towards us, don’t you think?”

“Seems like it……” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo quickly raised the binoculars again and continued to say in surprise: “Ah, she seems to be waving in this direction. Who do you think she’s saying hi to?” Chen Guo stood up and looked around, but didn’t notice the person next to her waving back.

After looking around in a circle, she obviously didn’t find anything. When she sat back down and looked through her binoculars again, Su Mucheng had already stopped looking in their direction.

On stage, the four participating pros had already gotten up. Zhou Zekai, of course, was one of them. In this event, three pros could sign up on their own and the fourth one was usually chosen from the all-stars list, in order to raise the stakes. Anyone on the all-stars list was naturally more popular than any normal pro. These types of players had a status similar to a box-office celebrity.

The popular pro’s task was to pick out four lucky guests and then participate in the event along with everyone else.

In the first event, the Hurdles, the popular pro was Zhou Zekai. When he stood alongside the normal audience members and the other participating pros, he already stood out.

He seemed somewhat uneasy, but it wasn’t as obvious as the chosen guests’ nervousness was. The other three pros, who were not as popular, looked even more calm than the God.

The host announced the eight participants.

He asked the four chosen audience members their names and then their Glory IDs and classes. He then asked them for their thoughts.

Two of the four expressed their excitement. Another one of them could only laugh and smile nervously. He couldn’t get a clear word out. The other was a female, who was staring at Zhou Zekai with sparkling eyes. Though to her disappointment, Zhou Zekai never turned his head to look at her. His head was lowered towards his feet the entire time.

After asking the chosen audience members their thoughts, the host turned to the pros, who were skilled at interviews.

Finally, the mic was handed to Zhou Zekai. The host was already sweating.

“Zekai…..” The host called.

Zhou Zekai lifted his head to look at him.

“What do you think? Do you have any confidence in winning?” The host asked.

“Uh…..” Zhou Zekai hesitated.

“Good.” He said.

“You can do it.” The host didn’t even attempt to figure out what he meant by “Good” and hastily ended the God’s interview. He immediately announced that the first event would begin soon.

This match was purely for fun, so no one bothered with being fair. The pros would use their own accounts, while the chosen audience members would use their own, as well. Only if they didn’t bring their account cards would the host provide them with one. When they advertised the event, they had reminded the audience members to bring their account cards because there was a chance they could play with the pros on stage, so these four chosen audience members used their own accounts.

The eight players got up onto the match platforms and their eight characters appeared on stage. The most eye-catching character was obviously Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. His character was covered in grey and wore a black cap. Its posture was similar to Zhou Zekai. His character was looking down and standing silently behind the starting line.

Beside him was a lucky audience member’s character. The seven characters were lined up in this way. Four of the characters had their heads turned. These were clearly because the four normal players were admiring the Great Gunner’s elegance.

The three pros were also rare existences to normal players, but compared with a God, they were immediately drowned out.

“Ready…….. Set……” A very loud voice resounded throughout the entire stadium.

‘Bang!” A gunshot.

“Bang, bang, bang, bang……”

After the starting gun shot, more gunshots closely followed. The audience were surprised and thought that something had happened to the starting pistol. But soon after, they saw Zhou Zekai flying backwards. The repeated gun shots weren’t from the starting pistol, but Zhou Zekai’s Silver weapon, Wildfire Revolver.

Zhou Zekai was undoubtedly using Aerial Fire.

Aerial Fire required high frequency shooting. Aerial Cannon could push a character very far, but Aerial Fire required repeated shooting to keep the character floating. In terms of difficulty, Aerial Fire was harder to do than an Aerial Cannon.

But for Zhou Zekai, the current God among Gunners, Aerial Fire was beyond easy to use. As soon as the starting pistol went off, his character quickly turned around and flew backwards, instantly pulling ahead of the other seven players.

When using Aerial Fire, the character touched the ground much more frequently than when using Aerial Cannon. But under Zhou Zekai’s quick fingers, Cloud Piercer slid along the ground like a dragonfly. He quickly arrived at the first hurdle. Without turning around, he simply angled himself downwards and then gently jumped. Cloud Piercer gracefully leaped over the hurdle without over-jumping it by even the slightest inch.

The electronic screens immediately replayed this part. The applause from the audience was very warm. This was Samsara’s stadium, which meant it was also Zhou Zekai’s home grounds. Here, he was absolutely the most welcome player there.

Among the other seven players, one of the pros was a Witch. He hopped onto his broom and flew low, quickly winning a small lead. When he met a hurdle, he would make a slight adjustment and his character would gently glide across the hurdle. The absolute majority of pros were extremely adept at these sorts of basic skills. It was impossible to tell who was better with just one move.

Apart from these two classes with their more unique movement methods, the other six were more ordinary and were running along the ground. But the other two pros quickly pulled ahead of the four audience members. Whether it was from their equipment or movement speed, they had a better grasp of the tempo. The pros were obviously much more skilled than normal players. This type of difference was obvious at a glance.

If they kept on running like this according to the normal rules, then this match would be quite boring. But in a match with no rules, who would abide by them? Everyone awaited for that moment.

The audience didn’t have to wait long. One of the pro players broke the silence. His character was a Battle Mage. Even though he didn’t have any special movement abilities, he had an ability that could increase his movement speed. When he passed by the first hurdle, he threw out a Dragon Tooth at the hurdle. The hurdle broke and a Neutral Chaser appeared behind him. If he could attack with the Chaser, then he would be able to obtain the movement speed buff.

Chasers couldn’t be used against the hurdles. They could only target other people. The players near him were both audience members. Even though there were no rules, the pro felt that bullying the normal players would be somewhat embarrassing to do, so he sent his Neutral Chaser towards the other nearby pro.

But how could a pro be hit so easily? That pro was a Berserker, who directly jumped to a different lane to avoid the attack.

Correct, he switched lanes……. In a match with no rules, there was nothing wrong with switching lanes. That Battle Mage didn’t hesitate and immediately chased after him. He was clearly determined to get his Chaser buff.

The pros were clearly more on top of things. The four audience members were still running normally, while these two had already started fighting. The current second place pro, the Witch, began to move too. Seeing that Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer didn’t seem to be slowing down, he wanted to stop him. As a result, he began casting Magic Missiles towards Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer was flying backwards, so he could clearly see them coming. He immediately began to adjust his flying angle. His character continued to adjust his flying direction and he was no longer flying in a straight line.

His quick changes were like a butterfly passing through flowers. His beautiful movements caught the audience’s attentions and the applause once again came. The Witch saw that his Magic Missiles weren’t working, so he chanted again. His character threw out a sparkling light, which transformed into a ray of light that shot towards Cloud Piercer.

Witch skill: Star Ray.

Chapter 317 – The Second Event

Star Ray moved quickly and was very difficult to dodge.

However, the more difficult the challenge, the greater the skill required to overcome it. For someone at the top of the pro scene, avoiding the Star Ray couldn’t be said as extremely hard. This was especially so in this sort of scenario where there wasn’t any strategy involved to ensure Star Ray would connect.

However, this wasn’t a serious competition. It was only a show match, so the players wouldn’t think too hard. If they had a skill to use, just use it! It would be a battle of luck!

This Star Ray was thrown out with this type of carefree attitude. As a result, Zhou Zekai wouldn’t be hit by it. The instant the Star Ray flashed out, his Cloud Piercer lightly jumped. While dodging the Star Ray, he also leaped over a hurdle.

“Pa!” The Star Ray directly hit the hurdle and the powerful magic shattered the hurdle.

Wood pieces flew through the air. At this moment, no one was able to hear the quiet “ka” sound amidst this. If they heard it, then the experienced players would realize that this was the sound of a bullet being loaded. Furthermore, this wasn’t a normal attack, but a skill.

As the wood pieces fell, the Witch hastily flew over, when he saw an ice-cold black muzzle pointed at him.

“Bang!”

The gunshot was extremely loud. The sparks that flew out were like a small explosion. The gunpowder that flew out raised a dust cloud around Cloud Piercer. It could be seen just how strong the skill was based off of its visual effects. This was a Sharpshooter’s most powerful skill: Thunder Snipe.

Correct, right now Cloud Piercer was holding a giant sniper rifle. When he used the skill, his character would create an item that would fit the skill for the game’s visual effects. Whether it was from the ground or from the air, no one knew where the item came from.

With this distance, wanting to dodge the Thunder Snipe after seeing the gun fire couldn’t be called difficult, but rather impossible.

The Witch was hit in the head by the skill and blood immediately splattered out. Those who were hit in the head by Thunder Snipe would trigger a hidden effect that would cause the bullet to do twice its normal damage.

However, the Witch’s head exploding with one shot was only a visual effect. He would receive a large amount of damage, but he wouldn’t immediately die. However, his rush forward had been interrupted. When the bullet hit, his head flew backwards like a train, carrying his body along with it. In that instant, he went from being second place to last place.

Cheers! More cheers.

In reality, most of the audience didn’t realize that Zhou Zekai’s Thunder Snipe had used the hurdle shattering sound as a cover, but the attack’s power, as well as its quickness, was enough to bring about the audience’s cheers.

Cloud Piercer continued with his Aerial Fire. Behind him were the Battle Mage and Berserker, who were fighting as they ran forward. These two classes lacked long-range abilities. The two were fighting with each other as well and had no way of stopping Cloud Piercer. It was somewhat boring to see the match being decided so quickly. Though for this type of fun event, winning or losing wasn’t really the main attraction.

At this moment, Cloud Piercer’s beautiful and steady Aerial Fire was the biggest watching point, while the two pro players fighting with each other were the second watching point. The four audience members who had entered the show mode and their chaotic fighting were the third watching point. As for the Witch who was blasted away, after climbing back up, his hasty broom riding to try and catch up became the fourth watching point.

The commentators and the screens wouldn’t recap the more technical areas and would displayed the more fun parts instead. For this match, the purpose wasn’t to praise the winners, but to try and get everyone to smile and laugh.

From the looks of it, the first match could still be considered successful. With the winner already decided, the remaining contestants became more relaxed and simply took the match as just a fun match. In the beginning, the pros were only fighting with each other. They felt too embarrassed to bully the audience members. But as the audience members began to attack the pros, everyone gradually began to a huge fight, which was quite funny to watch.

Along with the sound of a whistle, Zou Zekai reached the end destination. And the group behind him? There were only four players left. Of the four audience members, three had already died along the way. The remaining audience member was the female player. The three pros were clearly being somewhat nicer to her. In truth, if the pros were seriously fighting, then the pros would have gotten rid of the audience members long ago and there wouldn’t have been a huge fight. However, since they were simple doing it for fun, the fight turned out like so.

When the four remaining players were about to reach the final destination, the Battle Mage and the Berserker seemed to have suddenly reached an agreement and they began bullying the Witch. Just before they hit the end goal, they killed him off. After that, the two began fighting again, intentionally giving the female audience member an opportunity. The girl swept past the finish line as the second place contestant and the other two also reached there shortly after.

When the match ended, the electronic screen showed everyone’s record and placing. After that, they even put out the stats for things like who did the most damage for everyone to see. The commentators talked about the placings jokingly and the stadium’s atmosphere lightened up even more.

The eight players returned to the center of the stage. The second-place female player received the champion Zhou Zekai’s hug under the host’s directions. With her face red, she scurried off stage, forgetting to pick up her prize.

The other three pros didn’t care at all about the match and were laughing along with the host.

“Zekai, you won the match. How are you feeling right now?” The host still asked the God.

Zhou Zekai replied as if he were extremely prepared and immediately said: “I feel very happy.”

He only said four words and then smiled at the host. The host didn’t attempt to go deeper. The day’s event was mainly for the audience. After saying a few words to the three male audience members, he gave them souvenirs and announced the end for the Hurdles event.

The second event was the High Jump. But for this event, the contestants weren’t jumping for height, but for speed. The goal was to reach the highest point as fast as possible.

In the past years, the map was set on some sort of tall mountain peak. But this year, due to the projection technology, it was only a few platforms floating in the air.

This was done for convenience. If they used some sort of tall mountain peak, then if the projection technology was used, it would be difficult for the audience to see every character. With floating platforms, every player could be easily seen.

“Next up is a pro player from Team Excellent Era. She’s someone we all know and love, Su Mucheng!!”

After the host announced it, the stadium’s cheers and applause shook the heavens and the earth. For a beautiful female player like Su Mucheng, even enemy fans would find it hard to dislike her. It wouldn’t be excessive to say that everyone liked her. Apart from the home team’s players, any other pro or God would find it difficult to contest with the audience’s applause for her.

“Ah, ah, ah, Su Mucheng! Su Mucheng!!” Chen Guo excitedly shouted. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, felt somewhat uneasy. Su Mucheng hadn’t gotten binoculars just to find him and wave at him, right? Right? She hadn’t counted which seat he was in to call him up onto the stage, right?

The occasional joke suited Su Mucheng’s personality. But she knew that Ye Xiu never showed himself to the public, so acting on her own and playing the joke out was somewhat headstrong. Ye Xiu felt like it wasn’t something Su Mucheng would do.

“Mucheng, how do you plan on choosing the four audience members?” The host’s tone was very excited. It was probably because of his previous experience with Zhou Zekai.

“Let’s do it randomly for now!” Su Mucheng said.

“Okay, then we’re going to show the numbers on the screen and it’ll stop when you say stop.” The host said and the numbers began to roll.

“Stop!” Su Mucheng’s shout was almost faster than Zhou Zekai’s. The host almost slipped on the ground, causing the audience to laugh.

After Chen Guo finished laughing, she took a look at the seat number chosen and felt very dejected when she saw that it wasn’t hers. This time, her idol was on stage and Chen Guo wanted to go up very badly.

The speechless host didn’t want to tell Su Mucheng to slow down. He was afraid that she’d be like Zhou Zekai.

For the second roll, Su Mucheng did things normally and told him to stop after a while.

“Ah….. not me again…..” Disappointment was written all over Chen Guo’s face.

“Next up, I’m going to switch methods!” Not waiting for the host to speak, Su Mucheng took the initiative to make a suggestion.

“Oh? Mucheng, what’s your new method?” The host excitedly asked.

“Oh, I don’t have a new one. Can I just randomly call out two seats?” Su Mucheng said.

The host fell over again. Was Su Mucheng going to act like Zhou Zekai?

“I pick Area C.” Su Mucheng said.

“Ah….” Chen Guo cried out in surprise. She was sitting in Area C.

“Row 18.”

“AH……” Chen Guo jumped up. She was in Row 18.

“#21!” Su Mucheng concluded.

Chen Guo’s brain immediately exploded. As if something had blown up, she asked Tang Rou in disbelief: “What number?”

“21! That’s you!” Tang Rou was also happy for Chen Guo. No one knew better than her how much she liked Su Mucheng.

Chen Guo’s gaze was still somewhat blank. Except this time, when she looked around, everyone had their heads turned towards her, their gazes filled with envy and jealousy.

“It really is me!” Chen Guo didn’t know what to do.

Su Mucheng continued: “Next up, I have an idea. I want to choose this friend’s neighboring seats. I think it’ll be very fun if we invite people who know each other to come up.”

“Mm, Mucheng, that sounds like a great idea. Then which one are you going to pick? #19 or #23?” the host said. They were in an odd number only area. Number 19 was Ye Xiu. Number 23 was Tang Rou. After hearing Su Mucheng’s suggestion, Chen Guo shouted excitedly: “AH! We can even go up together!”

Chapter 318 – Meeting an Idol

She isn’t actually going to make me go up, is she? Now that things had gotten this far, Ye Xiu couldn’t help but feel uncertain. And when he looked on stage, Su Mucheng was currently hesitating with her answer: “Number 19 or number 23?” Su Mucheng mumbled.

The surrounding audience members had all turned around to look at them. Their eyes were filled with envy. It didn’t matter what her answer was, one of them would have the chance to go up.

“Right now, we only have these two choices. Do you want to flip a coin to decide it?” The host suggested.

“No need. I’ve already thought of my answer.” Su Mucheng said.

“Oh? Then which one?” The host asked.

“It’s…….” Su Mucheng said and then paused with a deep breath. Ye Xiu had figured it out. He was certain that Su Mucheng wouldn’t pick him. The girl was just messing with him deliberately in order to scare him. Unfortunately, her little scheme had been seen through by Ye Xiu and he wouldn’t be fazed by it.

Sure enough, after taking her deep breath, Su Mucheng chose number 23, Tang Rou’s seat.

“Ah! It’s you!!” Chen Guo was the first to shout. She was clearly more excited than the person who was chosen. Tang Rou had been at a loss before, but her mind was clear now. She laughed: “It looks like my luck today is pretty good!”

“Though it’s too bad for a certain someone!” Chen Guo laughed as she looked at Ye Xiu. She patted Ye Xiu’s shoulder: “Sigh. You just barely missed it. Don’t be too disappointed!”

But Ye Xiu’s face was as calm as ever. He didn’t have any sort of envious or jealous expression like the other spectators did. In fact, he didn’t seem disappointed at all. He looked as if everything was just as he had expected.

Chen Guo suddenly remembered that even though she had never heard of his name before, he had been in the pro scene before. It seemed like going up on stage really wasn’t that big of a deal for him!

Chen Guo felt somewhat sorry that she wasn’t able to use this opportunity to deal a blow to Ye Xiu. The host had already called the two forward and the two handed their belongings to Ye Xiu to take care of.

“Work hard and admire our heroics!” Chen Guo handed her binoculars over to Ye Xiu.

“Good luck getting closer to your idol.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“As if you need to say that.” Chen Guo loftily turned around and walked towards the stage with Tang Rou.

“The final two guests have arrived on stage. Two very beautiful girls. Let’s all get to know them.” The host noticed that Chen Guo and Tang Rou were both very beautiful. It could be said that they weren’t much inferior to Su Mucheng.

“Could I ask for your names?” The host asked.

“Chen Guo.”

“Tang Rou.”

The two replied.

“It seems like you two are like Mucheng wanted. Are you two together?” The host asked.

“Yup, we’re good friends.” Chen Guo replied.

“You two were lucky enough to participate in today’s event for the All-Star Weekend. What are your feelings about this?’ The host continued to ask.

“Of course, I’m very excited.”

The questions were pretty much all answered by Chen Guo. After Tang Rou said her name, she just stood on the side with a smile. Her gaze turned as she saw the all-star Su Mucheng, Chen Guo’s favorite all-star, smiling at her. Their gazes met and Su Mucheng waved her hands back, smiling. Tang Rou was somewhat startled, but she quickly returned a friendly smile back.

“Of course it’s Su Mucheng!” At this moment, the host asked Chen Guo who her favorite player was, which Chen Guo replied quickly with Su Mucheng’s name. The host immediately had Su Mucheng come over and interact with her fan. Chen Guo didn’t know whether she was dreaming or not, but everything seemed to go by too quickly as she was rushed over. When she got in front of Su Mucheng, she became a lot more boastful. Hearing Chen Guo’s gentle and low voice talking with Su Mucheng was enough to make people familiar with her feel like it wasn’t real.

But the host couldn’t only revolve around them. After all, the three other pro players and the other two guests were already on stage, as well. They couldn’t be left feeling ignored.

While the host interviewed the other participants, Su Mucheng and Chen Guo were still chatting with each other.

In truth, Chen Guo had no idea what she wanted to say to her idol, though Su Mucheng took the initiative to chat with her about some of the fun things interesting to Glory female players.

Unfortunately, they didn’t have much time to chat. After the host finished with the introductions, the match officially started and the eight players went to their respective platforms.

It was too short!

This was Chen Guo’s only regret. She really wanted to chat with Su Mucheng more. Su Mucheng was no longer that far-away idol that she could only see on the Internet, but instead, she was like a good friend. She really wanted to get closer to her.

Sadly, when the day was over, Chen Guo knew that she would never get another chance. In the end, Su Mucheng was a celebrity-type figure and she was just a normal player. Reality was always like this. When Chen Guo walked up to her platform, she felt quite forced and looked back from time to time at the spot where she had chatted with Su Mucheng.

The event continued.

After the eight players went up onto their respective match platforms, they began to log in with their account cards. The host had obviously asked about their account’s class and level. However, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist wasn’t even Level 40 yet. If she played with the other max-level characters, then it wouldn’t be fair at all, so the host proposed to give Tang Rou a Level 70 Battle Mage account. Tang Rou didn’t complain and gladly accepted it.

The eight players’ characters were projected onto the stage. The electronic screens featured each character’s perspective. But to everyone’s surprise, when Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze appeared on-screen, there was quite a bit of commotion among the audience.

“Chasing Haze? That Chasing Haze?” After seeing that character appear, the audience members suddenly began to discuss with one another.

“Yeah! It’s that one. I remember her equipment.” Some audience members affirmed.

Chasing Haze was quite famous and her fame came from when Ye Xiu used her to battle with Poplar Beach.

Poplar Beach might not have been very well-liked, but in the Heavenly Domain, he was certainly a famous expert. To be beaten so quickly in such a manner caused quite a bit of commotion in the gaming community. The recording for that match had been on the popular videos ranking list for a very long time.

Whoever saw the video knew of Chasing Haze.

During those initial days of popularity, Chen Guo constantly received friend requests every day. Her mailbox had received countless letters with all sorts of content in them. Chen Guo had been tossed from side to side so much that, in the end, she directly closed her ability to add friends and shut down her mailbox in order to go back to her peaceful days.

And now, Chasing haze had suddenly appeared at the All-Star Weekend event, which was quite surprising to the audience members.

Chasing Haze was like a grassroot celebrity. Her fan base could be considered quite large. Her appearance on stage didn’t lose to those three other pro players. As for the other guests, they were only given a polite applause.

The hosts had no way of anticipating this. Quite a few people knew of her. If they had known that such a coincidence would occur, the hosts would have fully utilized it. But right now, the High Jump event was about to begin.

The map was projected onto the stage as the eight characters lined up. The eight characters all had their heads up, looking up at the steps floating in the air.

It was the first time the High Jump event was like this. The floating steps didn’t have any mountain walls as obstacles, so there was much more freedom in the jumping and the competition would be more intense.

The eight players didn’t have much time to look. After the eight characters each got into their position, the match quickly began.

“Bang!” A gun sounded and the match began. The pro players used their own methods to jump up. Su Mucheng, as the all-star, didn’t disgrace her status. She used her Aerial Cannon to jump up and rapidly ascended. After a few ups and downs, she pulled ahead of everyone.

This High Jump event clearly wasn’t as simple as the Hurdles. For that one, if you didn’t know what you were doing, and you just ran straight forward, you would eventually reach the finish line. But for this High Jump, if the players failed their play, they would fall down just as the Sin City clock tower.

Of the four guests, three of them were doing quite well. Only one of them clearly wasn’t good enough. After a few jumps, that player would always fall down. Like that, no one needed to work it out for him. He himself knew that he wouldn’t be able to finish the match.

As for the pros, they began to compete. Like the Hurdles, the pros felt too bad for bullying the guests, so they fought amongst one another. And it was too easy to mess things up for others in this event. If a player was hit by a crowd control or knockback skill, then they would immediately have to start from the bottom again.

Chapter 319 – Harming Others for One’s Personal Gain

The High Jump event was much more difficult than the Hurdles event. Even though the match was only for fun and winning or losing didn’t matter, repeatedly failing to reach the floating steps was a bit embarrassing. The All-Star Weekend was being watched by numerous Glory fans and no pro player wanted to be remembered in this way.

As a result, those who signed up for the High Jump event all had real skill in this area. There were many areas a player could be strong at in Glory. Every pro player had particular skills or techniques they excelled at. If these pros who signed up for the High Jump were evaluated based on their skill at jumping, then these pros would be among the top of all players.

Su Mucheng jumped the quickest, but the other three weren’t far behind. These four had strong fundamentals for jumping. They continued to steadily ascend as they fought with one another. Those who were hit down wouldn’t fall to the very bottom. They would usually fall a bit and then think of a way to stop their descent at a chosen floating step.

This type of difficult game immediately created a clear divide between the pros and the normal players. Tang Rou’s mechanics were completely based around her hand speed. However, this type of jumping required the player to determine the distance, height, and jumping power. With only her hand speed, every time she jumped onto the next floating step, she had to stop and slowly think about how to jump onto the next one.

Compared to her, Chen Guo was a bit faster at this. Another guest had pretty decent skill as well. But the remaining fourth guest was more miserable. Overall, he was very bad in this area and after a few jumps, without any interruptions, he would fail again and again. He immediately became the star of the show. Every time he fell to the bottom, the audience would laugh.

Even the commentators were paying attention to him. In the beginning, they had been encouraging him, but towards the end, they were stumped for words. He simply wasn’t good enough. It had nothing to do with how hard he was trying.

Being laughed at for failing wasn’t easy for this poor brother. Compared to the other seven contestants, the four pros had already climbed so high that he couldn’t see them anymore. As for the other three guests, even though they were way behind the pros, they were at least steadily climbing.

Having seen the pros fight in the previous match, this brother suddenly felt inspired. He had become a joke, but he could at least drag others along with him.

This guest just happened to be a Sharpshooter, which was a long-range class. Thus, after jumping up a few times and feeling like he couldn’t jump any higher, he took out his gun and fired at the other three guests.

These three guests were completely focused on jumping up. Chen Guo and Tang Rou naturally wouldn’t attack each other. As for the other guest, after seeing the pros so far ahead, he didn’t feel like there was any point in attacking each other. If he made a mistake and accidentally fell down, then that would be very unfortunate, which was why he only thought of reaching the end floating step and nothing else.

The three hadn’t thought of doing anything bad to each other, but unfortunately, they had a poor crackpot beneath them. When the firing began, the three immediately panicked a bit.

Compared to Su Mucheng and the other pros, their jumping skills were greatly inferior. Even under circumstances where there were no obstacles, they had to jump slowly and cautiously. With bullets flying towards them, danger sprang up all around them as they had to both jump and dodge at the same time.

“Ka!” Using normal attacks wasn’t enough for this guest. He fired the Sharpshooter skill that Zhou Zekai had used in the Hurdles: “Thunder Snipe”.

The bullet flew up with a bang.

The bullet headed towards Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze. Chen Guo had played the game for many years and she knew of “Thunder Snipe’s” power. But with her skill level, she wasn’t able to determine where the bullet was being aimed at. Helpless, her only choice was to dodge. However, there wasn’t much time to dodge, so she hastily chose to jump towards the next floating step.

The bullet whistled by. It hadn’t connected with Chasing Haze. But because Chen Guo had hurried the jump, Chasing Haze missed the floating step and fell.

Chen Guo immediately fired her cannon in the air and wanted to use Aerial Cannon to land on another floating step. But with her skill, her mechanics weren’t involved in this move at all, only luck.

Unfortunately, her luck failed her. Chasing Haze had gotten to a few floating steps, but she wasn’t able to steady herself on them and, in the end, she fell to the very bottom.

Chen Guo was furious.

If everyone had been fighting, then being blown down like this wasn’t too bad. After all, that was a part of the game. But the player beneath them had already been seen by everyone as being inferior in skill. It wasn’t possible for him to finish the game and it could be said that he had already been eliminated from the competition. But this guy was hurting others for his own selfish reasons. He wasn’t able to jump up, so he just had to cause trouble for others. It really was somewhat disgraceful.

As soon as Chasing Haze got up after falling down, she directly fired a Gatling Gun at the Sharpshooter.

As if he had found a new toy to play with, the Sharpshooter excitedly began to fight with Chen Guo. Two guests fighting with each other on the ground was a first for this High Jump event.

The audience were at first in disbelief, but they quickly thought of Chasing Haze’s exceptional skill displayed in the video and felt like the fight would be quite fun to watch. As soon as one person took the lead, the others began to clap and cheer.

The Sharpshooter had gotten the wrong idea and thought he was the one being cheered for. His anger was appeased and he immediately began fighting with more energy.

On flat ground, the Sharpshooter’s skill wasn’t as poor as his jumping ability. After the two attacked for a bit, it wasn’t certain that Chen Guo would win. The audience watched for a bit, but didn’t see the skill they were expecting out of Chasing Haze and all felt very disappointed.

On that day, someone else had played on the Chasing Haze account. Quite a few players in the tenth server knew this, but this information wasn’t given in the video, so players from other servers who had seen the video didn’t know of this.

On the ground, the two continued to fight intensely. Up above, the four pros were also fighting fiercely. In the middle, the two guests were the same as before. They didn’t pay attention to each other and continued to jump. But Tang Rou’s character stopped. After seeing that Chen Guo and the other guest were fighting evenly, without hesitating, she stepped off the floating platform and jumped down.

The audience went into an uproar, but Tang Rou was very calm. She didn’t feel fired up enough simply jumping up. But if it was PK, then she was quite confident in herself.

The Sharpshooter was still fighting with Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze and didn’t know that a disaster was coming from up above. The falling Tang Rou jabbed forward with her spear, causing the enthusiastic guest to stumble.Tang Rou’s character didn’t use any sort of stalling method and, after falling down from so high up, her health plummeted to half. Chasing Haze, on the other hand, had used Aerial Cannon to stall. Even though she hadn’t landed steadily, she didn’t take any damage from the fall.

When the Sharpshooter turned to look, he saw that Tang Rou’s character was already at half life from falling. He laughed out loud and believed her to be a noob. He knew that the person playing the character was a very pretty girl, so he teased her in a very casual manner: “Pretty girl, did that hurt? Would you like a hand?”

The second day’s events were interactive, so they didn’t prohibit voice chat like in the official matches. Players could freely communicate through their voice.

When a character fell from high up, besides losing health, the character would also be briefly stunned. This was something Tang Rou didn’t know. She had been prepared to follow up, but then she discovered that she couldn’t move because of her stunned state. This would have given the opponent a good chance to attack, but the guy had decided not to and instead had instead chosen to tease her.

After he finished talking, the stunned state wore off. Tang Rou immediately had her character use a Dragon Tooth.

This max-level Battle Mage had a complete set of skills, but because Tang Rou was only familiar with skills below level 40, she didn’t use the high leveled skills. When she added in points, she maxed all of the skills she was familiar with and then randomly put in points in other skills.

Tang Rou was very serious for this battle, so she didn’t want to test out any high level skills and only used familiar ones.

In terms of PK, Tang Rou was far above normal players. The Sharpshooter was completely crushed. He didn’t have any ability to keep up and tease the girl at the same time. On the other side, Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze had rushed over and didn’t hesitate to fight with Tang Rou in a 2v1. This brother’s situation wasn’t looking good.

The commentators were somewhat unable to keep up. After a short pause, one of them said: “If I’m not looking at things wrong, then these two girls have formed a team…..”

At the same time, the audience members weren’t the only ones astonished; even the spectators in the pro player seats were watching seriously.

“That Battle Mage seems to be pretty good!” someone said.

“Her hand speed is very fast!” The pro level players were instantly able to recognize what Tang Rou’s strongest point was.

“Sigh, but she’s not experienced enough! Why didn’t she use a Raging Dragon there?” another sighed.

Raging Dragon Pierces the Heart was a Level 60 Battle Mage skill. It was a skill that currently wasn’t in Tang Rou’s train of thought.

Chapter 320 – Helping Each Other

The poor Sharpshooter wanted to show off his might in front of the beauties, but his efforts only resulted in being flattened by them. After hearing the commentator say that the two of them had even partied up, he refused to give up and, as he climbed back up, he shouted: “How shameless! You even partied up?”

The crowd laughed. The commentators had even checked the rules and explained: “Uh, the rules never talked about this….. But since it doesn’t talk about it, that means it should be okay?”

Everyone watching could see the scene very clearly. No one sympathized with him. They all watched in glee as he was crushed by the two beauties and applauded repeatedly.

However, the broadcasting team wasn’t really sure what to do. The spectators in the stadium had more freedom and had a full view of the match. They could choose where they wanted to watch. The broadcasting team, though, could only show a single point of view. From the audience’s reactions, it was clear that everyone was watching this battle. But all in all, this was the High Jump Event. Should they broadcast the fights between the pros or show the random fighting between the three normal players?

Seeing that he was unable to beat Chen Guo and Tang Rou, the Sharpshooter chose to run. Tang Rou wasn’t a person who liked to give up and Chen Guo was already furious at him. The two didn’t stop to rest and chased after him.

The three, one in front and two behind, headed straight for the edge of the map. Quite a few of the audience members stood up, wanting to see what was happening at the border. Would they go off the map and into the stadium’s seats?

In the end, just as that Sharpshooter was about to run off the edge, he suddenly switched directions and followed along the borders of the map.

The audience booed, but after a short moment, the audience went silent again. This was because they could see from the screens that it wasn’t possible to run past the edges of the map. The audience couldn’t see the edges of the map from the projection, but the screens gave the players’ perspectives. The map actually did have borders. After hitting a wall, what else could he do but turn?

But how long could he run for? Chen Guo and Tang Rou split apart until they finally trapped him. With a wolf at the front and a tiger at the back, the player had nowhere left to run and was killed. The stadium went into an applause. Tang Rou and Chen Guo’s characters heroically returned to jumping up the floating steps.

In the first event, the audience witnessed the Great Gunner, Zhou Zekai’s, elegance. In the second event, the audience witnessed a farce brought to them by the normal players. The atmosphere was lively and even those at the pro player seats were talking amongst each other more.

“What do you think?” Players in all of the teams were asking this question. The person they were paying attention to was, of course, Tang Rou.

“Her hand speed is quite good.” they all said.

“Though there’s something that’s really weird.” A Battle Mage said, “I watched closely the entire time, but I didn’t see her use any skills above Level 40. No matter how good the opportunity was, she never used them.”

“Maybe she thinks that there’s no need to use such powerful skills against her opponent?”

“Maybe! Maybe the difference in skill was just that wide.”

While the spectators discussed amongst themselves, Chen Guo and Tang Rou continued to jump. As of now, Su Mucheng and the other pros were almost at the finish line. The other guest had already gone past the halfway point, as well. Chen Guo and Tang Rou were now starting at the bottom again. But after providing them with such a fun show, the people in the audience were very supportive of them and constantly shouted words of encouragement.

After a few minutes, the four pros reached the top, one after the other. Su Mucheng kept her initial lead and won first place.

The others followed soon after, though they knew that this time, the match wasn’t focused on them, but rather upon the two beauties who weren’t even a quarter of the way up yet.

The four pros stood at the top platform and looked down. Chen Guo and Tang Rou weren’t making a fool of themselves and jumped up step by step. Even though they weren’t nearly as nimble as the pros, they hadn’t made any mistakes yet.

“Go! We’re almost there!” The two girls encouraged each other. They looked up and saw that the other guest had reached the top as well. They were the only two left.

“Go! Go!!” The audience cheered.

“Oh, no!” an audience member suddenly cried. He saw Chen Guo make a mistake. Chasing Haze didn’t jump high enough and missed the floating step.

Tang Rou’s Battle Mage leaped up and sent a Sky Strike at Chasing Haze. Chasing Haze was launched up and, as she fell, she landed on the floating step that she had previously missed.

“Little Tang!” Chen Guo shouted and hastily turned her camera to look. Tang Rou’s Battle Mage was standing on floating step two levels behind.

“I’m fine.” Tang Rou laughed.

It was also an attack, but it had been done between two friends to help each other. Compared to those attacks by the Sharpshooter trying to undermine everyone else, this scene moved many among the audience.

Even those standing at the finish line had their characters make an “applauding” motion.

Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze stood up from the floating step and didn’t hurry to jump to the next one. She waited until Tang Rou’s Battle Mage reached the same height and continued on together. After this, their jumping went smoothly and the two reached the finish line under the audience’s cheers and shouts.

The host went along and pushed forward to reach a greater climax. The seven characters standing at the top waved their hands at the audience and then faded away. At the match platforms, the players walked down.

“Congratulations for your victory, Su Mucheng. Is there anything that you’d like to say?” Under normal circumstances, the champion would be the last to be interviewed by the host. But this time, the host switched the order. The first to be asked was the champion, Su Mucheng.

“I’m very happy. But I’m even more happy that I was able to see such a beautiful scene in this event. I remember someone often said that Glory has never been a game played alone. I really like this saying. And they perfectly showed this. I’m very moved.” Su Mucheng said.

“Was this what you wanted to see when you picked the two of them?” the host said.

“Yes. I thank them for their outstanding performance.” Su Mucheng smiled.

The audience applauded wildly. The host walked over to Chen Guo and Tang Rou. The two of them had become this event’s lead characters.

“Congratulations you two.” The host said, “From the audience’s applause, we know that not only Su Mucheng, but the entire audience was very moved by you two. Are you two happy?”

“Of course…….” Chen Guo really wanted to say that this was a stupid question, but….. In front of the cameras, she resisted.

“The display of friendship you two showed to everyone was very moving. Can I ask how long you two have known each other?” the host asked.

“Two years!” Chen Guo continued to be in charge of replying, while Tang Rou stayed to the side, smiling.

“Two years….. Uh……” Two years couldn’t be considered as just having met, but they couldn’t be considered old friends, either. The host wasn’t sure what to say. After a short pause, he quickly followed: “I can see that the two of you have a very strong relationship with each other. Did you two meet through Glory?”

“No.” Chen Guo replied honestly, though her answer didn’t really fit in with the situation.

“Oh, then do you two must play a lot of Glory together now, right?” the host asked.

“Uh….. in the future.” Chen Guo said.

“In the future? Why not before?” the host asked curiously.

“Because she only started playing Glory not too long ago!” Chen Guo looked to Tang Rou.

This time, the biggest uproar came from the pro players’ seats. This beauty, who had caught their attention, had unexpectedly only recently started playing. Her previous performance meant something completely different now.

“Not too long ago? How long?” The host asked the question the pros were hoping to know.

“About a month!” Chen Guo said.

“A month! Are you saying that before that, she had never touched Glory?” the host asked curiously.

“Just a tiny bit!” Tang Rou said.

“How much is a tiny bit?” the host asked again.

“I sometimes helped her with a few matches in the Arena.” Tang Rou said.

“She even helped me finish the Heavenly Domain Challenge!” Chen Guo added.

The audience went into an uproar. For someone who barely touched Glory to have beaten the Heavenly Domain Challenge! And then after seeing her previous playing, how was that someone who had only played for a month? Of the countless players, how many of them could play like that?

The pros all looked at one another. Heavenly Domain Challenge? It wasn’t anything difficult in their eyes. But with this, they had a better understanding of Tang Rou’s skill and knew what having such skill with only one month of playing meant.

Before this, the pro players’ evaluation was only an “Oh, she’s not bad.” But after knowing that she was just a beginner who had only played for a month, now that was frightening.

Chapter 321 – After the Fireworks

Even though Tang Rou made everyone feel astonished, this wasn’t a stage that was set up for her; this was the All-Star event. After the High Jump, there were still other events. Which is why, no matter how mysterious and amazing Tang Rou was, the host could only give her so much attention.

“To have such skill after only a month of playing, that’s quite amazing, no?” The host walked to the three pros and asked them.

“It’s very amazing. I think she should consider entering the pro scene and further progress there.” One of the pros said.

The audience immediately turned into an uproar. Pro scene? That was a completely different existence. That was the true “Heavenly Domain”.

However, the host had a lot of experience. He wasn’t a stranger to these kinds of words. The words were more of an exaggerated compliment. He didn’t want to switch the focus back to Tang Rou at this moment, so he just laughed and continued to interview the pros. Afterwards, he interviewed the remaining players, even the Sharpshooter. Though when it got to him, the entire crowd booed. The Sharpshooter clearly wasn’t in a good mood. After answering two questions, he concluded the interview.

The host gave the chosen guests souvenirs and ended the event.

This result made Chen Guo very pleased. She had the chance to meet with her favorite idol and talk face to face with her. She received the entire stadium’s cheers during the event and, in the end, she even won the acknowledgement of her idol. She couldn’t be any happier. As for that shameful Sharpshooter, she had long forgotten about him.

Under the audience’s envious stares, the two returned to their seats. Chen Guo sat down and patted Ye Xiu’s back. She was the type of person who liked to share her happiness with others. Her way of sharing just happened to be more intense.

“That must have been fun!” Ye Xiu laughed.

“It was very fun.” Chen Guo said with her face full of smiles.

“And comrade Little Tang?” Ye Xiu put his hands up like a microphone and extended them towards Tang Rou’s mouth as if he were interviewing her.

“It was pretty fun.” Tang Rou smiled. The gaze she gave back to Ye Xiu seemed to hold a profound meaning to them.

After a short break, the host announced the third event: Targets.

This was also a traditional game played during All-Stars. The characters stood on a pillar and flying discs would come from all around them. Contestants could use any way they liked to break these flying discs and obtain points. The person who earned the most points was the overall winner.

“Next up, we invite Team Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian to pick this event’s four lucky guests!” the host shouted. The lights dimmed and a pillar of light descended onto Huang Shaotian as he stood up and walked towards the stage. This guy actually did have a bit of stardom in him. As he walked, he waved to the crowd.

“Hello, Shaotian.” The host shook Huang Shaotian’s hand.

“Hi to you. Hi to me. Hi everybody!” Huang Shaotian’s opening words were always more than other people’s.

The host clearly knew about his situation and began to sweat on the inside. The event was a live broadcast, so there was a certain time limit for each event. He couldn’t give him the chance to talk too much or else they would go off-schedule.

As he thought about this issue, the host didn’t give an introduction and directly asked: “Shaotian, how do you plan on picking our four lucky guests?”

“I want to use four different ways to pick our four lucky guests.” Huang Shaotian said.

He really does like to talk……. The host muttered to himself. With his face beaming like usual: “Then, how about we start?”

“For the first method, I want to use the random selection. I want to see if I’ll be able to yell out the number I’m looking for. Bro in charge of the machine, when you hear “Stop!”, you’ve gotta be quick!” Huang Shaotian said.

The host didn’t answer back. He waved his hand and the numbers began to roll.

“Ah, ah, just like that? Why didn’t you tell me first? Can I say stop yet? Hm?”

“You can…..” the host said.

“Stop!” Huang Shaotian shouted and the numbers stopped rolling. Huang Shaotian claimed that it had stopped on the number he wanted. No one knew if he was telling the truth or not. The host just complimented him with an “Amazing! Amazing!” and then asked the person with that seat number to come up.

The second method……

The third method…..

The fourth method…….

Huang Shaotian really did use four different methods to choose four guests. The host quickened the pace and shortened the interviews. The three pros that signed up came up and then they were rushed over to their match platforms.

The lights dimmed.

This time, the projected map wasn’t the first to appear. The eight characters appeared, scattered around the stadium. They were quite far from each other. Afterwards, the sounds of metal clanging rang out and pillars of the same size began to rise up from the stadium, lifting the eight characters into the air.

“Ready!” After the pillars locked into place, the host shouted.

“Begin!”

As soon as his words fell, countless whooshes sounded out and flying discs began shooting towards the eight players. Every flying disc was a different size and they flew at different speeds and angles.

This was only the beginning, though. Even normal players wouldn’t have trouble dealing with these flying discs. The eight characters drew their weapons and the sound of them breaking the flying discs were quite pleasing to the ear. In addition, after the flying discs broke, they would explode into bright, dazzling colors like fireworks.

This was a first for this event. Even though it was the same game, after each game, something new would be added.

These fireworks didn’t impact the game’s difficulty, but under the projection technology, the visual effects made it look much better.

Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh……

The flying discs continued to fly out, faster and faster, more and more.

The normal players were beginning to have trouble and, soon, some were unable to keep up.

If the flying disc hit a character, then the character would lose some health. And if the player wasn’t careful, he could be hit off the pillar. If the character’s health depletes to zero or if the character falls off the pillar, then the player would be eliminated from the game. If the character dodged the flying discs, then no points would be earned.

“Oh, no!” Along with a cry, one of the normal players made too large of a step when dodging and stepped off the pillar. He was immediately eliminated from the game.

As for the other three normal players, even though they didn’t directly fall down, in the end they weren’t able to completely block the flying discs. The fireworks exploded on their bodies and the three eventually died.

As for the pros, the four were very calm. Every one of the flying discs that shot towards them were hit down.

The theory was the same as the High Jump. The pros who signed up for the match were obviously those who had confidence in this area. In terms of just this one area for breaking flying discs, they might not be inferior to even a God like Huang Shaotian.

As the flying discs flew faster and faster, the bright fireworks continued to explode around the four pillars. The dazzling colors poured down, glimmering as if it were raining coins.

The applause and cheers from the audience were like thunder, allowing these colorful flowers to fully boom. Finally, when the final round exploded and descended down like falling stars, the flying discs stopped flying out.

The four characters were still standing on the pillars. If the contestants who signed up weren’t able to last until the end, then they might end up as a laughingstock.

The results quickly came out. Huang Shaotian won first, but even he wasn’t able to hit every single one of the flying discs. In the end, he missed two of them. As for the other three pros, they missed many more.

The pillars gradually fell. The characters were sent back to the ground and then faded away. The eight participants returned to the center of the stage to be interviewed. This time, Huang Shaotian was put last. In addition, the host only asked him a single question about how he was feeling. The host answered with a short “Thank you” and then concluded Huang Shaotian’s interview.

The three events all had their own good and bad points. Now, they were over. This time, there was a relatively long break in between. Many of the audience members got up to move around, go to the restroom, etc.

Chen Guo’s thoughts were still on the second event. Ye Xiu seriously doubted that she had paid any attention to the third event. She was completely in her own dream.

The stadium’s lights brightened. Chen Guo came back to reality and after seeing everyone go to the restroom, she immediately had the same feeling.

“Little Tang, are you going?” Chen Guo asked.

“I don’t need to…..” Tang Rou said.

As a result, Chen Guo went by herself. Ye Xiu continued to look around, when he saw Tang Rou sitting at Chen Guo’s seat, looking at him.

“What’s up?”

“Who are you really?’ Tang Rou suddenly asked.

“Hm?”

“Mu Mu’s voice is very pleasant to listen to and it’s unique. I can recognize it.” Tang Rou said.

“Oh? What’s unique about her voice?”

“Her words are very clear and clean.”

“How is that unique…..”

“And also that Huang Shaotian is actually Flowing Tree, right?” Tang Rou said.

“But you haven’t heard much from him, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“But his voice is also unique. When he speaks very fast, his words become more pointed.” Tang Rou said.

“You seem to have very good ears.” Ye Xiu said, “You don’t seem like anyone ordinary, either. Tell me, who are you?”

Chapter 322 – Secret Operation

“He he!” Tang Rou gave a sly smile, “Keep on guessing. But isn’t it already obvious who you are?”

“Oh?”

“Ye Xiu is Ye Qiu, no? Am I right?” Tang Rou asked.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu’s calm reply surprised Tang Rou. She thought that she had seen through his true identity, yet he didn’t seem to have any sort of reaction to it. Be it giving an excuse or telling her to keep it a secret, she didn’t expect him to reply so nonchalantly. If he really didn’t care, then why did he go so far as to change his name in order to hide his identity?

Tang Rou couldn’t understand. She looked at Ye Xiu and hoped to hear a reason why. But Ye Xiu returned a sly smile: “You want to know why I use two names? Unfortunately, I can’t tell you that.”

“Oh.” Tang Rou answered calmly. Even though she was curious, she could control it. If he didn’t want to reveal his secrets, then she wasn’t going to dig deeper.

“Can I tell Guo Guo?” Tang Rou asked.

“Up to you.” Ye Xiu was as nonchalant as before.

“It isn’t hard to imagine how she would react.” Tang Rou grinned.

“That’s hard to say. She might feel like her dreams were crushed.” Ye Xiu said.

After Tang Rou thought about it for a bit, she nodded her head: “That’s true.”

Ye Xiu chuckled and didn’t say anything more. Tang Rou returned to her original seat, but Chen Guo still hadn’t come back yet. After waiting a bit, the stadium’s lights began to dim. The break was clearly over and only then did she receive a short text from Chen Guo grumbling about the line to the restroom.

The event continued. The next All-Star Weekend event was the most traditional event: Player vs Pro Battle.

For this event, the pros would come out and receive challenges from the audience.

After the host announced this, Ye Xiu looked towards Tang Rou. Sure enough, he saw that the girl looked very eager to have a go. After hearing the host say they would be using the answering device on the seats armrest, she immediately put her hand on it.

Once the host finished explaining the process, he began to introduce the pro that would go up: Team Samsara’s Blade Master, Du Ming.

Even though he wasn’t a top-tier God, Du Ming was a part of Team Samsara’s main roster. His foundation was sturdy and his playing was bold. He was a player whose style stood out and was nicknamed the “Berserk Blade Master”. With the home ground advantage, he was met with loud cheers and applause from the crowd.

When Du Ming went up, he accepted a brief interview and then went to the competition platform. The host began to call for the audience members who wanted to challenge him to get ready..

“The instant that the electronic screen gives the signal, press on the answering device. Our system can detect them with an accuracy of 1/1000th of a second to determine who pressed it first. Everyone pay attention to the screens. Get ready.”

When the host finished his words, the stadium fell silent. There were quite a few audience members who wanted to challenge the pros. They were all focusing on the screen, waiting for the instant the signal popped up.

“Ding…..”

All of the electronic screens flashed at the same time. There was even a “Ding!”, the in-game notification sound used in the game. Those who wanted to participate immediately pressed the answering device. The host also raised his head. The first participant would soon be revealed on the electronic screens.

“Area C Row 18 Number 23!!!”

The instant the electronic screens revealed the result, the host shouted out the winner.

“Congratulations to this participant for having the chance to challenge Du Ming.” The host finished his report. The entire stadium was in an uproar. Those who had a good memory looked at this familiar seat number and quickly remembered that in the High Jump event, Su Mucheng had chosen this exact seat number. It was the beautiful Battle Mage.

“Impressive!” Ye Xiu was also amazed. He didn’t expect Tang Rou to actually have pressed the answering device first.

“I guess it’s luck?” Tang Rou was also quite surprised. For a method like this, she really didn’t expect herself to have won with just her own skill.

“Good luck.” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course.” Tang Rou got up and headed towards the stage again. The surrounding audience members all had an astonished expression on their faces. To be called up onto stage twice in an All-Stars Weekend had never happened before.

Though the host didn’t have a very good memory. When he looked at the seat number, he didn’t find anything astonishing about it. But once he saw Tang Rou go up on stage, he finally realized that she had already gone up on stage before in the High Jump event. She was one of the two very eye-catching beauties.

“Ha ha…….” The host organized his thoughts and then said: “Who would have thought that our winner would be an old friend! But we’ll still be going on as planned. You’ll still have to introduce yourself, even though everyone already knows you.”

“My name is Tang Rou and I play as a Battle Mage.” Tang Rou smiled.

“She has only played Glory for a month and she’s already gotten the chance to play with a pro player up on stage. Not only that, but she’s about to get her second chance! Miss Tang, your luck really isn’t ordinary!” Tang Rou had been the most eye-catching of all the guests that had come up on stage, so the host at least remembered this about her.

“I’m very honored.” Tang Rou said.

“Then let us see how you’ll do! Oh, right, do you still need an account?” the host said.

“Yeah I do!” Tang Rou nodded her head.

“Is the one you used previously okay?” The host asked.

“That’s fine!” Tang Rou didn’t object.

After receiving her account card, Tang Rou went to the competition platform. Right now, the audience were murmuring about her ridiculous luck. Chen Guo returned from the restroom and when she heard this, she cried out in surprise at Tang Rou’s luck. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, was aware that it might not necessarily be luck.

Tang Rou had talent in Glory. No one doubted this. Even someone like Wang Jiexi recognized it. And today, under the eyes of all the pro teams, Tang Rou had made a grand display. After knowing that she had only played Glory for only a month, that sort of performance was enough to catch the attention of these pro teams.

As for Samsara, using their home-ground advantage, they could very easily rig it so Tang Rou would be invited for this event. Tang Rou’s second appearance might not have been luck.

Ye Xiu thought of this as the match officially began.

The maps were chosen by the player. Tang Rou didn’t have any maps she was familiar with and just chose a random one.

The two characters appeared on the map and rushed towards the middle of the stage. Soon after, they both appeared within each other’s sights.

The two players didn’t have their characters stop. They continued to rush forward. Just before they were about to close in, a blade flashed! Du Ming had made the first move!

Tang Rou immediately moved and her character sidestepped it. She was also the type who liked to initiate, but before she could do so, the other side attacked. For Tang Rou, being at a disadvantage as soon as the match started was something she rarely saw.

Du Ming’s hit didn’t connect, but he didn’t give any chances for Tang Rou to counterattack. His character turned his hands and used an Upward Slash.

Tang Rou reacted quickly and rolled to the side, dodging it.

Triple Slash!

Sword Draw!

Rising Dragon Slash!

A rapid combo flowed out from Du Ming’s Blade Master. Blade light flashed around Tang Rou’s character. After just barely dodging the Triple Slash, the Blade Master’s next hit connected with her back. Experience was something Tang Rou was severely lacking. Her decision-making clearly wasn’t good enough and she was hit by the Sword Draw. The following Rising Dragon launched Tang Rou’s Battle Mage into the air.

Falling Phoenix Slash!

Rising Dragon Slash into a Falling Phoenix Slash was a commonly used Blade Master combo. To the audience, seeing the combo coming out of a pro’s hands seemed to add to the impact.

The descending slash could not be dodged and she was cut down from her waist. Du Ming wouldn’t let up. After a Falling Phoenix Slash, he followed up with a Falling Light Blade and he chased after Tang Rou’s falling character like an arrow.

Tang Rou’s quick fingers burst forth. As soon as she hit the ground, she quickly used a Quick Recover to roll to the side. Du Ming’s Falling Light Blade descended, but it had been dodged. When he lifted his head after finishing the animation, a battle spear thrust towards him like a viper. Du Ming hastily put up a Guard. “Dang!” He blocked the Dragon Tooth and was pushed back several steps.

Even though the Guard had been successful and he wasn’t stunned, the damage was only reduced and he would still take damage. Under this situation, a Battle Mage’s Chaser would be created. Tang Rou fired the Neutral Chaser towards Du Ming.

The Chaser automatically chased after the target and couldn’t be dodged. But just as it was about to explode, a blade light flashed and the Neutral Chaser was split into two before exploding. Du Ming had sliced it apart.

“How unfortunate…..”

The audience wasn’t too interested in this match. They all hoped to be able to go up onto the stage and fight with a pro.

As for those in the pro player seats, they were all watching the match intently. Like Ye Xiu, they were wondering if Samsara had rigged the event in order to have her come up onto the stage. Although, this was also what they wanted to see, too. Everyone wanted to know just how good this player, who had only played for a month, was.

Chapter 323 – Noob Strategy

“How unlucky!” Quite a few pros sighed after seeing Tang Rou’s Chaser get blocked.

“If she hadn’t used Dragon Tooth that time and used a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky instead, then Du Ming probably would have been hit.”

“Yeah, this girl’s hands are very quick! If she had used a Rising Dragon, it would have certainly connected.”

“So she really is a new player? She hasn’t used a single Level 40 and above skill. It truly is unfortunate…..”

Usually, the pros rarely went into such a serious discussion over the for-show All-Star Weekend. And as the pros discussed, the audience’s mood also began to move.

They had thought that after being hit by the Sword Draw, Tang Rou’s Battle Mage would be locked into a combo. No one had thought that Tang Rou would be able to Quick Recover after being hit by the Falling Phoenix Slash.

It has to be known that a character hit by Falling Phoenix Slash would crash down like a meteor, which was extremely quick. By successfully using a Quick Recover and then immediately beginning a counterattack, the exchange had actually ended disfavorably for the pro player, Du Ming.

“Ah, why didn’t she use Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!” Chen Guo was an experienced player and even she had felt that that would have been the correct move.

“Rising Dragon Soars the Sky…… She probably doesn’t know how to use it?” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh right…… I forgot.” Chen Guo suddenly realized.

“Do you think Little Tang has a chance at winning?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“You….. don’t look down on pros!”

As soon as he said this, the tables turned.

After Tang Rou comboed a few times, Du Ming quickly seized an opportunity to take back the initiative. He used several skills and normal attacks to restrict her, luring the inexperienced Tang Rou into a trap, which ended with Tang Rou getting hit by the Level 70 Blade Master’s ultimate skill, “Formless Phantom Blade”.

Under the relentless slashes, blood flew out all over the stage from Tang Rou’s Battle Mage. The electronic screen soon showed the combo count.

Mirage Blade relied on the player’s skill to fully utilize the combo. The higher the combo, the higher the damage. Currently, the highest record was 13 and there were already many Blade Masters who could reach this, but no one had gotten to the 14th blade yet.

In order to achieve what looked to be the limit, the move’s distance and angle had to be calculated. Du Ming’s Mirage Blade had completed early because of Tang Rou’s extremely quick reactions. She was able to force a dodge even in a hopeless situation, causing Du Ming to end the Mirage Blade at 10 blades.

The final blade made by Mirage Blade had a strong Blow Away effect. This attack was very important. If this attack didn’t connect, then the one-second “stun” from the end-animation allowed for more than enough time to completely return the damage.

As a pro, Du Ming obviously wouldn’t mess up at this crucial moment. After the final blade came out, Tang Rou’s Battle Mage was blown away.

As of now, the opponent practically hadn’t taken any damage, while Tang Rou’s Battle Mage had already lost a fifth of her health.

The current Tang Rou was no longer the same Tang Rou from before. She now understood the gap between her and Du Ming. Especially in the last move, she had been completely suppressed by her opponent. Blow after blow, the opponent forced her into a specific situation until she had no choice but to eat that final blow.

In order to beat an opponent, one had to know where the gap was.

Tang Rou remembered what Ye Xiu said, but she discovered that the gap between her and these pros was truly too wide.

Experience was the greatest different between them. Tang Rou’s battle experience was equivalent to a noob’s. In front of these pros, it wasn’t nearly enough. They could easily see through her intents and thwart her plans. And then they could easily lure her into a trap.

“She really is a new player…..”

While Tang Rou thought about this, the pros were also discussing.

Tang Rou was a new player. This was something that was thoroughly exposed after she had to face a pro like Du Ming. If some of them had been doubting it before, then now it was for certain.

But this confirmation only made Tang Rou more valuable. Next up, how would the new player react? Everyone looked forward to seeing it.

Tang Rou moved!

Even though she clearly recognized the gap, when Du Ming charged forward, she did the same without hesitation.

Dragon Tooth!

This time, Tang Rou beat Du Ming to it. Her Battle Mage’s Dragon Tooth stabbed forward.

Sky Strike!

Double Stab!

Circle Swing!

Falling Flower Palm!

Like before, she only used these pitiful low-level skills along with a few normal attacks mixed in.

Du Ming calmly dodged them and prepared to strike back.

An opening!

Tang Rou’s attack had unexpectedly completely missed. Du Ming saw the chance and used Sword Draw!

“Pu!”

The sound of an attack hitting.

Du Ming discovered in astonishment that the one hit wasn’t his opponent, but himself. The missed attack was somehow turned around towards his body.

It was only a normal attack and it didn’t do much damage, but it was completely out of Du Ming’s expectations.

Tang Rou’s attacks continued. Du Ming gradually felt some pressure. He could clearly feel that his opponent’s attacks were growing faster and faster.

“Her hand speed is increasing!” The pros could sense this. They discovered in astonishment that Tang Rou’s hand speed hadn’t been at her limit before. Now, her attacks were growing faster and faster.

“So she was hiding her strength!” one gasped.

“No….. this isn’t hidden strength……”

“Her attacks might be faster……. But there’s no thought put into them.” Many of the pros realized this.

Tang Rou’s attacks didn’t seem to have any plans behind them. They were just being used for the sake of being used. If she didn’t have any skills available, she would use normal attacks.

This was a noob’s strategy, through and through. There was no showing of knowledge or decision-making. The attacks would simply go wherever the opponent was.

This type of strategy shouldn’t have any power behind it. But right now, it was completely suppressing Du Ming.

Because of hand speed!

Through just hand speed, Tang Rou’s level was already at a pro level. It was just that her attacks weren’t very accurate, so in order to maintain accuracy, she had to slow down her hands. But right now, she no longer cared about all this. She would do her utmost to send out her moves as quickly as possible.

“Her hand speed…… How fast is it?”

“That’s hard to say…. There’s a lot of useless movement……”

The pros were all somewhat speechless. When they talked about hand speed, they usually only considered meaningful moves. But right now, Tang Rou didn’t care. Speed, speed, speed! She was only seeking speed! Under her whirlwind hand speed, many of her attacks hit nothing. No one knew just how many missteps she made or just how many moves she wasted. Although, this type of method was enough to stop Du Ming, for now.

“How incredible!” Chen Guo was somewhat dumbstruck at the scene.

“How smart!” Ye Xiu smiled.

“What do you mean?”

“She finally understood where their gaps were, so she chose to use a method to avoid her lacking parts.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?”

“In a normal battle, because she lacks experience, she has no way of seizing the initiative. As a result, she simply decided not to think about all this. Right now, she is simply using the methods she knows to attack her opponent as quickly as possible. Because of her exceptional hand speed, even a beginner like her could look mighty through her random attacks.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“So you’re saying Little Tang could win?” Chen Guo said excitedly.

“Unfortunately, I don’t think so.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Why?”

“Because she’ll get tired….. How long can she keep up such attacks?” Ye Xiu said.

Ye Xiu wasn’t the only one to see this point. All of the pros watching analyzed this. After Tang Rou’s explosive hand speed, they could fully see her limit. No one knew better than the pros just how hard it was to keep such a hand speed up.

With this type of rhythmless hand speed, the winner would be the person who endured the longest.

Du Ming was a pro player, so he also understood this. However, as the “Berserk Blade Master”, being suppressed like this made him feel very depressed. But there was nothing he could do about it. There was no way he could have predicted that his opponent would do this, because she was just randomly attacking. He had no way of taking back the initiative, because he couldn’t help but acknowledge that, based on hand speed, he was unexpectedly unable to keep up with this guest.

“This new player really does have some skill, though how long can she keep this up?” Du Ming thought as he looked at his character’s health.

Chapter 324 – Desire for Victory

Tired……

Tang Rou quickly felt it. After not even a minute of such intense playing, her fingers began to feel tired. And then at her wrists, her elbows, and her arms, fatigue struck.

How long could she last? Tang Rou didn’t know and didn’t think about it, either. Her concentration was entirely focused on her opponent. As she made fierce attacks, she also tried her hardest to maintain accuracy. She hoped that more of her attacks would fall on her opponent.

One minute…..

Two minutes….

Three minutes……

The expressions on the pros’ faces began to change. They discovered that this girl’s hand speed wasn’t the scariest part about her, but rather it was her perseverance.

Four minutes! She was actually able to keep up such a hand speed for four minutes. Many of the pros were already asking themselves how long they could keep up their fastest hand speed.

Even scarier was that she still wasn’t done after four minutes. Her fast fingers continued to move…….

“If she knew had know how to use more powerful skills, then she might have already won the match…….” one player said.

“That might not be true. Powerful skills have larger openings. With her random fighting, powerful skills will only create openings for her opponent and, no matter how fast her fingers are, it’s not possible to get rid of the system’s end animation!”

“If it’s like that, then only knowing how to use low-level skills is actually an advantage for her……”

“Unfortunately, low-level skills don’t do much damage and her accuracy is quite poor, too….. With her current pace, if she wants to beat Du Ming, then she’d need at least ten minutes.”

“She can’t keep it up for ten minutes, right?”

“……”

No one dared to jump to the conclusion because Tang Rou already made them feel inconceivable. Such a strong desire to win was rare for a show like this. They already couldn’t understand just how much energy she had.

Five minutes……

Six minutes…..

In the blink of an eye, two minutes had passed and the Battle Mage’s relentless play style continued being maintained.

“What’s going on, is she cheating…….” With every passing minute, Du Ming grew more and more nervous. His Blade Master’s health had already gone down by more than half and there were no signs of weariness from his opponent or any extremely large openings. He could feel that the other side was trying her hardest. Even though she couldn’t maintain accuracy, she was giving her utmost to win.

“Pu!”

Another sound of being hit. During these few minutes, Du Ming had already grown numb to these sounds. After being hit so many times, the only reason he was still here was because they were all either low-level skills or they were normal attacks. Du Ming didn’t feel nervous towards these attacks and was actually trying to dodge these attacks. Whenever he was hit, it meant that his hand speed wasn’t able to keep up. There was nothing that he could do about it.

“Pu!”

Who would have thought that not long after, another sound resounded. Du Ming was hit again by Tang Rou’s battle spear.

“Pupupupu……”

In the next minute, the sounds of being hit became more and more hurried. Du Ming’s Blade Master was hit multiple times.

“What’s going on?” Du Ming was startled. The pros were also startled.

“Her hand speed is still increasing??”

“No….. not her……” Suddenly, some of the more perceptive players noticed the issue.

“It’s not that her hand speed increased, but rather Du Ming’s hand speed slowed down…..”

“Even though her attacks have no strategy behind them, Du Ming has also been trying his utmost to dodge these attacks. If not for that, he would have died a long time ago.”

“If the opponent attacks faster, than he also has to dodge faster……”

“In a high-speed battle, speed isn’t only used by one person, but rather, they were used by both sides.”

“Even though Du Ming isn’t using as much energy as his opponent, he was the first to be hit by the fatigue.”

Just when everyone was wondering whether Tang Rou would be able to last for ten minutes, they astonishingly discovered that the first one that would be unable to persist was Du Ming.

Attacks continued to land on the Blade Master. Du Ming startled at first, thinking that his opponent’s hand speed had increased, but he quickly noticed that he had been the one that had slowed down. And now, he was already at a red blood status.

He was going to lose!

Du Ming finally realized.

From the beginning to the end, he had never considered this. No matter how fast his opponent’s hands were, she was just an inexperienced new player. How could she keep on using such a barbaric strategy to the end?

This was the origin of Du Ming’s confidence, but he didn’t think that the opponent would really last until the end, up to the point where even he wasn’t able to keep on going.

“Du Ming is going to lose…… he lost because his desire to win wasn’t as strong.” one player sighed.

Everyone was silent.

Without a doubt, for a show like this, the pros really didn’t care about winning. When going against normal players, they didn’t need to care about winning.

But for normal players, it was different. Beating a pro player had a different meaning to them. Their desire to win would, of course, be much greater than a pro’s desire.

The desire to win and their hand speed was the difference between Du Ming and Tang Rou. This difference was completely grasped by Tang Rou, while Du Ming’s confidence, that there was no way he would ever lose, was now exposed.

The already somewhat panicked Du Ming was unable to come back when in Red Blood and his Blade Master quickly fell to Tang Rou’s Battle Mage.

The entire stadium was silent.

This year, there were too many unprecedented events in the All-Star Weekend. And now, a normal player had even beat a pro player.

This match clearly wasn’t a match that was meticulously planned. Even the audience was able to see that Tang Rou’s crazy hand speed had firmly suppressed Du Ming.

No one thought of cheering at this moment.

This was Samsara’s home ground and Du Ming was one of their main players. Being beaten by a normal player was absolutely shameful to the majority of the audience.

After a moment of silence, someone suddenly shouted angrily. After that, rowdy jeering spread to every corner of the stadium.

For their own team, fans didn’t only support them but when there was something that they weren’t happy about, they would mercilessly speak out.

This was where these angry shouts originated from.

In addition, everyone was together. Nobody talked about what Tang Rou wasn’t. They were all pointing out how useless Du Ming was.

From the beginning till the end, not only did Du Ming lose, he lost miserably.

In the end, the match took 7 minutes and 34 seconds. Du Ming had been thoroughly suppressed for 7 minutes, all the way until he had died.

The angry shouts grew louder and louder and the words they were saying grew more and more varied. The audience was completely out of control. The host’s voice was drowned out by them and no one could hear what he was saying.

These sort of shouts weren’t unfamiliar to a pro player. Many had experienced this before. For example, when Excellent Era’s Liu Hao gave away the match, Excellent Era’s fans mercilessly swore at him.

Amidst these angry shouts, Tang Rou and Du Ming left their platforms and stood at the center of the stage.

The shouts immediately rose to even high volumes and Du Ming was so sad that he wanted to die.

After constant calls to keep order, the host was finally able to calm the down audience a bit.

“Look at that guy’s face. Ha ha ha ha!” Chen Guo excitedly handed the binoculars over to Ye Xiu, while laughing uncontrollably. This immediately drew numerous angry glares from the surrounding audience members. After Ye Xiu took the binoculars, he found that he was in a dangerous position. After all, Chen Guo was a beautiful girl, so she had a bit of privilege. If he laughed as arrogantly as she did, then he couldn’t guarantee that the furious audience members wouldn’t get into a fight with him.

After using the binoculars to take a look, he saw that Du Ming’s expression really was quite splendid. On the other hand, Tang Rou didn’t look any different than the previous match. Her energy and determination were definitely her greatest talents.

After the stadium gradually calmed down, the host’s voice could finally be heard.

But the first to speak wasn’t the host; it was Du Ming.

He took the initiative to ask for another match with Tang Rou.

His intent was obvious. He wanted to win the match to regain his honor. But who would have thought that he would bring in another round of laughter.

A pro player wanted to compete with a normal player. In their eyes, his challenge only proved how little of a future he had.

Du Ming’s face turned even more ugly.

He was shouted at for losing and for trying to win back his honor. Was there really nowhere he could turn to?

Though amidst these shouts, Tang Rou’s voice sounded out: “Okay, I accept your challenge.”

The entire stadium went into another uproar. The situation had turned into Du Ming challenging the normal player.

There were still those who were angry at Du Ming for having no future, but Tang Rou’s arrogance also brought about a lot of discontent. Quite a few impolite words were thrown down towards Tang Rou. After all, Du Ming was the person that they truly supported. It was tough love. They felt that it was okay for them to be angry, but if some outsider disrespected him, then they would stand at their player’s side.

Amidst these shouts, Tang Rou was actually even more mature than the pro. She didn’t care at all and simply walked onto the competition platform.

The host didn’t know what to do. Playing another match just after finishing one was something that had never happened before. The experienced host could only feel that this year’s All-Star Event had truly become a mess.

Chapter 325 – It’s a Mess. A Complete Mess.

Amidst the shouts that were coming from all around the stadium, Du Ming returned to the match platform.

Even though winning back a match would not be able to erase the previous match’s loss, it would still be better than sitting back and doing nothing. Aside from playing another match, Du Ming didn’t know of any better method to come back.

Tang Rou once again randomly chose a map and the match quickly began. The host hadn’t even run off the stage yet, when the projection fell.

The stadium’s noise lessened after the match started. It had originally been an insignificant performance, but now they were beginning to care about who won or lost. Due to Tang Rou’s previous arrogance, numerous people were hoping to see her get crushed in this match.

This time, Du Ming wouldn’t be as careless. He wouldn’t carry the attitude that he would certainly win. His focus was now 120% and he had the conviction that he had to be victorious during this match.

The two sides fought and Du Ming quickly seized the advantage.

Du Ming’s fingers also flew quickly and he took the initiative, time and time again. He wanted to return everything Tang Rou had done to him, back to her.

Du Ming’s hand speed might not be as good as Tang Rou’s, but the quality of his actions was on a completely different level. Every action maintained accuracy and effectiveness. Even though he could randomly attack like Tang Rou previously did…… as a pro player, if he used that sort of tactic, he’d probably drown in the audience’s spittle.

He had to win and he had to win beautifully to let everyone know that the previous loss was just a mishap, an anomaly. His own skill completely soared above this normal player.

As for Tang Rou, she repeated her old strategy and randomly attacked by moving her fingers as fast as possible.

This time, the feeling of fatigue struck faster while her opponent was brimming with battle spirit. The two sides began a true contest of hand speed.

One side had quality.

The other side had speed.

Comparing the two, Tang Rou’s hand speed really wasn’t that much faster than his, but the quality of Du Ming’s actions were much, much better than hers.

In the end, the quality won.

But Du Ming didn’t have it easy, either. He couldn’t have imagined that such a pretty girl, who just had an intense battle, would accept another match without any rest.

He could win this match, but it would be quite difficult to win as beautifully as he’d have liked.

Regardless, he had to win this time.

Du Ming clenched his teeth and fought. But Tang Rou didn’t back down, either.

The pros were once again astonished…… even under this situation where she had already won a match, she was still going to maintain such a strong desire to win?

Was she really just a normal player? The pros discovered that they were all wrong. Even though her skill level was truly inferior to theirs, she still caught their attention. She wasn’t like the other normal players. She wasn’t thinking how amazing these pros were or how superior they were to them.

She truly wanted to beat them. This wasn’t just for fun. It was a true competition.

“This girl’s…… abnormal?” One player couldn’t help but make this somewhat impolite evaluation.

“After seeing this girl, I suddenly want to go up and play!” Quite a few players remarked.

There weren’t many players who were paying too much attention to the match now. With their experience, the pros quickly determined who would win the match. The reality was just like they had determined. Du Ming’s Blade Master took down Tang Rou’s Battle Mage.

How tiring, but how great!

Du Ming was dripping with joy after this battle. When he got down from the competition platform, he was nearly smiling.

At the center of the stage, the host was already somewhat speechless towards these two. Then, Tang Rou unexpectedly spoke.

“Can I challenge you again?”

Du Ming was startled. The host was startled. The audience was startled.

The first to react was still the host. He hastily followed: “Miss, that doesn’t conform to the rules, no?”

“What rules?” Tang Rou asked.

According to the rules, after an audience member finishes a match, a new one would come up. This rule had already been broken and the one who broke it was Du Ming. He did it in order to regain his reputation and dragged the audience member to play another round. They had already broken the rules once, so they couldn’t just fix it again, right? It wouldn’t be fair to say that the pro player had special privileges, right?

The host didn’t know what to say. Tang Rou ignored him and only asked Du Ming.

Du Ming could only agree. He couldn’t refuse because he couldn’t find a reason to. If he had won the first time, then he had the right to refuse another challenge. But the problem now was that he had lost once and he had lost very badly, too. Now that the other side wanted to challenge him again, he had no way of refusing. If he refused, then people might think he was afraid. Because last match, he hadn’t won without putting in effort, he couldn’t help but admit that against a new player with that type of hand speed and that type of random attacking tactic, if he didn’t focus, he really might lose just like he did the first time.

Amidst the audience’s confusion, the two started the third round.

“It’s a mess, a complete mess……” the host muttered. The team responsible for the broadcast were also going crazy. But there was nothing that they could do. They couldn’t just force them to leave the stage in front of all of these spectators, right?

In the blink of an eye, the third match began and Tang Rou once again ferociously moved her fingers.

“Still so fierce……”

Compared to the worried host and broadcast team, the pros didn’t care. In fact, they found it more interesting.

“Does this girl plan on using the same strategy over and over again to outlast Du Ming?” someone guessed.

“How fierce!”

“But the host won’t allow it! Or else it’ll never end……”

“Little Zhou, what do you think?” One pro even ran over to Samsara’s team to ask. Now, the pros were no longer secretly whispering amongst their own team about Tang Rou’s skill. The exciting scene made them gather together into one joyous group.

Samsara wasn’t included in these happy teams. Du Ming was one of their players but when other pros ran over to ask them, Samsara’s players stayed silent. Zhou Zekai, who was mentioned by name, replied: “No idea!”

“It’d be best if they didn’t interrupt them, so we can see just what that girl is planning.” One player said.

“No idea!” Zhou Zekai repeated himself, making the other pros walk away speechlessly. They looked around, wanting to see what the host would try and do to stop them. Right now, no one was paying attention to the content of the match. Some weren’t even paying attention to the end result. They just wanted to know if there would be a next match, whether there would be a fourth or a fifth match, and also whether it would continue until one person collapsed from exhaustion.

The pros looked all around, but they didn’t find anything. Though, for Ye Xiu and Chen Guo, one of the employees there looked for them.

“Miss, that Miss Tang on the stage is your friend, right?” The employee asked politely.

“Yup!” Chen Guo replied. She cared a lot about who won or lost. She watched intently and hadn’t really noticed him.

“Could I ask that both of you have her come down after the match ends?” The employee said.

“Hm?” Only then did Chen Guo turn to look and discover that the host had unexpectedly run over.

“You see, we have to give other people a chance! She’s already played three rounds.” The host tried to reason. He was clearly afraid that they were going to play another match after the current one ended.

“If they want to fight, then let them!” Chen Guo didn’t want the excitement to end. She didn’t want to drag Tang Rou down.

“But our event needs to continue. I beg of you.”

“Isn’t that the event right there?” Chen Guo said.

These one on one matches usually only took a few minutes. The host personally running off stage to try and negotiate with Chen Guo was clearly a mistake. While they were talking, the two finished the match.

And this time, Tang Rou unexpectedly won again. The two once again competed with their hand speeds, but this time, Tang Rou performed abnormally well. As for Du Ming, because he had won a match, he had relaxed considerably and hadn’t expected Tang Rou to be so abnormally accurate with her actions. Her randomly thrown out attacks suddenly jumped up a level and he hadn’t able to adjust in time. Amidst another wave of shouts, he lost once again.

The host was still begging Chen Guo, when Ye Xiu reminded him. The host turned around to look and almost coughed up blood.

And this time, Tang Rou didn’t come down again. Du Ming had challenged her again, which Tang Rou naturally accepted. The two didn’t even wait for the host and directly started another round.

“Wow, Du Ming’s luck is so bad!!” The pros were almost about to roll on the floor laughing. In this match, Tang Rou’s unsteady actions suddenly became more on point out of nowhere, catching Du Ming off-guard.

After losing a match, he had to win the next one to win back some of his reputation. If he won again after that, then that would truly be better. But he unexpectedly lost another one. Who knew how many more he needed to win in a row to win back his reputation.

This time, the host didn’t dare delay any further and hastily ran back.

“Forget about it. I’ll call her down!” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was a soft on the inside, but hard on the outside type of person. In reality, she had already been convinced by the host. Her previous words were done to delay the host and help Tang Rou play another match. Now that she heard Ye Xiu say this, she nodded her head: “Alright, go ahead!”

Chapter 326 – Refusing to Give Up

Du Ming’s face fell ashen. He didn’t dare be careless anymore. He brought out 120% of his concentration and quickly seized the advantage.

At the pro player seats, besides Samsara’s players, everyone else laughed crazily.

They could all clearly see that Du Ming’s skill level was absolutely above that girl’s. It was just that the girl wasn’t a simple normal player. Du Ming had been careless and had unexpectedly gotten into a such a low probability occurrence and lost. And that wasn’t all. When the low probability occurrence happened again, they were beginning to doubt whether it really was a low probability.

In the audience’s eyes, when a pro player fought against a normal player, the pro should win ten times out of ten. But currently, they had played a total of three matches and Du Ming had actually lost two of them. Another wave of boos and shouts flooded the stadium. Right now, even if Du Ming won the next match, he wouldn’t be able to win back his reputation. In order to prove that those two losses had just been lucky flukes, he’d have to win at least eighteen matches in a row. But they were at the All-Star event; how could they be allowed to do that?

Thinking of this, Du Ming’s mood fell even further into depression. But he didn’t dare get distracted. If he lost again, then he wouldn’t be able to even show his face anymore.

The complete mess of a match continued. The stage showed the projection and the host could only stand there with a face full of bitterness. He had already sent other employees to continue urging Chen Guo and he constantly looked over in that direction. In the end, he saw Ye Xiu walk down and, after a short blank stare, he recognized him as someone who was with the two girls and immediately went to welcome him.

“I’ll go call her down!” Ye Xiu said to the host.

“Thank you! Thank you!” The host was so moved that he almost broke down crying.

Ye Xiu looked around and pointed in a direction: “Can I go up that way?”

The host stared blankly for a second before nodding his head: “Yes, you can…..”

Ye Xiu nodded his head and followed along the edges of the stage to there. The host watched as Ye Xiu walked and then the host scratched his head in doubt. Because of the projection, all of the lights were turned off for the match. The little ladder over there couldn’t be seen in the darkness. That person……. seemed to be quite familiar with the stage.

Although, in the end, he had come to save the event, so the host settled down and continued to pay attention to the match’s situation. This time, Du Ming actually went all out and completely dismantled Tang Rou’s random attacking strategy. Du Ming carefully determined which of the random attacks were effective, which ones were misses and, through this, he ferociously sent out counterattacks.

This match ended very quickly and the host reckoned that his rescuer wouldn’t be able to make it in time! But if the two came down to talk…….

There was no if…..

Tears streaked down the host’s cheeks. The two didn’t come down from their platforms and began a new match. And this time, the entire audience was able to see that the person to make the challenge was once again Du Ming and not the loser, Tang Rou.

Tang Rou decisively accepted the challenge again.

“HA HA HA HA, Du Ming’s really impatient!” Many of the pros were laughing. They knew what Du Ming was thinking. He was impatient to hurry and win more matches to take back some of his face. He knew that there wasn’t enough time to completely negate those two losses, but he had no choice; he could only do things like this. Using what few minutes he had, he had to win as many matches as possible!

Tang Rou once again used her old strategy. Du Ming’s desire to win now had finally reached its peak. He completely controlled the match and not a single opening appeared on him. He repeatedly attacked, finally showing why he was called the “Berserk Blade Master”. This match was won even quicker than the last.

They didn’t exit the match and fought again. The one to initiate the challenge was Du Ming, again.

The booing had stopped and the audience also realized what Du Ming wanted to do. He just wanted to prove himself. He wanted to return fire to the audience’s boos.

As a home player, the audience still supported Du Ming on the inside. Their boos could be considered a wake-up call to encourage him. And the results finally came through. Their boos weren’t for nothing and the crowd felt very gratified.

The next match started again. Even though the previous two matches had been finished quickly, the fact that it was the sixth match already was a reality. As the person responsible for controlling the event, the host was extremely nervous and hard-pressed. His headpiece was filled with sounds from the backstage crew to hurry up and resolve the problem. As for the broadcasting team, they just directly cut to the advertisements.

But how was he going to resolve it? He had gone through a lot of trouble to find a way to get Tang Rou down, but how could he have known that the problem wasn’t on Tang Rou’s side, but Du Ming, who refused to give up proving himself after losing two times……

Helpless, the host could only run over to the pro player seats again and hope that Samsara’s players would persuade Du Ming. But in his heart, he felt that it wasn’t likely. Samsara’s players definitely didn’t want Du Ming to lose face, either, and might even support his current actions. Plus, with Zhou Zekai’s slow responses, he would be asked a question and then think about it for a minute. By the time he finished thinking, the match would be over…..

The host ran over to Samsara’s side and, sure enough, they were all humming as if they were deaf and mute. Right now, Du Ming was going all out. With the opponent not running away and fighting head on, the battles were extremely quick. The matches lasted one to two minutes. As soon as the host reached the pro player seats to say a few words, the match had already ended.

The winner was, once again, Du Ming and the person who refused to rest was also Du Ming.

“Three wins in a row……” Du Ming counted. How many matches did he need to win? He didn’t have a count in his head. He just knew that there wouldn’t be enough time for him to get all the matches he needed, so he didn’t bother thinking about it.

“I’ll just keep going until someone stops me.” Du Ming thought and once again issued a challenge. The other side naturally accepted. The audience let out astonished cries. When was this complete mess of a battle going to end?

As soon as they began, Du Ming immediately put his whole mind and body into the match. The host tried his hardest to persuade Samsara’s members. However, these friends of Du Ming clearly exposed their team’s tacit agreement. Their thoughts were the same as Du Ming: just keep going until someone stops them. But the ones who would stop them definitely weren’t going to be Samsara. As a result, they all sought to delay or ignore the host.

In the blink of an eye, another match concluded. Du Ming successfully won four times in a row. After displaying the skill a pro player should have, Tang Rou had no chance.

Du Ming looked around and, since he didn’t see anyone trying to stop them, he immediately issued another challenge.

Tang Rou didn’t hesitate and went to accept the next match. But when she moved her mouse, she felt a shudder. The instant she was about to click accept, a hand came out from the side and pressed down on her hand.

Tang Rou was surprised, but she was quickly able to recognize who the hand belonged to.

“That’s enough!” Ye Xiu called.

Tang Rou lifted up her head, her gaze determined: “I can win.”

Ye Xiu nodded his head: “You can win, but he can, too. For every ten matches he wins, you will win one. What is that supposed to mean? If you only wanted to prove that you could win, you’ve already done so.”

“I can beat him!” Tang Rou said.

“You think you can beat him?” Ye Xiu laughed, “I think you’re making a big misunderstanding! In Glory, you don’t compete until the last player stands; you compete until the last character stands. Even if you kept playing until he became so tired that he had no way of continuing, I can assure you, the number of times he’ll have won will be much greater than yours. In the end, he’ll have been the one to win, not you.”

Tang Rou stared blankly. She stared at that Battle Mage on her screen and didn’t say anything for a long time.

“And I have to remind you that among the pro players, there are many many players who are just as determined and tenacious as you are. Don’t look down on others!” Ye Xiu followed.

The electronic screen stayed fixed like this. Previously, the match had always started immediately, but this time, there was no response.

“Why isn’t she accepting it?” Du Ming was very impatient. Currently, the score was 5 to 2. He felt that it wasn’t even close to enough. He still wanted to win more to prove himself.

“What’s wrong? Can she not go on?” The pros weren’t laughing anymore and were discussing amongst each other again. For the teams other than Samsara, they didn’t care at all about what Du Ming was feeling. They wanted to use this opportunity to see just how good this new player was.

The only happy one was the host. He reckoned that the rescuer had finally arrived and persuaded the girl to stop playing. As a result, the host stopped bothering with Samsara’s players and ran back to the stage.

On the screen, Tang Rou’s game interface had gone dark. She had already logged out from the game. Tang Rou stood up and was ready to follow Ye Xiu out from the match platform.

But who would have thought that Du Ming would suddenly shout from across the stage.

“What’s wrong? You don’t dare fight me?”

It was a provocation that pros often used, but it was a bit excessive to say that to a normal player. Though for Du Ming, he felt that he hadn’t won enough. Since the opponent didn’t want to fight anymore, he hoped that his opponent would say that she admitted defeat or something along those lines.

Not dare? These weren’t words in Tang Rou’s dictionary. She immediately turned around to fight, when Ye Xiu calmly turned on the booth’s speakers.

“How about I give it a try?” Ye Xiu said.

The entire audience went into an uproar. Where did this guy come from?

Chapter 327 – A True Expert

The host, who was halfway to the stage, suddenly heard this and almost tripped. He suddenly felt that he had let a wolf into the house.

The broadcast team backstage suddenly shouted at him: “F*ck, where’s the next person? Hurry up and get him on stage. We’ve already been broadcasting ads for five minutes!!!”

The host nearly rolled and crawled his way onto the stage, when Du Ming asked the question that everyone wanted to know: “Who are you?”

“The main player is tired. I’m the substitute.” Ye Xiu replied calmly.

The audience laughed. They were wondering if the event host had intentionally sent someone funny out.

At this moment, the host jumped onto the stage. The lights lit up and he announced, gasping for breath, for the second challenger to come up.

The host wanted to hurry up and get to the second challenger. Even though he knew that the person who had just gone up seemed to be someone who would mess things up, in any case, they at least moved a step forward!

As result, the second challenger didn’t even get a round of polite applause. The people in the audience were still in disbelief! They didn’t even know how this guy had gotten up onto the stage.

The pro players all had a big question mark above them, as well. This year’s All-Star event had turned into a complete mess! Even they didn’t know what was going to happen next.

“Are you ready?” Ye Xiu said.

“You have to log in first……” Du Ming was depressed. Since things were already like this, he didn’t withdraw. It’s not like he could call for only that girl to come out! That would be too shameful.

“Oh, my bad, one sec!” Ye Xiu said.

The audience then heard a voice call out from the booth.

“Give me the account card!”

“No need, I’ll go!”

“Don’t be fussy…… Hurry and give it to me!”

“I refuse……”

Pa…… Everyone in the stadium was dumbstruck. The booth’s speakers had been turned off.

Pa……. It sounded like the speakers had been hit on. Sounds of fighting transmitted out on and off.

“Ha ha, one second everyone. It looks like our employee and our challenger are having a bit of a problem exchanging account cards……..” With his forehead dripping with sweat, the host spoke nonsense. The audience immediately booed in response.

“Maybe I should go up and check…….” the host muttered. The game interface finally appeared on the electronic screens. The Battle Mage had finally logged in.

“What type of skill distribution is this…….” After hearing this, another “pa!” and the speaker turned off again.

Du Ming felt like his luck was truly terrible today. Why did all of this happen to him? Just as he was feeling annoyed, the other side finished logging in and sent out a challenge.

Du Ming accepted. No matter who the opponent was, he didn’t dare be careless again.

After the two had accepted the match, the two characters appeared on stage.

On one end of the stage, Du Ming’s Blade Master charged forward. With how he was feeling, he was prepared to use this match to vent his anger. It didn’t matter who you were. Du Ming wasn’t going to play nice anymore.

“He’s coming!” Tang Rou reminded Ye Xiu.

“Got it.” Ye Xiu said. He was still looking at his character’s equipment and skills.

With Ye Xiu’s skill, a quick look was enough for him to get a rough sketch of the Battle Mage’s stats. The map wasn’t large, either. By the time he finished looking, Du Ming’s Blade Master had arrived.

The running Blade Master initiated with a Triple Slash to close even faster with Ye Xiu’s Battle Mage.

Tang Rou had already encountered this initiation several times. It wasn’t hard to deal with, but she was curious as to what Ye Xiu would do.

Then she saw that Ye Xiu didn’t react at all.

When the first blade of the Triple Slash came down, Ye Xiu’s Battle Mage just stood there, not moving. But when the blade light slashed down, not a single bit of damage was inflicted.

Du Ming was surprised. He didn’t know if it was coincidence or whether the opponent had completely seen through his attack’s range. If his opponent really had seen through it……

He then saw that the Battle Mage had already stepped to the side, immediately signalling to Du Ming that it hadn’t been a coincidence. With that step, the Triple Slash’s second attack wouldn’t be able to reach him.

And when this step came out, his opponent lifted his spear and slashed up with a Sky Strike.

Du Ming had been prepared and hastily stopped his Triple Slash’s animation, putting up a Guard to block the Sky Strike. But when he moved his mouse to lift his sword, he discovered that the Sky Strike had come at a nasty angle, making it so that his Guard wouldn’t be able to block it.

“Pu!”

Sure enough, the Sky Strike had arrived before the Guard and Du Ming’s Blade Master was launched into the air.

All this had occurred in an instant. The audience members weren’t fully paying attention yet, but for those at the pro player seats, their eyes were all wide open.

A single step and a single Sky Strike had accurately launched Du Ming into the air, sending him up with an unblockable attack.

An expert…….. Many of them were already thinking of this.

But it was still too early to make the conclusion with just that. Under this surprise, the pros stowed away their banter and began seriously looking at the match.

Du Ming wasn’t without options in the air. He was very serious in his playing for this match. In the air, he quickly adjusted his position. A Falling Light Blade was used to force his character to come down.

But the instant he hit the ground, there was nothing but air in front of his eyes. The Battle Mage had disappeared. The audience could see very clearly that the instant his Falling Light Blade descended down, the Battle Mage had circled behind him. But the pros astonishingly figured out that his movements had also avoided the Blade Master’s camera, so Du Ming wasn’t able to see what had happened.

“Vanishing Step!!” many of them blurted out.

“Who is this guy?” Many of them were looking at one another. Two consecutive high-level movements were enough to verify this person’s status as an expert. Many of them weren’t paying attention to the projections anymore and switched to look at the screens.

It was true that the projection was beautiful, but the spectators had a fixed view. It pretty much meant that their point of view was fixed. The pros needed to see from several perspectives in order to understand the second challenger’s skill.

Du Ming wasn’t some noob, either. After using Falling Light Blade and not seeing anyone in front of him, he determined that the opponent was behind him. He immediately rolled forward and turned 180 degrees, sending out a Sword Draw at the same time.

These movements were executed extremely smoothly. The audience was even about to applaud, when they saw the Battle Mage rush forward diagonally. Facing the Sword Draw, it looked as if he would certainly be hit by it. But then they watched as the Sword Draw just passed through him. Taking advantage of the brief moment the Blade Master was still finishing his Sword Draw animation, he closed in and stabbed with a Dragon Tooth.

The audience was completely dumbstruck.

Speaking of this, Ye Xiu’s previous astonishing movements, Sky Strike and Vanishing Step, were all very minute. With a normal player’s skill level, it wasn’t easy for them to see how incredible those moves were. But this time’s Sword Draw was completely out in the open. This was because many of them knew the theory behind the move. The image of the sword aura hitting him was simply an afterimage. The instant the Sword Draw arced through him, he wouldn’t take any damage.

However, the timing for this was incredibly difficult. If he was too early, then he would take damage. If he was too late, then even though he wouldn’t be hit, he wouldn’t have made it in time to reach Du Ming while he was still in mid-animation.

And this difficult move had been done immaculately by the challenger. The Blade Master didn’t have any time to react to the Dragon Tooth. It wasn’t that Du Ming didn’t want to dodge, it was that he was still in the brief stun from the finishing animation and he had no way to move.

The pros weren’t the only ones to see the brilliance of his move. Except….. Should they still clap?

Their two hands which had originally been meant as applause for Du Ming’s Sword Draw were all suspended in mid-air now.

The challenger’s play had been brilliant, but he was still their home ground’s opponent, so they were somewhat hesitant to clap.

Though of course, there would still be a few who didn’t care and cheered at the brilliant play.

For example, Chen Guo…… She hadn’t been a Samsara fan from the start and she knew that the one playing was Ye Xiu, so why would she care? Of course she would support him! The moment Dragon Tooth shot out, Chen Guo cheered and applauded as if Du Ming had been killed.

After being hit by the Dragon Tooth, Du Ming’s Blade Master was stunned again. Ye Xiu followed up with a Sky Strike.

The Blade Master was once again launched into the air, but his Falling Light Blade was still on cooldown. He had no way of using the same method to get out and could only hastily adjust his camera to see what the opponent would do.

But when he tried, there was no one there……

“Vanishing Step……” Du Ming also realized at this moment.

He almost wanted to cry. He was completely aware that he had come across an extremely difficult opponent. What the heck was this with this challenge competition? The following challenger was unexpectedly strong and it turned out that he was even having trouble keeping up. Someone who knew how to use Vanishing Step to such a degree obviously wasn’t another abnormal new player. This time, he was up against a true expert!

Chapter 328 – Unable to Fight Back

Double Stab!

Falling Flower Palm!

Circle Swing!

Along with these skills flew various Chasers of different elements. They flew out, coiled around the spear, with dazzling colors.

As for Du Ming? He was completely helpless against these attacks. After being hit by these low-level skills, he was slammed into the ground by a Circle Swing and blasted by numerous Chasers, immediately dropping his healthy by a chunk.

Who is this guy!

A sliver of panic trembled across Du Ming’s heart.

Vanishing Step definitely wasn’t a normal technique. It required a vast amount of experience as a base. Someone who didn’t have a deep understanding of the game had no way of achieving it. Du Ming couldn’t even determine what level the challenger’s Vanishing Step had reached, but at the very least, he had already been caught by it twice.

If it hadn’t just been lucky and had been intentionally done, then this challenger’s Vanishing Step had reached a frightening level.

The previous opponent had been a new player who didn’t even know how to use high-level skills.

And now he was fighting against an experienced expert who even knew how to use Vanishing Step.

He definitely couldn’t be careless. Du Ming concentrated harder. Even though this was still a show in the All-Star event, because of what had happened previously, Du Ming couldn’t lose.

He hastily pressed a key and his Blade Master rolled backwards after touching the ground. He didn’t immediately rush forward to attack, but backed out instead and leaped backwards twice.

His leap backwards make it look like he was running away. Du Ming knew that it looked somewhat shameful and he could already hear a few boos from the crowd.

However, running away was better than losing.

Du Ming clearly understood that his challenger wasn’t simple. He definitely wasn’t the normal player like everyone else believed he was. Charging forward without feeling out the opponent’s strength had been a very reckless action.

He was nicknamed the “Berserk Blade Master”, but the “Berserk” pointed at his bold and unrestrained fighting, not recklessness. Du Ming knew that he was only a mid-tier character in the pro scene. It was quite possible that there was a pro player hiding in the audience.

When he fought with Tang Rou, Du Ming had employed pro-level mechanics. But against Ye Xiu, he felt a huge pressure. He didn’t have confidence in solely using mechanics to win and was now using tactics he knew of.

Temporarily retreating, escaping out of the opponent’s momentum and setting up a more favorable situation was his best option right now.

After Du Ming made these movements, he earned a bit of disdain from the audience. Many of the players in the audience had limited skill. For high-level techniques like Vanishing Step, not just them, but even the pro players had difficulty recognizing it.

Amidst these boos, the pro players’ faces grew more and more serious. They were the same as Du Ming and felt that this challenger wasn’t ordinary.

Some of them were even beginning to look around to see if one of them had snuck off to have some fun. But when they searched, they found that all of the pros were sitting at their respective seats. Besides Du Ming, no one else was missing.

What would happen next?

Everyone looked forward to it. Du Ming chose to retreat, but his opponent, the second challenger, chose to charge forward.

His spear shook and he sent out another Dragon Tooth.

This challenger clearly wasn’t a new person, but he acted the same as that girl and only used low-level skills. Some of the Battle Mage pros could tell that the Battle Mage hadn’t distributed the skill points normally. Perhaps because that girl didn’t know how to use high-level skills, she had maxed out the low-level skills she knew well and then because she still had points left, she put them into other skills randomly.

When distributing skill points, the player didn’t necessarily only seek for more damage.

For example, if we take the low-level skill, Sky Strike, the higher the level, the greater the knock-up effect. For this skill, almost no one put points into it for more damage, but rather for the crowd control effect.

And when things got to the pro level, these minute differences mattered more. Every person had a different play style, so the knock up amount they required was different. Some players might feel like a Level 7 Sky Strike had a good enough knock-up, but some might feel like a Level 9 Sky Strike wasn’t enough.

But this Battle Mage, whether it was attacks or Chasers, every low-level skill was maxed out.

Du Ming couldn’t just ignore these maxed out low-level skills, either. He didn’t dare to meet force with force and so he chose to dodge.

As a result, a somewhat historic scene resulted: the “Berserk Blade Master” Du Ming didn’t take the initiative to attack, but dodged around instead, waiting for an opportunity.

As a result, this scenario lasted for several minutes. Du Ming had unexpectedly been unable to find an opportunity to counter and in the end, he was suppressed by his opponent’s attacks.

At this moment, if the audience still couldn’t see that this challenger wasn’t ordinary, then that would mean that they didn’t understand Glory.

Even if it was just a show and even if Du Ming was intentionally letting him win, it shouldn’t go so far as this, where he was only running around like a little mouse. That was a bit too embarrassing!

“Why isn’t Du Ming fighting back?” The Samsara players who were on good terms with Du Ming were having trouble watching and were feeling very worried for him.

“It’s good to be cautious.” one player said.

“He can’t fight back.” Zhou Zekai, who was sitting on the very edge of their section, suddenly spoke.

“What?” Everyone looked towards Zhou Zekai.

Zhou Zekai lifted his head a bit and looked intently at the screens, looking at the scene through several angles. He then said after a short pause: “There aren’t any opportunities.”

“No opportunities?” The pros who weren’t able to see this were startled.

“Are you saying that it isn’t that Du Ming doesn’t want to strike back, but he isn’t able to?” one player said in astonishment and then immediately looked at the match more carefully. A bead of sweat rolled down his face for Du Ming. No opportunities…… This meant that, this time, Du Ming was being completely suppressed.

He only had a bead of sweat rolling down, but what about Du Ming? Du Ming’s hands, head, and even his back was soaked with cold sweat.

At first, he had been dodging and observing, hoping to figure out his opponent’s pathing and an opening.

But after a few minutes, he discovered that he had no choice but to dodge. Every time the opponent attacked, besides dodging, he couldn’t think of any other method to react.

The opponent’s attacks were relentless. A continuous string of low-level skills, along with complex normal attacks mixed in, continued to batter him. From time to time, Chasers would even fly at him.

Du Ming tried his hardest to search for an opening, but there just weren’t any.

Perhaps his ability just wasn’t good enough. In short, in his current situation, dodging like this was already his best option.

But he wasn’t able to dodge everything completely. He would always be hit by a few attacks from time to time. The blood that blossomed out from the hits splattered along his escape route and looked quite horrifying to see.

He couldn’t keep going like this. He had to try fighting!

Du Ming immediately concluded this. He decided he would try a few methods that he wasn’t very good at yet.

As soon as he made the decision, Du Ming immediately made his move. He executed a Lunge and the tip of his blade emitted two cold streaks of light.

“My god, that idiot! How would that work!” At the pro player seats, Huang Shaotian watched as Du Ming tried to initiate with a Lunge and immediately sighed.

The Battle Mage then used a Dragon Tooth, a low-level skill like the Lunge.

“The other side’s skill level is higher! Even if they were the same, Dragon Tooth has more priority over Lunge! Using Lunge at this moment is just looking to die!” Huang Shaotian chattered and the results turned out just like he said. The two streaks of cold light from Du Ming’s Blade Master immediately disappeared and the Battle Mage’s spear thrust through his head.

The spear was pulled away, along with a stream of blood.

The Battle Mage didn’t waste the brief stun and chained a few attacks before ending with a Sky Strike. Du Ming’s Blade Master was launched up. Unable to find where his opponent’s attacks were coming from, he was comboed some more, except this time, the opponent switched strategies and ended with a Falling Flower Palm.

Du Ming’s Blade Master was blown flying. He immediately steadied his camera, but then his body suddenly shook. His body crashed into the wall and then bounced off of it.

Du Ming started. He saw the Battle Mage in front of him raise his spear with both hands. The tip of his spear seemed to grow brighter and brighter.

Not good! Du Ming cried out in his heart.

Battle Mage Level 65 Skill: Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Chapter 329 – Dragon Raising Its Head

The Battle Mage finally unleashed a Level 40 and above skill.

In addition, it was a Level 65 skill: Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

In terms of physical damage, this skill was undoubtedly the Battle Mage’s strongest skill. The Level 70 skill Rising Dragon Soars the Sky was an AoE magic spell that did both physical and magic damage. Their combined damage did more than Dragon Breaks the Ranks, but in terms of physical damage, the two couldn’t be compared.

Once Du Ming saw the cold glint of the Battle Mage’s spear, he wanted to dodge. However, after being hit into the wall, his body entered into a mini stunned state and was unable to move.

Du Ming panicked and rapidly mashed his keyboard, hoping to immediately move the instant that the stun wore off.

In the end, the cold glint from the spear suddenly grew brighter and instantly transformed into a beam of light, fiercely striking the stunned Blade Master.

Ye Xiu’s attack struck the lower half of Du Ming’s Blade Master. The powerful force sent the Blade Master hurtling into the air.

Just how fast Du Ming’s character was spinning could be seen from the screen which was showing Du Ming’s first person perspective.

The screen spun so fast that it was impossible to distinguish anything clearly. At this moment, the player could only rely on his game sense, experience and knowledge.

Du Ming subconsciously acted and sent out two cold slashes as he spun, although, to the audience, it only looked like he was juggling.

Right now, everyone’s attention was focused on the Battle Mage.

The Battle Mage held onto his long spear. His right hand pulled the end of it behind him, while his left hand supported the spear’s front, which was slanted into the air.

Another skill appeared.

Battle Mage Level 60 skill: Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

The Battle Mage hadn’t used any high-level skills for quite a long time. But as soon as he had begun, he unexpectedly used them one after the other. However, Du Ming’s Blade Master was hit and was tumbling into the air rapidly by Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Would he be able to hit him?

He would!

Reality provided him the best answer.

When the Blade Master hit his peak, during the instant where he was about to fall, the Battle Mage’s spear soared. Like a bolt of lightning, the spear pierced through the falling Blade Master.

Furious Dragons Strikes the Heart!

But only a light passed through.

The instant the spear pierced the Blade Master, he flew up once again, but only a few specks of blood fell.

Would the offense stop here?

Not yet!

The Battle Mage chased after the Blade Master’s body. His spear turned into a dragon. Its roar lifted up the earth and the dust as the dragon’s head shot towards the Blade Master.

Du Ming didn’t give up. He had predicted this Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. The instant the skill was unleashed, he ferociously let loose a Falling Light Blade, causing his Blade Master to crash down quickly.

Would it hit? Everyone’s heart leapt into their throats. During this moment, they didn’t know who to side with. They had only hoped that the answer would come soon.

It wouldn’t!

The Falling Light Blade altered the Blade Master’s flight path. With the sudden turn, the dragon missed.

Those who had watched the Rookie Challenge yesterday suddenly felt that this scene looked somewhat familiar.

The Sun Xiang vs Han Wenqing match.

Wasn’t the deciding move in that match Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, which was dodged by Han Wenqing through a precise Eagle Stamp, forcing his character to move in the air, allowing him to dodge it?

And right now, a mid-tier pro player and unknown challenger unexpectedly repeated the same stunning scene that had previously occurred between two Gods.

In that match, the move had been the turning point. Han Wenqing, who had dodged the Rising Dragon, struck down Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf immediately after.

And now? It wasn’t the time for it to be the deciding move, but Du Ming, who had been suppressed the entire time, was finally able to find an opening.

For a powerful skill like Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, the ending animation would certainly be very slow. A Triple Slash after landing could let him close in on his opponent before the animation was finished.

The instant that Rising Dragon Soars the Sky flew past him, Du Ming had quickly made the decision. The audience who had watched Du Ming dodge the dragon’s head also thought this way, as well.

However, the dragon head that had already flown past him suddenly turned as if its neck had turned, and hit the Blade Master’s body, gobbling up Du Ming’s Blade Master.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky hit!!

The Blade Master wasn’t dead yet, but Du Ming was completely at a loss. He had no idea what had happened.

The spectators were all at a loss as well. They had seen it, but they thought that they had just seen it wrong.

And at the pro player seats, shock flashed across their eyes.

“Dragon Raising Its Head??? Who’s up on stage??” Every pro player could hear Team Tyranny captain Han Wenqing’s voice. Even some of the spectators who weren’t that far from the pro player area could hear him.

“Dragon Raising Its Head? That’s Dragon Raising Its Head??” The discussion quickly spread.

Let alone the audience, even for the pros, the majority of them had only seen this legendary Battle Mage technique from videos. And according to what they knew, only one person had the ability to pull off the technique.

Battle God One Autumn Leaf’s former owner: Ye Qiu!

The top tier God, who had recently left the stage for an unknown reason, suddenly showed off his sole special in the All-Star Weekend.

“Is that really Dragon Raising Its Head? Did I see that correctly? Why aren’t they showing the replay? Why aren’t they showing the replay?” At Team Blue Rain’s side, Huang Shaotian was chattering.

“So it’s like that…….” At Team Samsara’s side, Zhou Zekai simply said.

As for Team Tiny Herb’s side, Wang Jiexi appeared to be the most calm. He had noticed Tang Rou long before this. When an even stronger expert appeared right after, Wang Jiexi had already reached his conclusion.

All of the teams’ pro players were discussing in astonishment. While some of the younger generation weren’t able to understand everyone else’s astonishment, their seniors immediately informed them about the shocking scene.

Afterwards, many of them looked towards Team Excellent Era’s side.

Excellent Era’s players were even more complicated.

Some were astonished. Some were hesitant. Some were puzzled. Some felt uneasy. The players were feeling all sorts of emotions.

Vice captain Liu Hao’s gloominess seemed to drip off of him. But after seeing that many people were looking at them, he changed his expression.

As for their ace player, Sun Xiang, his eyes were filled with shock, as well as unhappiness. He couldn’t help but think back to what Han Wenqing had said to him yesterday: “If that was Ye Xiu, he would have definitely hit that Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.”

And now, a similar situation appeared and, sure enough, Rising Dragon connected.

He felt as if he had been slapped in the face.

Dragon Raising Its Head……

Sun Xiang had obviously heard of it. He also knew the theory behind this micro. He had even researched it, but he still hadn’t been able to learn it.

Though he did know that in the past two years, Ye Qiu hadn’t used Dragon Raising Its Head.

This technique was undoubtedly extremely difficult. Knowledge, experience, and hand speed. The player couldn’t be lacking in any of these aspects.

Sun Xiang had thought that Ye Qiu hadn’t used it because his skill had gone down, so he wasn’t able to use it anymore. And since he was still on the rise, there would be a day where he’d be able to use it, which was why he hadn’t been worried.

But today…….

“No wonder that Han Wenqing said that if it was Ye Qiu, the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky wouldn’t have missed.”

Sun Xiang heard a few discuss this. After seeing some of them look at him, Sun Xiang felt that there was a hint of contempt in their gazes.

It was as if they were all saying: “Sure enough, he’s not even close to good enough!”

“Dragon Raising Its Head……”

Sun Xiang ground his teeth and clenched his fists tightly as he muttered the words.

The pros were so astonished that they had practically forgotten to continue watching the match.

The match wasn’t over.

After three consecutive high-level skills, Du Ming’s Blade Master didn’t have much health left, but he wasn’t dead yet.

The reason for this was naturally because of Tang Rou’s random skill point distribution. Because she had maxed all of the low-level skills, there weren’t many skill points left for the high-level skills, so only Battle Spirit had been raised to the max. The rest of the points were just distributed randomly. She had learned the three skills, but their levels weren’t high enough, so even though their damage couldn’t be ignored, they didn’t do nearly as much as they should have.

As a result, after Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, Ye Xiu’s Battle Mage once again rushed forward.

At this moment, Du Ming had already lost all will to fight.

He had completely no idea how that Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had hit him. He even wanted to rush out of his seat and look at the replay.

Without any fighting spirit and a loss in confidence, Du Ming’s movements were extremely stiff. He couldn’t make any decisions and his actions lost all purpose.

One hit, two hits, three hits…….

Low level skills continuously battered at him.

Du Ming was still in his own little world. His mood had fallen extremely low. His Blade Master quickly fell.

And only then did the pros realize that the match was officially over.

As Du Ming’s Blade Master fell, the shock extended to the entire stadium.

Chapter 330 – Quiet Withdrawal

Compared to the pros, the audience members were much quieter. The absolute majority of the audience were supporters of Du Ming. The match had been brilliant and they would clap, but it would only be a sign of courtesy and respect for the winner. No matter what, Du Ming losing wasn’t something they could be happy about.

However, this time, even though Du Ming lost, there weren’t any boos. This was because those who understood Glory could see that Du Ming wasn’t against some random new player, but he was against a true expert. The more experienced players felt the same as the pros and recognized the legendary “Dragon Raising Its Head”.

It was too incredible to believe, but it happened right in front of them.

Who was this challenger?

Everyone wanted to know the answer.

Chen Guo, who had initially been shouting and jumping around excitedly, suddenly froze the instant “Dragon Raising Its Head” came out. But she still kept her posture straight until Du Ming’s Blade Master fell.

Dragon Raising Its Head!

Chen Guo was also an experienced Glory player and, as a fan of Excellent Era for so many years, how could she not recognize Ye Qiu’s sole specialty?

Her thoughts returned to that night in the winter.

“Let me tell you a secret. I’m actually Ye Qiu……”

Chen Guo still remembered these words, but at that time, she hadn’t believed him. This was because she had clearly seen Ye Xiu’s ID card as proof. Someone could be called by different names, but their ID card couldn’t be wrong, right?

The ID card had dispelled all of Chen Guo’s doubts towards Ye Xiu. From then on, she had considered Ye Xiu as a pro who hadn’t been able to make it that far and eventually had no choice but to find a job at her Internet Cafe.

Even though Ye Xiu displayed extraordinary skill, Chen Guo wasn’t too surprised since he had still been a pro once. In the pro scene, there were differences in skill. However, no matter how bad they were within the pro circle, they would still be far superior when compared to a normal player in terms of skills, so being incredibly skilled wasn’t anything strange! That was what Chen Guo had believed.

But now, Dragon Raising Its Head appeared! Up until now, not a single person had been able to successfully recreate it, but Ye Xiu had…….

“Could he really be Ye Qiu?” Chen Guo’s mind was a mess.

Chen Guo wasn’t the only one whose mind was a mess. When Du Ming’s Blade Master fell, the host’s mind went into a mess as well. His head replayed the previous scene, where the two players turned back and continued to fight nonstop……..

“Ah……. How unexpected. It seems like Du Ming’s very nice today! This time, he unexpectedly let the challenger win again. Ha ha. Beating a pro must feel good, right, challenger?” The host hastily announced the end of the match and began giving excuses for Du Ming. His words indicated that Du Ming had let the challenger win on purpose.

The host wasn’t unfamiliar with Glory, but his words completely exposed the fact that he hadn’t watched the match at all.

In that match, Du Ming hadn’t been nice at all. He had been suppressed from the very beginning to the very end. There wasn’t any niceness in that.

As soon as the host finished speaking, boos began to come out. These boos were directed at him. Putting the match in that kind of light was way too shameless.

After hearing the audience’s reaction, the host felt that he had made a mistake, but his eyes were stuck on the electronic screens, afraid that Du Ming would refuse to give up and would instead continue fighting.

However, a new match didn’t appear. The screens had already switched to the replay for “Dragon Raising Its Head”. The commentators were already excitedly shouting: “Let us see the replay. The replay.”

“Everyone look, the Falling Light Blade should have allowed him to dodge it, but…… the head turned and then the chomp! That is without a doubt Dragon Raising Its Head! That is definitely it! Just who is this second challenger? Because of a few technical difficulties, we weren’t able to see him come up onto the stage, but now that the match is over, will we be able to find out who this mysterious challenger is? Many of us have already thought of the same name: Ye Qiu!

After seeing the replay, the commentator’s words had shocked the host.

“That guy was God Ye Qiu?” The host recalled the person’s appearance, but it was somewhat fuzzy. At that time, he had been extremely anxious and hadn’t paid attention to the rescuer’s appearance.

“What are you waiting for! Hurry up and introduce the challenger to everyone.” The commentators said to the host through his earpiece. The host regained his composure and glanced at the big screen. The two characters had already exited the game and the event looked like it had returned to its normal state.

As the host walked to the center of the stage, he asked the players from both booths to come down.

Du Ming came down. Right now, he no longer had that depressed face from when he lost to Tang Rou. His face was filled with complete surprise.

And on the other side, Tang Rou had come down as well. She slowly walked over with a smile.

But what about next to her? There was no one there!

The second challenger, who had called himself a substitute, was nowhere to be seen.

“And him?” The host unexpectedly didn’t pay any heed to Du Ming and instead asked Tang Rou first.

“Which him?” Tang Rou asked.

“Your friend. The one who just fought.” the host said.

“Oh, he went to the restroom.”

“The restroom…….” The host almost fainted. The backstage broadcasting team had also noticed the situation and called out to him: “That guy? Where is he?”

“He went to the restroom…….” The host said quietly and heard sounds like the other side falling over from his earpiece.

The host, the backstage employees, the audience members, and even the pros, they had all wanted to see the challenger.

“Turn on the lights!” the backstage team directed. The stadium immediately lit up. Everyone looked around wildly, but aside from those three on stage, there was no sign of anyone else.

“Uh, the challenger’s stomach wasn’t feeling too good, so he went to the restroom……” the host said evasively.

“I don’t suggest waiting for him to come back…….” Tang Rou said to the host.

The host felt gloomy. Going to the restroom had clearly been an excuse. Had he slipped away? That meant…… that guy really might have been God Ye Qiu, the Ye Qiu who never exposed himself to the public.

The host’s mind accidentally wandered off, but it was quickly called back by the backstage broadcaster’s shouts.

At the pro player seats, the pros hadn’t been able to see the challenger’s face, so they could only guess.

“It’s him. It’s definitely him!” Huang Shaotian said to Yu Wenzhou, “Restroom? Do you believe that? He definitely slipped away because he didn’t want to be exposed!”

“Yeah.” Yu Wenzhou nodded his head: “He’s very experienced with playing cat and mouse. They probably won’t be able to find him.”

“He he, Dragon Raising Its Head……” Huang Shaotian muttered and then looked at Sun Xiang’s ugly expression: “It was as if he had slapped his face. Could he have been working together with Han Wenqing?”

“Using Dragon Raising Its Head at that moment is very normal.” Yu Wenzhou plainly said.

Team Tyrannical Ambition, Team Tiny Herb, etc. There were many pros who were familiar with Ye Qiu. At this moment, they were all raising their heads and looking at that replay.

“Dragon Raising Its Head……”

Han Wenqing had a thought.

It was a move that hadn’t been used in two years. To suddenly use it now in front of millions of people, was it really just a coincidence that he chose to use it?

Dragon Raising Its Head…… Could he be saying that he wouldn’t lower his head? Was it a declaration of his return?

The majority of the pros were now even more certain that the challenger was Ye Qiu after seeing his stealthy escape. They continued to discuss, but in the end, there really wasn’t too much they could talk about. It was just that they hadn’t been prepared, which was why they had been so shocked. Ye Qiu had already withdrawn quietly. It was the same as every match he had ever been in. He would never appear in front of the public. The only thing that he left behind was his incredible achievements.

“How unfortunate for Du Ming……”

After seeing Du Ming return to his seat, it looked as if he had seen a ghost. Many empathized with him.

In the end, they were only spectators. No one could be more shocked and frightened than Du Ming was. He had originally thought that he would be able to have a nice and relaxing time playing against some normal players, but in the end, he had been the one to be utterly crushed. When he got back to the team, the others went up to talk to him, but he had to take a while to answer, as if he were Zhou Zekai.

Ye Qiu.

Every person in the stadium was discussing this name. The host continued on with the scheduled event and invited the second pro to come up. But the audience’s claps were few and sparse. Their minds clearly weren’t ready to move on, yet.

Tang Rou had already returned to her seat. The audience’s attention towards her was even greater than for the pro player who had just gone up.

Chen Guo was finally no longer standing up like a statue. She had changed to a statue that was sitting down. When she saw that Tang Rou had returned, she looked at her blankly and asked: “And him?”

“He left early.” Tang Rou said, while looking around. The surrounding audience members were all looking towards her. One of the audience members who were sitting next to Tang Rou simply went up and asked: “Was that person God Ye Qiu?”

The surrounding audience members were waiting for Tang Rou’s reply.

“Let’s go!” Chen Guo suddenly stood up and pulled Tang Rou away.

The audience members couldn’t stop them from leaving and could only watch as the two left without answering their question.

On stage, the host was getting the next lucky challenger to come up onto the stage, but who could care about that right now?

Chapter 331 – As If Nothing Happened

The All-Star event continued. Ye Xiu was already standing outside the stadium, all alone.

This sort of situation was something that he was quite familiar with. In his many years as a pro, he had always left the stage early. He had never participated in any of the press conferences before or after the matches.

As Glory grew, year by year, he received more and more attention and the media’s pursuit and blockade grew fiercer and fiercer. Being able to last so long without being exposed could be seen as no easier than creating an era.

He looked back at the great, brightly lit stadium. Compared to it, he looked so measly.

“Tsk, tsk.” Ye Xiu clicked his tongue. He had turned his head and prepared to head back to the hotel, when suddenly, he saw a girl sitting on a railing near the street in front of him. She carried a pair of binoculars around her neck and was currently waving at him.

“Amazing. You’re actually even faster than me.” Ye Xiu greeted back and went to meet her.

“He he.” Su Mucheng laughed and jumped down off of the railing. She was once again wrapped tightly in thick clothing, a cap, and a mouth mask. If Ye Xiu hadn’t been familiar with her, he wouldn’t have been able to recognize her.

“The match is over. You wanna grab some ice cream?” Su Mucheng said.

Ye Xiu was surprised and asked: “That store is still open?”

“It still is!” Su Mucheng lifted her binoculars and looked towards the other side of the street, “See.” She then handed the binoculars over to Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu looked and, sure enough, in a small street behind Samsara’s stadium was a small ice cream shop that still had its lights on.

“It’s winter, though.” Ye Xiu said.

“Winter’s the best time to eat ice cream. It won’t melt as quickly, so you can eat it nice and slow.” Su Mucheng said.

“Alright, let’s go!” Ye Xiu replied.

Su Mucheng climbed over the railing.

“Be more civilized……” Ye Xiu muttered, but also crossed over slowly the same way.

After crossing the street, they entered a small street. The small ice cream shop was still the same as ever. There were four little tables for two people to sit. The assortment of flavors was displayed on the refrigerator and they each had a small, handwritten price tag attached to them. The owner of the store was a forty or so year old uncle. When he saw that there were customers, he neither greeted them warmly, nor ignored them coldly. He simply stood in front of the refrigerator and quietly waited for their order.

“I’ll have this one, this one, this one, and this one. Can I have a quarter of each of them?” Su Mucheng selected skillfully.

“Sure.” The owner grabbed a large cup and evenly distributed each of the four flavors. He stuck a small spoon into the cup, handed it over to Su Mucheng and then turned his gaze over to Ye Xiu.

“Can I smoke here?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yes.” The owner nodded his head and, seeing that Ye Xiu wasn’t going to order anything, he then ignored him.

At a little table inside, Su Mucheng fiddled with her ice cream and quickly ate it. Ye Xiu smoked his cigarette and quietly sat in front of her.

The weather was very cold and so was the ice cream. But this sort of familiar feeling made them feel especially warm.

Outside of Samsara’s stadium, Chen Guo and Tang Rou finally ran out.

Chen Guo also had her binoculars ready. She immediately took them out in order to scout around, but didn’t find any signs of Ye Xiu.

“How quick!” Chen Guo said. She and Tang Rou had exited the stadium fairly quickly.

“He said he’d head back first.” Tang Rou said.

“Go. Let’s go back!” Chen Guo stopped a cab and swiftly returned back to the hotel. They didn’t even enter their rooms. They instead, directly knocked on Ye Xiu’s door, but there was no response.

“He’s still not back?” Chen Guo asked, “Where’d he go?”

“Maybe he went out on a stroll. Let’s wait!” Tang Rou opened their door and went in.

“Is he really Ye Qiu?” Chen Guo followed behind Tang Rou.

“Yeah…… “ Tang Rou replied helplessly. Chen Guo had asked this question for the seventh time.

“This guy…….” Chen Guo mumbled to herself as she turned on the TV. She switched to the eSports channel. The All-Star event was still going on and, just like in the past, the pros would accept the challenges from the audience. This time though, nothing unexpected occurred. The pros easily dispatched the audience members, but the atmosphere never grew as excited as it was before. With such a high climax, aside from the audience members who were chosen to go up, no one could feel as excited as they did before.

Chen Guo stared blankly. Her mind clearly wasn’t on the TV. Whenever she heard a small movement from outside her room, she would rush out like an arrow, but it would not be Ye Xiu.

“Where’d he go?” Chen Guo mumbled. She would look outside the window with her binoculars for a while and then run outside her room to knock on the room next door to see if Ye Xiu had come back. After doing this over and over for at least an hour, the second day of the All-Stars Weekend ended, but Ye Xiu still wasn’t back.

“He doesn’t even have a phone.” Chen Guo grumbled. At this moment, the event broadcast had ended and the press conference for the second day soon began. The challenge competition’s unforeseen event was clearly today’s main focus. As one of the main players in it, Du Ming was naturally selected to participate in the press conference and he received God-level treatment.

Du Ming had calmed down quite a lot. If he couldn’t let go of a loss, how would he survive in the pro scene? Even though losing to a normal player was quite embarrassing, he had still won four matches in a row afterwards to prove himself. In addition, the girl’s skill had received a lot of acknowledgement after the match.

As for that even more abnormal second challenger, even though no one saw his true face, pretty much everyone was certain that he was Ye Qiu.

So in reality, there wasn’t much that could be given from Du Ming. It obviously wouldn’t be good for him to appear so unsportsmanlike, so he praised Tang Rou’s skill and then showed his respect towards the God.

“What are your thoughts on God Ye Qiu’s sudden appearance in the All-Star event?” This was a question that practically every reporter asked to all of the pros being interviewed. They had even gone and asked some of the audience members.

The replies from the audience members were obviously very brazen. As for the pros, they answered back cautiously and half-heartedly.

For this issue on Ye Qiu, the reporters obviously wouldn’t let go of the chance they had to interrogate Team Excellent Era’s players. In the end, Team Excellent Era’s players replied very plainly, saying that they hoped he was doing well. There wasn’t any substance to their replies. And since Su Mucheng, who was very close to Ye Qiu, was nowhere to be seen, no one could interview her.

The final highlight shined onto the interview with Han Wenqing. The domineering team captain stared at the camera and bluntly said: “I’ll be waiting for your return.”

This phrase became the reporters’ biggest catch and it became the headlines. The media had guessed that this meant Ye Qiu was planning on coming back. The fact that Ye Qiu had used Dragon Raises Its Head, a move that no one else could replicate and a move that he hadn’t used in two years… It was his way of telling everyone that he wasn’t done yet.

Seeing these assumptions from the media, Chen Guo felt a sort of pleased and superior feeling. While everyone was concerned about how he would do it, Chen Guo jumped up with her fists clenched: “Once that guy comes back, I’ll definitely ask him.”

As she said this, she once again walked over to the window and then to outside of the room. Seeing that it was getting late and Ye Xiu still wasn’t back, Chen Guo was finally beginning to worry: “Don’t tell me…… that after his revealing his identity, he won’t be coming back?”

Tang Rou was also startled: “No way, right?”

“He……. still hasn’t received his first month’s salary.” Chen Guo suddenly said. Her tone was full of sadness. She suddenly discovered that, even though she still wasn’t able to equate Ye Xiu with Ye Qiu, whether it was that lazy and irritating guy or that God that she respected greatly, him leaving so quietly left a bad taste in her mouth.

Chen Guo suddenly quieted down and sat on her bed silently.

“He’ll come back.” Tang Rou walked over to comfort her.

Just as she said this, they heard a movement from outside their door. It was just that with Chen Guo’s mood, she only let out a sigh, but didn’t move.

Except this time, the movements got closer and closer and then stopped outside of their door.

“Is he back?” Chen Guo was still lost in thought. This time, Tang Rou said this and checked. When she opened the door, sure enough, Ye Xiu was fiddling with his door.

“You’re still not asleep?” Ye Xiu turned his head and greeted. Chen Guo had already rushed out from the room like the wind. In the end, Ye Xiu simply opened his door, turned his head, said a “Try to sleep early.” and then went into his room.

Chen Guo had so many things she wanted to say, but the guy just slipped away.

“What’s going on?” Chen Guo’s mind wasn’t able to process what had just happened.

“It’s as if…… nothing ever happened……” Tang Rou forced a smile. She reckoned that Chen Guo was about to set off.

Sure enough, after a short pause, Chen Guo immediately rushed over and madly hammered at his door. Ye Xiu opened the door. His face was filled with puzzlement as if he didn’t know what was going on. Tang Rou was already speechless.

“What’s wrong?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Explain yourself!” Chen Guo said furiously. She had been thinking about how she would approach him. In her head, Ye Xiu and Ye Qiu were two completely different beings. Now that the two were one, should she talk to him like the poor Internet Cafe employee she knew or the idol she had respected for so many years?

Chapter 332 – Embarrassing Past

Chen Guo had initially been unsure of what tone to use when talking to Ye Xiu. But after being infuriated by Ye Xiu’s attitude as if nothing had happened, she took out her usual furious state for Ye Xiu.

“Okay.” Ye Xiu calmly said and nodded his head: “What do you want me to explain?”

“You……” Chen Guo looked like she could pounce and attack him at any moment. Tang Rou hastily stepped in to be the mediator. She pushed the two into the room, while saying: “How about you two take a seat first before talking!”

“Pick anywhere you’d like.” Ye Xiu brought them into his room and took the role as the room’s owner.

“What exactly is up with you?” After Chen Guo sat down, her tone became much calmer, but it could easily be heard from her voice’s ups and downs that she was trying to keep her emotions under control.

“I’m Ye Qiu. Didn’t I already tell you that a long time ago?” Ye Xiu finally spoke.

“That counts?!” Chen Guo turned angry.

“Then how am I supposed to make it count?” Ye Xiu countered back.

Chen Guo fell silent. True! How was he supposed to say it so she’d believe him? Chen Guo couldn’t refrain from thinking about it. But after thinking for a while, she suddenly remembered: why had she been so certain that Ye Xiu wasn’t Ye Qiu? Wasn’t it because she had seen his ID card?

“If you’re Ye Qiu, then what’s up with Ye Xiu?” Chen Guo immediately questioned.

“Ye Xiu is me as well!”

“Why do you have two names?”

“Now that’s a much more complicated question.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo sat upright, ready to listen to why he had these two names. In the end, her upright posture was for nothing as Ye Xiu was done talking. He then moved a bit as if to tell Chen Guo that he was waiting for Chen Guo’s next question.

Chen Guo’s expression began to gradually grow stiffer. Tang Rou silently turned her head to look out the window. The reason for having two names was something that anyone would be curious about, but Ye Xiu had clearly expressed that answering the question wasn’t convenient. He wasn’t going to change his mind.

From the window’s reflection, Tang Rou could see Chen Guo grip her fist and say: “Why do you have two names?” Chen Guo didn’t think that Ye Xiu wouldn’t be able to recognize that this was the question that needed the most explaining.

“I can’t tell you that.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“Because…… it’s a secret.” Ye Xiu said helplessly.

A reply without any substance, which hid everything of importance. No matter how badly Chen Guo wanted to know, she couldn’t force him to speak. She breathed in deeply and calmed herself down. She then asked: “Then which one is your real name?”

“Guess?” Ye Xiu asked back.

Deep breaths! Deep breaths!

Chen Guo took several deep breaths and then slowly stood up. She paced back and forth and then stopped at the window’s side and actually guessed.

“I’ve seen your ID card. Even though I personally can’t tell if it’s real or not, when I registered your name for the hotel, your ID wasn’t a problem, so it looks like it’s real.” Chen Guo said.

“But you’ve also been in the Pro Alliance. From what I know, the players in the Pro Alliance have to use their ID cards as well. I don’t know if the Alliance allows you to change your registered name; since most people don’t care, I’m not sure about that.”

“You’ve played in the Pro Alliance for seven years and you’ve never revealed your identity to the public. If I said you simply did it because you liked to be secretive, it wouldn’t make sense because you told me you were Ye Qiu when we just met. You definitely have other reasons for not wanting to show yourself to the public, so your name of Ye Qiu is probably fake and is also a cover up for your real identity. That means that Ye Xiu is your true name, right?”

Chen Guo explained her guess and was quite logical. After saying this, she looked at Ye Xiu, waiting for his response.

Ye Xiu was silent for awhile, before nodding his head: “It seems like it was pretty easy to guess, huh.”

“What do you mean, easy? Are you looking down on my ability to analyze things?” Chen Guo said angrily.

“It was a beautiful analysis.” Ye Xiu applauded.

“So you’re saying I’m correct?” Chen Guo said.

“Is it okay if I don’t say it?” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re really intent on not letting me sleep!” Chen Guo grinded her teeth.

“Okay, I concede. You’re correct. Ye Xiu. I’m Ye Xiu.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Why do you need to use a fake name? Why don’t you want to reveal your identity? What are you hiding for?” Chen Guo was beginning to ask more deeply.

Ye Xiu stood up. He also walked over to the window and looked outside. Tang Rou looked at his face and discovered an unexpected expression of hesitation. This sort of wavering look was something she had never seen on Ye Xiu’s face before.

Chen Guo silently went back to her seat. She had asked what she wanted. If Ye Xiu didn’t answer, then she wouldn’t force him, so she simply sat down, silent.

“Uh……” Ye Xiu turned around. His face now held a self-ridiculing smile: “The reason is actually very embarrassing.”

“Oh?” The two girls’ ears perked up. Was he actually going to say it?

“It’s because I ran away from home.” Ye Xiu said.

“You….. ran away from home?” Chen Guo repeated stupidly. Tang Rou gave Ye Xiu a weird look, which quickly disappeared.

“Why did you run away?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu didn’t answer. His face said “You know why.”

Chen Guo immediately understood and, along with a face full of astonishment, she said: “It’s not because you wanted to play games, is it?”

Ye Xiu smiled bitterly.

Chen Guo and Tang Rou looked at each other. Even for Chen Guo, who loved Glory, she couldn’t understand his actions. Running away from home to play games and becoming so addicted… Was there something wrong with his mind?

The room immediately fell silent. Amidst the cloud of awkwardness, no one knew what to say. Ye Xiu also returned to his seat. His expression continued to stay calm. But when Chen Guo looked at him again, apart from the skilled God and the infuriating smoking demon, he had another face: an extremely naive child.

“You…….. When did you run away?” Chen Guo was the one to break the silence.

“Ten years ago!” Ye Xiu said.

“When Glory came out?” Chen Guo asked.

“Around then.”

“You ran away just to play Glory?”

“Not exactly. I played other games before that, as well.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo didn’t dig deeper because there wasn’t much of a point. In the end, in order to put in every effort he could into playing games, he ran away from home. Then, after Glory came out, he threw himself into Glory, entered the pro scene, and then became a skilled God-level player.

The result was very spectacular. On the other hand, Chen Guo was hoping that he had some sort of tragedy occur to him that forced him to run away. If that had happened, then it would have been a lot more moving to listen to.

Though unfortunately, Ye Xiu had already said that he had run away to play games and he also admitted that it was very embarrassing.

Ye Xiu understood this very well. He had been very lucky to be talented at the game and also succeed upon the release of Glory. If not, then running away from home might have ended in a tragedy.

“Then what about now? You’ve never gone back home to visit?” Chen Guo asked.

“I have.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“We parted on bad terms.” Ye Xiu said.

“How?”

“Because in their eyes, playing games for a living will never be seen as an honest profession.” Ye Xiu calmly said.

Chen Guo was silent. As a gaming fan, she clearly understood this sort of view. Even though Glory’s eSports scene was thriving and the pros had a luxurious income and a tremendous popularity, it required that the players give up on school. In addition, a pro’s career was very short. There also wasn’t a good system to guarantee their life’s well-being after their retirement. These sort of problems still existed.

The chance to become a pro was also very low. Of all of the players playing Glory, only two hundred of them were able to make it into the pro scene.

No family would encourage their child to walk this path. Every single one of the pros in the Alliance had a moment of bitterness in their past. And Ye Xiu seemed to be among the more tragic ones.

He had run away from home to play. Chen Guo and even Ye Xiu himself felt that he had gone somewhat overboard. And for those who looked down on gamers, this sort of behavior would only seem that much worse to them.

“At least you succeeded!” Chen Guo suddenly said because she suddenly felt that the disdain in her heart wasn’t right. For some, gaming was seen as a terrible drug, the electronic version of heroin. As for Chen Guo and other players, they saw it as a way to kill time. But what about for Ye Xiu and those other pros?

Ye Xiu hadn’t run away from home just to have fun. Chen Guo felt that seeing things like what the majority of society did was somewhat harsh.

Ye Xiu had ran away from home for his passion, for his ideal, for his pursuit of a dream.

If a youth ran away from home to pursue his dream in music, would he receive the same harshness?

If a youth ran away from home to pursue his passion for science, wouldn’t people see it as a testament to his ambition and drive?

There were many many examples of this. It was just that not many would accept gaming as one.

But for Ye Xiu, his dream and passion would never change.

“I wouldn’t get tired even after ten years!”

Chen Guo recalled Ye Xiu’s smile when he said this and suddenly felt the urge to cry.

Chapter 333 – A Sleepless Night

Chen Guo was never very good at controlling her emotions. When she wanted to laugh, she would laugh. When she wanted to be angry, she would be angry. When she wanted to cry, it was even more troublesome. She didn’t hold back her tears.

When she thought about Ye Xiu’s past and realized Ye Xiu’s helplessness, Chen Guo’s nose turned sour and she knew that tears would soon be pouring down.

“I’m going to sleep.” Chen Guo stood up, stamped her feet, and then rushed out.

Ye Xiu was a bit surprised. From his understanding of her, he assumed that she would begin conducting another, even deeper, interrogation. Who would have thought that the boss would just run out like that.

Ye Xiu scratched his head and looked towards Tang Rou. Tang Rou smiled and stood up: “Then I guess I’ll go back and rest as well.”

“Alright.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. After seeing her begin leaving, he put a cigarette to his mouth.

Tang Rou walked towards the door and pulled it open. Suddenly, she stopped and turned her head towards Ye Xiu: “Do you regret running away from home?”

“Never. I just feel a bit sorry. If I regretted it, then I would have gone back long ago. We’re still family.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s true.” Tang Rou paused, nodded her head, and then left the room.

The door to the other room was unlocked. Tang Rou didn’t hurry in. She leaned on the wall for a bit before finally pushing the door open. When she looked inside, she saw Chen Guo lying there on the bed. Her head was squished between two pillows, like the stuffing in a steamed bun.

“Ah! What happened? You don’t like your hair style?” Tang Rou walked up and said.

“You’re back…….” Chen Guo pulled her head out from the pillows and said as if nothing had happened. Her tears had been wiped clean by the pillows already, but her two red eyes couldn’t be hidden. Tang Rou kept smiling and said as if she hadn’t noticed it: “Rest early!”

Quickly, the room turned dark. Chen Guo’s eyes were still wide open as she looked towards the stars.

“Little Tang, are you asleep yet?” Chen Guo suddenly asked.

“Not yet.” Tang Rou replied.

“Do you approve of Ye Xiu’s reckless playing?” Chen Guo asked.

‘Yeah.” A simple reply.

“But now……. He can’t play.” Chen Guo said.

Silence.

Tang Rou obviously understood what Chen Guo was trying to say. For Ye Xiu, the Pro Alliance was his stage. However, he had already retired. On the dazzling All-Star stage, he could only be put together with the normal audience and sit there as a spectator. What would he be feeling during those moments?

“He’s not done yet!” Tang Rou said.

“What do you mean?”

“Someone who was determined enough to run away in order to play wouldn’t give up so easily. His Lord Grim will definitely stand on the stage once again.” Tang Rou said.

“Right, Lord Grim!” Chen Guo thought of that account: “An unspecialized has never appeared onstage before. He also has that self-made Thousand Chance Umbrella. When the time comes, he’ll definitely be scary, no?”

“Yeah, that’ll be fun!” Tang Rou said.

“But…….” Chen Guo was still worried. She had been following Glory up until now and was a fan of Team Excellent Era. She had quietly watched the downfall of the team and had read all sorts of media reporting Ye Xiu’s slipping condition. Even though she had her own thoughts on it, with so many people saying the same thing, Chen Guo didn’t feel very encouraged.

“It’s not that simple!” Tang Rou said after listening to Chen Guo’s doubts.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“One night……” Tang Rou quickly explained the night when Liu Hao paid a visit to the Internet Cafe.

“So there was something like that!!” Chen Guo jumped up from her bed in astonishment.

“That’s why I think that there is still a lot being hidden about his retirement.” Tang Rou said.

Chen Guo nodded her head repeatedly.

“I don’t really have a good understanding of that stuff though, so there’s only so much I can guess about it.” Tang Rou said.

“Uh…… I don’t know too much about the inner workings of the Club, either. However, with Ye Xiu’s seniority and status in Excellent Era, I don’t really think that such a three-footed cat like Liu Hao would be able to do too much.” Chen Guo said. She hadn’t originally been so disgusted by him. She had actually supported him before this because he was the vice captain, but in the blink of an eye, her impression of him turned into a three-footed cat.

“So you’re saying that there’s no way these guys could cause such a storm and that there are most definitely other reasons as well?” Tang Rou said.

“But in Excellent Era, only the Club’s owner would have a higher status than him, right?” Chen Guo said.

“If the owner wanted to kick him out, then it would be easy to do it, right?” Tang Rou said.

“In theory…… but he has to consider a lot of things too. For example: his team’s stability, the fans’ feelings, the sponsors, etc.” Chen Guo had never experienced it herself, but she had seen it before. After following Glory for so many years, she understood quite a few things.

“If for you it’s like that, then….. What if some of the players on the team objected to him, so even if he left the team, the team wouldn’t become a mess but, on the contrary, be even more steady?” Tang Rou said.

“Ah…… and as for the sponsors, he never showed his face, so he had no one to speak for him. He also doesn’t help advertise what the sponsors want, so no matter how amazing he is at the game, he’s of very little value to the sponsors…….” Chen Guo said.

“As for the fans’ feelings…… they saw that the team was performing poorly and that the captain’s condition had been falling as well. For those reports you talked about, they often put those two points as one and the same? For these reports, were these truthful public media reports or was there someone in the dark leading the discussion?” Tang Rou said.

If there was someone spinning the webs behind all this, then the two girls discovered that there were many more possibilities now.

“So you’re saying that Team Excellent Era basically wanted to kick him out?” Chen Guo said in astonishment.

“And it’s not just kicking him out of Team Excellent Era, but also kicking him out of the Glory pro scene.” Tang Rou said.

“That’s….. going too far!!” Chen Guo jumped up again. When she thought of Ye Xiu’s hidden heavy feelings and how hard he had worked in order to open the path for Team Excellent Era’s golden age, only to be kicked out after considerable planning, she felt sympathetic towards him.

“How terrible!” Chen Guo jumped down from her bed. She ran to grab a cup of water and drained it down.

“These are all just guesses!” Tang Rou said.

“It sounds right. Why else would he suddenly retire out of nowhere? His condition is slipping? Did you know? When he fought with Du Ming, he used Dragon Raises Its Head! Do you know what that is? Maybe you don’t know yet, but this is a move that only one person in the entire Glory can pull off! Even though it hadn’t been used in a while, he used it again today. Slipping condition? Bullsh*t!” Chen Guo fired off like a cannon.

“Ah…… then there’s something else I analyzed. Want to listen?” Tang Rou asked.

“Go ahead.” Chen Guo threw down her cup, wiped her mouth and returned back to bed.

“He said before, that when he went back home, he parted on bad terms, right?” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah.”

“What’s the salary for a pro player in Glory? Compared to the average person.” Tang Rou said.

“How could they be compared! Each and every contract is at a sky high price in addition to other sponsorship money. The above average ones can easily get more in a year than what you can get in a hundred years staying in my Internet Cafe.” Chen Guo said.

“Ye Xiu had been a top-tier God in Glory since the very beginning. Even if his family doesn’t understand his achievements, with just his income, his family should have at least been able to recognize that, even though there are several problems with being a pro gamer, Ye Xiu’s an exception. He had already become a top-tier player in the pro scene and he shouldn’t be so disdained like that, right?” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah…… That’s true…… With his status, he shouldn’t have too much to worry about.” Chen Guo said.

“However, they still parted on bad terms. That’s why I think that his family probably isn’t an ordinary family. His status as a Glory pro player and his income didn’t mean anything in front of his family’s eyes.” Tang Rou said.

“Could he be from an extremely wealthy family?” Chen Guo said in astonishment.

“That’s hard to say, but his family can’t be so simple. Whether his family is high up in the political world, business world, or even literary world, his future had already been decided when he was born. He might have a bit of leeway in his choices, but for him to become a pro gamer? That choice probably didn’t exist. That’s why, no matter how incredible his achievements are, his family will never acknowledge him.” Tang Rou said.

“That make sense.” Chen Guo nodded her head.

Tang Rou went silent for a moment. After seeing that Chen Guo wasn’t going to say anything, she continued: “If we go further, when Ye Xiu is no longer able to go on any longer in the pro scene, where will he go then? Is his home his first choice?”

When things got here, Chen Guo suddenly understood: “So you’re saying that his retirement might also have something to do with his family?”

“Yeah……. I have that sort of feeling.” Tang Rou said.

“That…….” Chen Guo didn’t know what to say. If it had only been Excellent Era conspiring, then she could still justly support Ye Xiu and look down on Excellent Era. But if it really was Ye Xiu’s family causing mischief, that would become a family issue and she wasn’t in any position to say anything. What status did she have? A fan? Ye Xiu’s current boss?

“If his family really had been working behind the scenes, then his family’s background can’t be simple……. We might be able to look for clues about his family’s background from his ID card’s address.” Tang Rou said.

Chen Guo heard this, stunned. After a short pause, she said: “I just discovered that your talent in gossiping is even greater than mine.”

Chapter 334 – Day Three

The two girls still didn’t sleep. They were once again whispering to each other. This was when Tang Rou’s deductions stopped though because, in the end, she didn’t really understand the Glory pro scene that well. Even after she began playing the game seriously, most of her attention was still focused on improving herself. She wasn’t a true fan like Chen Guo, who paid attention to the news reports on the pro scene and all the random gossip there.

The two did a recount of what they had discussed. Even though they had deduced all sorts of scenarios, it would be way too disrespectful and impolite to actually take Ye Xiu’s ID card and force him to explain his background.

“It’d be better to ask when an opportunity comes! If he doesn’t want to say it, then that’s that.” Tang Rou said.

“Okay…….” The gossip demon inside Chen Guo was still burning, but she was still someone who understood what proper behavior was.

“The real question is: what is he planning on doing for the future? Is he just going to wait around for a year and then apply with his unspecialized Lord Grim? With his ability, he wouldn’t have any trouble getting in, but which team does he plan on joining? Excellent Era probably isn’t an option, no?” Chen Guo said.

“It’d be best to wait for an opportunity to ask…….” Tang Rou said.

“Okay……”

The two girls chatted, until they finally fell asleep.

Early next morning, the sunlight lit up the room around their wake-up time. After telling each other good morning, they did their daily routines and then looked at each other. The two sneakily walked up outside their neighboring door.

After hearing Ye Xiu reveal a bunch of stuff yesterday night and then analyzing it, they realized that Ye Xiu had a lot of things he needed to worry about. They couldn’t help but prod carefully, afraid that they might accidentally trigger something.

The two girls put their heads against the door, one on top, one on the bottom, in order to listen. The cleaning lady came out of the neighboring room, pushing a small cart and looked suspiciously at the two of them.

“Cough!” Tang Rou immediately coughed after realizing that they had been discovered.

Chen Guo hastily stood up, turned her head to look at the cleaning lady, and officially said: “There’s no need to clean our room today.”

“Understood…….” the service lady said, pushing her cart over and turning her head every couple of steps. The two felt too embarrassed to continue with their previous actions. They also had to do something to try and explain themselves, so they directly knocked on the door.

After a while, Ye Xiu opened the door. His eyes were sleepy as he looked at the two of them: “Why so early? Are we going on a walk again? Even if you try to kill me, I’m not going.”

“Ah, you’re still not awake? Then go sleep a bit longer!” Chen Guo said. Before yesterday, she didn’t think she’d have been able to speak so nicely to Ye Xiu.

Tang Rou shivered. Ye Xiu also straightened up and immediately woke up. He looked at Chen Guo and after a short pause, he asked: “How long is a bit?”

“However long you want!” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu continued to be shocked. He looked towards Tang Rou and pointed at Chen Guo: “Did something happen?”

Tang Rou looked up at the ceiling: “It’s probably your strength as her idol!”

“Really? Wow!” Ye Xiu put out the expression pros used when they looked at the camera after winning a match: “Buy me breakfast and send it to my room.”

Bang!

Ye Xiu closed the door, almost hitting Chen Guo’s nose.

Tang Rou watched as Chen Guo’s warm expression gradually disappeared. After a few twitches, she looked as if she was about to kick the door down, when Tang Rou hastily stopped her: “Can’t you see that he was doing it intentionally? Why do you always fall for his traps!”

Who knew if it was because of Tang Rou’s urge or her idol’s status… but Chen Guo didn’t kick the door. She tugged on Tang Rou: “Hmph, we’re going to eat breakfast.”

In the dining hall, Chen Guo’s furious munching on her steamed buns attracted a few glances from other guests. They were all astonished at how such a pure looking girl could eat so barbarically. For a moment, glances toward Tang Rou’s pleasing appearance were snatched away cleanly.

After annihilating her breakfast, Chen Guo looked at the menu and revealed a hesitant expression. Tang Rou laughed and asked, while wiping her mouth: “Should we bring him something?”

“No! Never!” It had probably been better not to say anything. When Tang Rou asked this, Chen Guo immediately made a decision and got up to leave. Tang Rou laughed once again. She stayed a bit behind her, calling for a waiter to send that room some breakfast. Chen Guo saw her doing this from the reflection from a window, but pretended she didn’t know.

Back at her room, Chen Guo continued to vent her anger through the TV by mashing the remote control and switching channels randomly. Tang Rou didn’t say anything about that. She turned on the computer and logged into the game. When she got in, she discovered that Ye Xiu was online.

“Why aren’t you sleeping?” Tang Rou said surprised.

“I woke up from the noise and didn’t want to sleep anymore.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Breakfast will be sent to you soon.”

“Oh, thanks.”

After only a short exchange, Chen Guo came over. Seeing that Tang Rou was playing Glory and then the chat, she angrily said: “Didn’t he say he was sleepy?” She then rushed out of the room to knock on the neighboring room’s door.

Ye Xiu went to open it. Chen Guo wanted to say something, but she didn’t know where to start.

Ye Xiu lowered his head and looked suspiciously at her two hands: “Where’s my breakfast?”

“Two steamed buns the size of my fists. You want them?” Chen Guo raised her fists. They looked like the Striker’s Collapsing Fist, which Ye Xiu’s rival Han Wenqing was an expert at using.

“Little Tang, I thought you said that breakfast was coming. Did you set me up?” Ye Xiu cried out for help.

“A misunderstanding…….” Tang Rou’s voice floated by.

……

They had only finished half of their planned shopping spree yesterday, but Ye Xiu said that he refused to come today. Chen Guo and Tang Rou discussed for a bit and then decided not to go, either.

As a result, the two rooms turned into two Internet Cafe booths where Glory was being played. Ye Xiu was watching TV, though.

Each room had a computer. Tang Rou and Chen Guo occupied both stations, while Ye Xiu had been kicked out. The reasoning couldn’t be disputed: “You’re already so skilled, so why do you need to practice?”

“To level up……”

“If it’s just that, then I can help you……” Chen Guo said.

As a result, Chen Guo played on Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim account. A normal player getting the chance to use a Silver Weapon? Plus, the Thousand Chance Umbrella could change forms. Ye Xiu taught her how to use it and then Chen Guo slowly began playing with it. She was practically always switching forms. How was she killing monsters to level up? Wasn’t she just using his weapon as a toy to play with?

Seeing that she was having so much fun, he didn’t stop her. Ye Xiu ran over to look at Tang Rou and instructed her on a few Battle Mage techniques.

Dragon Raises Its Head.

This type of high end technique was obviously way beyond someone like Tang Rou, who wasn’t even Level 40 yet. Even though she had been watching yesterday, Dragon Raises Its Head didn’t seem like much in her eyes. She didn’t really know what was so startling about it.

However, yesterday night, Chen Guo had explained repeatedly how incredible Dragon Raises Its Head was. She didn’t know how many times she had repeated herself, but in the end, it made Tang Rou change her mind and realize why it had been so shocking.

Now that the user was here, Tang Rou really wanted to ask him. It was still early, though. Her character’s level wasn’t quite there yet and there was no way she could practice it yet, so what was the point in knowing?

Although, now, her motivation to level was even greater.

“What’d you think about yesterday night?” After Ye Xiu came in, he asked for Tang Rou’s opinion on the match.

“It felt good.” Tang Rou recalled. Her emotions were quite complicated. She wasn’t able to figure out how to describe it. She just felt that something had sprouted in her and was making her itch all over.

“Do you want to come with me into the Pro Alliance?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Go with you?”

“Yeah! I’m definitely going back. As for you, you’d definitely be good enough to become a pro. The real peak of Glory isn’t a single strong person, but rather to be the Champions of the Pro Alliance! Occasionally beating someone isn’t anything to be praised for. Being able to complete the challenges over the entire season and finally beating every single opponent, now that’s the true throne.” Ye Xiu said.

“But you’ve already become the Champion three times. What’s that to you?” Tang Rou laughed.

“There’s no highest, there’s only higher.” Ye Xiu replied.

“So you’re saying that surpassing you really is going to be hard. Just beating you in PK isn’t going to be enough?” Tang Rou said.

“Kid. Why do you like competing with me so much?”

“No matter how you say it, you’re also at the peak of Glory! We can just look at how many Championships you’ve won to see it. Even if your three Championship titles weren’t consecutive titles, you’re still the one with the most titles in Glory, right?”

“Oh, if you say it like that, then I really am quite amazing.” Ye Xiu looked out from the window.

“Who do you think will stand at the top this year?” Tang Rou suddenly asked.

“This year?” Ye Xiu was startled. Tang Rou had unexpectedly asked this question. He hadn’t been prepared for it.

“You can’t know until the last day! That’s what makes things interesting!” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s true….. Not being able to know until it happens is the most interesting.” Tang Rou said.

“Keep it up. You can definitely become a participant and not a bystander.”

“Okay, I’ll think about it.” Tang Rou nodded her head.

“If you’ve made a decision, then don’t be like me!” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou listened and understood what he was saying. She turned her head towards Ye Xiu and laughed: “I’m not 15.”

“I haven’t been 15 in a long time, either.” Ye Xiu grinned.

Today, nothing else happened until it was time for the All-Star event.

Yesterday, the three had shone in the spotlight, especially Ye Xiu. In the press conference after the event, many of the pros straight up told the reporters that he had to be Ye Qiu.

Would their seats be surrounded by dogs today?

Chapter 335 – All Star 24 (1)

From up above in the hotel, the bright Samsara stadium could be seen from the window. They were already busily preparing for the final day.

The All-Star Weekend was a three day event and only had a one-day pass and a three-day pass. Chen Guo had managed to obtain three-day passes. But just from their retail price, it could be seen that the ticket for the third day was the most expensive.

There was only one event on the third day: the All-Star Competitions. The 24 players that were chosen by the fans, in other words, the 24 most popular players, would be split into two teams and would compete in an official match format with an individual competition, a group competition, and a team competition.

Even though the competition was simply just for show, the number of viewers and the ratings it received could be compared to those of the finals in the regular season.

As a result, Chen Guo would be very conflicted as to whether she wouldn’t be able to watch the All-Star event live at the stadium. Tang Rou and Ye Xiu, on the other hand, didn’t really care. Tang Rou still hadn’t logged out of the game, while Ye Xiu was still giving her pointers. They would only turn their heads around whenever Chen Guo said something.

“In reality, your family all know that you’re a pro player, right?” Chen Guo suddenly asked Ye Xiu.

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu didn’t turn his head around this time.

“Then why are you still afraid of revealing yourself?” Chen Guo found the chance to dig deeper.

“Initially, I didn’t want them to find out, but later…… I didn’t want to embarrass them. In their eyes, no matter how great I become, I’m just a failure to them.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo fell silent. She realized that she shouldn’t have dug so deep into Ye Xiu’s roots. Perhaps he didn’t want to remember these things, but she had helped him in bringing them up. She felt extremely bad for doing so.

With this ounce of regret, Chen Guo immediately patted the TV: “Forget about it, then. We won’t go tonight. We can just watch from the TV.”

“Actually, it’ll be fine if only I don’t go. It’s not like it matters if you two go.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, that’s true! When the reporters come, I can give my Internet Cafe some advertisement.” Chen Guo spoke her thoughts.

Tang Rou turned her head and said: “But if you do that, when the customers come, they might be there to crowd around instead of going online, no?”

“Oh……” Chen Guo sighed in lament: “I forgot about that.”

“Go, go! You guys go ahead!” Ye Xiu stood behind Tang Rou and urged them.

“What are you going to do?” Tang Rou turned her head to look at him.

“You’re going to watch the event, no? Let me play!” Ye Xiu exclaimed.

“That isn’t your actual reason, is it? You just want to play the game!” Chen Guo said.

“No way. Didn’t I already tell you about my difficulties?” Ye Xiu said. It was just that his tone was very casual and didn’t sound pained. Chen Guo doubted for a second, but then decided not to say anything more and turned towards Tang Rou.

Tang Rou obviously knew that no matter what, Chen Guo still wanted to go very much. It hadn’t been easy getting the tickets. Missing the big event like this would be something that no fan wouldn’t regret. As a result, she got up and gave the seat to Ye Xiu: “Then we’ll be going now.”

“Go, go!” Ye Xiu waved his hands. He swiftly logged out of Tang Rou’s Soft Mist account and logged on to play his Lord Grim.

“You’re not going to watch the All-Star event?” Chen Guo asked.

“I will, but it’s still early, no? When the time comes, I’ll watch, while playing the game.” Ye Xiu said.

Thus, the two girls left the room, leaving Ye Xiu alone.

The All-Star Competition deserved to be comparable with the finals. It greatly impacted the number of players online. In the afternoon, the leveling areas were still quite crowded, but as it got closer to the peak hours at night, there were fewer players. Playing while watching? That wasn’t something easy to do. An intensive game like Glory didn’t allow for much room to be distracted when fighting.

As a result, Ye Xiu played for a bit and then, when he saw that it was almost time, he logged out of the game and turned on the TV.

The press conference began before the competition. At this moment, the 24 All- Stars hadn’t yet got onstage yet, when suddenly they were swarmed by reporters.

The first one to be interviewed was at the pro player seats. He had arrived early, the upright Team Tyranny vice captain, Zhang Xinjie.

“Hello, vice captain.” The reporter hastily went forward.

“Hello.” Zhang Xinjie nodded his head.

“Even though it’s the All-Star event, you’ve still kept your habit of arriving onstage thirty minutes earlier!” The reporter began to talk.

“Yes.” Zhang Xinjie nodded his head.

“I’m sure our audience is looking forward to how the teams will be split. Could you give us an early reveal?” the reporter said.

Zhang Xinjie looked at the reporter strangely: “Isn’t one of the rules not to reveal things early?”

“Ha ha, it’s about to start in half an hour anyways. It’s not like it’s going to matter much!” the reporter said.

Zhang Xinjie shook his head: “No comment.”

The atmosphere stiffened. The reporter could only switch to a different topic: “With vice captain’s class, you’re probably going to be competing in the team competition. As one of the Master Tacticians, could you have already prepared some sort of amazing strategy?”

“You’ll know when the times comes.” Zhang Xinjie politely replied. His tone didn’t reveal anything.

“Thank you, vice captain……” The reporter was helpless and could only end this pointless interview.

Afterwards, he looked around and saw that someone was already sitting at Team Excellent Era’s seat: Su Mucheng, one of the 24 All-Star players.

The relationship between Su Mucheng and Ye Qiu wasn’t a secret and it was currently an extremely good topic to talk about. The reporter wouldn’t let this opportunity slip and immediately rushed forward along with the cameraman.

“Mucheng, could you give the audience a wave?” the reporter said.

“Hi!” Su Mucheng waved her hands at the camera: “Are you watching TV?”

Ye Xiu, who was sitting in front of the TV, was completely speechless. Wasn’t that wave a bit personal?

Sure enough, the reporter caught it and laughed: “Your wave was a bit special. Was there some sort of special meaning to it?”

Su Mucheng smiled: “You understand.”

“Were you waving to Ye Qiu?” the reporter understood.

“Yup!” Su Mucheng confirmed.

“So you’re saying…… Ye Qiu won’t be coming to watch today?” The reporter immediately became aware of this issue.

“I actually have no idea!” Su Mucheng said.

“But you just waved your hands at the camera!” the reporter said.

“Isn’t it the same thing? If he’s watching in front of the TV, then he’ll have seen me. If he’s at the stadium…… then he’ll see me on the big screen, as well.” Su Mucheng pointed to the big screen in the stadium, which was broadcasting this interview.

“So it’s like that. Thank you, Mucheng.” The interview ended. The frame temporarily cut off and the reporter went to find another target.

The broadcast turned the camera around towards the audience. Ye Xiu looked. Wasn’t the camera pointed at Chen Guo and Tang Rou? The broadcast team had clearly prepared for this and began to focus in on them. These two beautiful girls very naturally looked good on camera. Even though it didn’t have the same feeling as it did yesterday, they were still pleasing to look at. However, the feature clearly wasn’t towards them. The camera turned and turned and then stopped at the empty seat beside the two of them.

After the reporter found another All-Star to interview, the camera turned back to the interview. For matches like these, the pros were more relaxed. Very few of them would be as official like Zhang Xinjie was. They joked around with the reporter and made fun of pros they were friends with. The thirty minutes before the event officially began went by quickly.

When the event officially began, the stadium’s lights turned off. Even though the list of which 24 players were chosen had been released on the first day of the event, the true All-Star event really only began on the final day.

The spotlights flashed on. The first to come up onstage was Samsara’s ace player, Zhou Zekai. Under the dazzling lights, he stepped onto the stage and a projection appeared beside him, which was Zhou Zekai’s character, Cloud Piercer. The crowd gave a deafening cheer for their home team’s ace. Zhou Zekai also acted very appropriately. Along with his looks, he gave off an air that was fit for a god.

The second player to come up onstage was also a Samsara player: Jiang Botao. His character Empty Waves was a Spellblade and was second in Team Samsara only to Zhou Zekai.

Only the player’s name and character was introduced, so the introductions went by very quickly. After Samsara’s two players, next up was Team Blue Rain. They had three players in this year’s All-Star event:

Yu Wenzhou. Character: Swoksaar. Class: Warlock.

Huang Shaotian. Character: Troubling Rain. Class: Blade Master.

Yu Feng. Character: Brilliant Edge. Class: Berserker.

Next came Team Misty Rain’s two players:

Chu Yunxiu. Character: Windy Rain. Class: Elementalist.

Li Hua. Character: Dark Forest. Class: Ninja.

Team Hundred Blossoms:

Tang Hao. Character: Delillo. Class: Brawler.

Zou Yuan. Character: Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Class: Spitfire.

The two Team Hundred Blossom players were somewhat of an anomaly. Tang Hao was a rookie who had only been a pro for two years. His character Delillo wasn’t anything special in the pro circle, but based on his outstanding performance in the last year, he had won over many fans and was able to obtain a spot as an All-Star despite his mediocre account.

As for Zou Yuan, he was the exact opposite of Tang Hao. This hastily-found substitute, using their original team captain Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossom, didn’t have much going for him. The reason he was able to become one of the 24 All-Stars was largely because of Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s popularity. There were too many Glory fans who didn’t want to see this God level character missing from the All-Star stage.

Zou Yuan clearly understood this. On the stage, he quietly stepped back when the projection of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms appeared.

Chapter 336 – All Star 24 (2)

Compared to the All-Stars that introduced before them, of the two Hundred Blossom players, one of them was lacking in terms of his character and his experience, while the other was lacking in skill. Though for Tang to be able to say “the junior succeeds the senior”, it meant that he was also a very arrogant guy. He didn’t care too much about all of this and stood there proudly.

As for Zou Yuan, he was more uneasy. He stood behind his character and it appeared as if he was too afraid to look at the audience.

Next up was Team Excellent Era’s two players, Sun Xiang and Su Mucheng. Their characters, the Battle Mage, One Autumn Leaf, and the Launcher, Dancing Rain, were quickly projected onto the stage. These two were originally the closest partners in the Alliance, but it was different now. Dancing Rain’s owner didn’t hide her thoughts. She stayed a good distance away from Sun Xiang, instead, standing closer to Hundred Blossom’s player, Zou Yuan. The broadcast team knew what they had to do and immediately featured this point. They shifted to the empty seat where Ye Xiu was supposed to be at and once again paused on it.

After them came Team 301’s captain, Yang Cong, with his Assassin, Scene Killer. Even though he was also the ace of a team, Yang Cong’s character couldn’t be considered top-tier and so, when it stood up on stage, it gave off a very modest appearance.

Following Yang Cong’s introduction was a short break. The audience counted twelve players on stage and immediately understood that these twelve players compromised one of the All-Star teams. Tonight, they temporarily became teammates. Team Samsara’s Zhou Zekai turned into the All-Star team’s temporary captain. However, this appointment was simply a title. Zhou Zekai carried the team captain name, but in reality, the one who took on the role of team captain was Team Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou.

No one had any objections to this. This friendly and polite team captain had exceptionally good relations with everyone in the pro circle.

The host conducted brief interviews with each of the twelve players and had them sit in specially prepared seats. The twelve players sat down on one end of the stage and then, the other twelve players began to come onto the stage.

First up was Team Tiny Herb and, like Blue Rain, they too, had three All Stars.

Team Captain Wang Jiexi. Character: Vaccaria. Class: Witch.

Vice Captain Deng Fusheng. Character: Angelica. Class: Knight.

And a Grappler. Li Yihui. Character: Flying Drops. He was also one of Team Tiny Herb’s main pillars.

Next up was two players from Team Tyranny, the team captain and vice captain, Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie.

Han Wenqing’s character was naturally extremely famous, the “King of Fighting”, Desert Smoke. Class: Striker.

Zhang Xinjie’s character, on the other hand, was a Cleric. Character: Immovable Rock.

After them was Team Void’s Li Xuan. Character: Sobbing Ghost. Class: Ghostblade. Alongside him was Wu Yuce from the same team. Character: Carved Ghost. Class: Ghostblade. He and Li Xuan’s duo Ghostblade combo was another classic combo in the pro scene and had been competitors against Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s title of best partners ever ever since their creation.

Following Team Void was Team Wind Howl’s Lin Jingyan. Even though his condition had fallen and now that he had been beaten by Tang Hao, the All-Star invitation was based on popularity, not skill. A God like Lin Jingyan could easily make it into the 24 All-Stars with just his past achievements. In addition, he also had Three Hits, the reputed number one Brawler character.

Lin Jingyan hadn’t come alone from Team Wind Howl. There was also Fang Rui. Character: Doubtful Demon. Class: Thief. His signature style was playing dirty, dirty and dirty.

Next up was Team Thunderclap’s captain, Xiao Shiqin, one of Glory’s four Master Tacticians. He was someone who could take a bad hand and give any team trouble. His character: Life Extinguisher. The name sounded extremely murderous, but his class was actually a Mechanic, which was not a character that could fight against another face-to-face.

After Xiao Shiqin was Team Royal Style’s Tian Sen, who had the back of a tiger and the waist of a bear. The energy from his build was enough to make one tremble. Pro players were practically all shut-ins. Very few of them exercised to such extents. As a result, a pro with a muscular physique was very rarely seen.

Tian Sen’s character was called Peaceful Hermit. Class: Exorcist. It was also a very old God-level character. Tian Sen was already the third owner of this character. With every following successor for this character, Team Royal Style turned worse and worse. Even with a top-tier character, they still weren’t even able to make it to the playoffs.

Following Tian Sen was Zhao Yang, Team Seaside’s ace player. Character: Boundless Sea. Class: Qi Master. Their team’s situation was the same as Yang Cong. The player himself and his character weren’t considered as extremely top-tier, but that was only when it was compared to the top of the top. After all, anyone on the 24 All-Stars list was still an excellent player.

The final twelve players had joined the stage. This team had Wang Jiexi as the temporary captain. He represented the team and said a few words. Afterwards, the host did a brief interview with each of them and the twelve sat down on opposite sides of the stage, facing the other twelve players.

Who would participate in the individual competition? Who would participate in the group competition? And who would participate in the team competition that hadn’t been announced yet? The audience was already quite excited.

Even though the All-Star event was just for show, if they were too relaxed, the viewers would lose interest. As a result, the Alliance would also set things up to fire up the All-Stars. For example, in this event, they had Blue Rain and Tiny Herb, Excellent Era and Tyranny, the two big rivalries, split into two different teams. By doing this, the players wouldn’t play so half-heartedly. Even if the players didn’t care, the fans still would. Some opponents, no matter the time, no matter the location, would never go easy. With these types of players bringing in the energy, what was there to be worried about?

The 24 players were, after all, the 24 most popular players in Glory, so they didn’t need a big introduction. The event quickly entered the competitive stage. The first round for the individual competition was about to begin. Who would be chosen among the two sides? The viewers watching at the stadium and those who were watching the TV were all impatiently waiting for the answer.

The host purposefully slowed down his words when announcing the first contestant in order to heighten the suspense.

In the end, the first team chose Team 301’s Yang Cong, while the second team chose Team Royal Style’s Tian Sen.

Of the twenty-four players, there weren’t any that even the top-tier Gods would be able to steamroll over. Their performance onstage was way more important in this level of competition.

Though for these two players, the end deciding factor was actually the differences in their characters.

Peaceful Hermit was more than powerful enough to be considered a God-level character. Comparatively, Yang Cong’s Scene Kill was a bit inferior. Tian Sen took advantage of his character’s superiority and struck steadily and surely without giving any major openings, until he won the match.

After finishing the match, the two received interviews on the spot. Naturally, the winner said that the loser had played well and that he had won through luck. As for the loser, they said that the winner had played better and deserved the victory. After all, this was only the All-Star event. The two didn’t have any enmity towards each other and weren’t affected by any riling up. The two happily shook each other’s hand and the first match ended.

For the second match, Team Hundred Blossom’s Zou Yuan was sent out. For the second team, they sent out Team Tiny Herb’s Grappler, Li Yihui.

Zou Yuan’s Dazzling Hundred Blossom was undoubtedly a God-level account. It was just that there was nothing praiseworthy about his performance in the season. This hastily-found substitute had to take the place of God Zhang Jiale and he also had to use the team’s core account. The amount of pressure on Zou Yuan was unimaginable. Though for this All-Star event, where there didn’t need to be any pressure, the relaxed Zou Yuan unexpectedly gave off his most outstanding performance of the season. He defeated the Champion team’s Li Yihui, obtaining a heated round of applause.

After another modest interview, the third match began. For the individual competition, each match was one round. There was no best-of-three format. As a result, there wasn’t a need for too much thinking for who to send out.

For the first team, they sent out Team Blue Rain’s Berserker Yu Feng. As for the second team, they sent out Team Wind Howl’s dirty Fang Rui.

In the individual competition, the two rivals, Blue Rain and Tiny Herb, had both sent out players. Unfortunately, they had missed each other. If these two teams’ players fought, the audience members were certain that the match would be more intense. From this, it could be seen that the host split the teams accordingly, but when it came to the actual competition, which players were sent out entirely depended on the players. If not, then how could the Alliance miss out on such an opportunity?

Yu Feng’s Berserker was a class that went for direct attacks. Fang Rui’s character, on the other hand, was a dirty Thief. This match turned into a game of hide and seek, but no one dared to look down on the amount of skill involved in the match.

The two were carefully examining the other side’s movements and slowly wearing down their opponent. Of the three individual matches, this one took the longest. After a good five minutes, Fang Rui’s dirty Thief made a mistake, which was seized by Yu Feng, who directly ended the match.

The applause was deafening. A dirty way of fighting was one type of extreme. Some people loved it, while others hated it. The audience members who were clapping like crazy were naturally those who hated that sort of dirty fighting. Seeing the dirty Fang Rui get cut down brought them incomparable delight.

Chapter 337 – All Star Competition

Even though the audience cheered when the dirty Fang Rui fell, he didn’t care at all. Although many did not like his way of fighting, he had many supporters as well. If not, then he wouldn’t have been able to enter the ranks of the all stars.

He politely waved his hands towards the audience along with the victorious Yu Feng and then left the stage.

The individual stage was over. Team One had earned 2 points, while Team Two’s had earned 1 points. Team Two was current losing.

Although it was only for show, the spectators still cared about who won or lost. They paid attention to which side their favorite pros were on. For example, Chen Guo naturally supported the team that Su Mucheng was on.

After a few minutes, the second competition, the Group Competition, began. The viewers quietly discussed the possible arrangements for the groups as the players for the first match went out.

For Team One, the first player to come out was Excellent Era’s ace, Sun Xiang. As soon as One Autumn Leaf was projected onto the stage, the crowd erupted into cheers.

For Team Two’s, their first player was Wind Howl’s Lin Jingyan.

Sun Xiang’s mechanics were not below Tang Hao’s and One Autumn Leaf was absolutely the better character. On paper, Sun Xiang had the higher chance of winning.

However, the paper didn’t account for the two’s current conditions.

In the Rookie Challenge Competition, one had been beaten with a “junior succeeds the senior”, while one had been beaten with a “still too green”. Both defeats had been somewhat embarrassing. Especially for Sun Xiang, since he had dug the hole himself. It had only been two days since then. If their mental states hadn’t adjusted, then their performance on stage could very likely be affected.

When the two sides fought, Lin Jingyan performed efficient and ruthless as always, while Sun Xiang clearly was having a bit of situation. Young people could rarely compete with the veterans in having this type of inner quality. Even though Sun Xiang was stronger on paper, the deciding factor in a match was still their performance on stage. Nothing praiseworthy could be said about Sun Xiang’s current performance. In the end, Lin Jingyan’s Three Hits still had a quarter of his health left, when One Autumn Leaf fell.

Sun Xiang silently exited his booth amidst the crowd’s boos. Chen Guo was even less polite and began ridiculing him. If this had been yesterday, she wouldn’t have gone so far, but after hearing of Ye Xiu’s past, Chen Guo didn’t have any good feelings towards Team Excellent Era. This clearly showed that Chen Guo cared more about the players than the team, so when she discovered a bad relationship between a player and his team, with the team being unjust, her opinions of the team naturally turned sour. How could she care about Sun Xiang, Ye Xiu’s replacement? As soon as she saw that he wasn’t helping the team win any advantages, she immediately looked down on him.

After Sun Xiang answered a few interview questions, he hastily exited the stage. The second player in Team One’s group was Team Misty Rain’s Li Hua using the Ninja, Dark Forest.

Li Hua was known for his quick mechanics and constantly changing movements. This type of player was the bane of a veteran with a deteriorating condition like Lin Jingyan. In addition, Dark Forest had a full health bar, while Three Hits only had a quarter health left. This time, Lin Jingyan was defeated.

Team Two’s followed up with Team Seaside’s Zhao Yang using his Qi Master, Boundless Sea.

Qi Masters were an all around class. They had both offensive and defensive skills. They could support and burst. They were very easy to pick up. However, once things reached the pro level, there wasn’t any advantage in being “easy to pick up”. No matter how difficult the class, at that level, all of them were being played at extremely high levels.

The battle between these two was another intense fight. Each side displayed their character and play style’s strengths. Neither side made any obvious mistakes either. In the end, Zhao Yang was able to defeat Li Hua with the small advantage Lin Jingyan had brought.

The final player to come out for Team One was Team Hundred Blossom’s Tang Hao. He had succeeded earlier with his “junior succeeds the senior” and was at peak condition. Against Zhao Yang’s Boundless Sea, he easily defeated him.

Team Two’s’s final player was unexpectedly Team Thunderclap’s Xiao Shiqin.

The audience was very surprised by this arrangement. This was because they all knew that Xiao Shiqin was good at team play. In the All Star Competition, players weren’t allowed to participate in more than one competition, so the audience had expected Xiao Shiqin to participate in the team competition. In this team of all stars, all of them should be a better choice than Xiao Shiqin, no?

In any case, the match began and just as expected, Xiao Shiqin’s solo ability couldn’t be compared to Tang Hao. Even if his character Life Extinguisher was slightly better than Tang Hao’s Delillo, he was still beaten.

In the end, Xiao Shiqin was defeated and Tang Hao had made a turnaround for Team One. Team One won the group competition and earned two points. They were now winning 3-2. Undoubtedly, the final team competition would determine who won and who lost.

Before that, there was a quick rest break and highlight replay. The audience recalled the all stars that played in the group competition. They discovered that on paper, Team One had the advantage. Sun Xiang and Tang Hao, the two second-year rookies already had God-level skill, while the players that came out for Team Two’s truly weren’t as good.

Of course, Sun Xiang didn’t play well and lost the first match, making many of them look down on him. In the end, Tang Hao defeated two opponents and played outstandingly in this All Star Competition. The players he had defeated were after all, All Star level players.

After a short break, the final performance in the All Star Weekend was about to begin. This sort of brawl between all stars could really only be seen in the All Star Competition. That sort of one on one play could be seen normally when two teams fought against each other.

As for which players were chosen for the two teams, all the audience had to do was eliminate the ones that had already gone up. The only part they didn’t know was who would be the substitute player.

Twelve players came up on stage one after the other. After receiving interviews asking random nonsense like if they had the confidence to win or not, the twelve players entered their respective booths.

The map was projected onto the stage and the arrangement for the two teams was immediately clear.

For Team One, the main roster consisted of Samsara’s Zhou Zekai, Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian, Misty Rain’s Chu Yunxiu, and Excellent Era’s Su Mucheng. Their reserve player was Samsara’s Jiang Botao.

For Team Two’s, the main roster consisted of Tiny Herb’s Wang Jiexi and Deng Fusheng, Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie, Void’s Li Xuan and Wu Yuce. Their reserve player was unexpectedly Han Wenqing!

Han Wenqing being the substitute was a big surprise to the viewers. However, after looking more closely at Team Two’s arrangement, they understood why they had Xiao Shiqin participate in the group competition.

Team Two’s had two Master Tacticians, so with Zhang Xinjie there, they could let Xiao Shiqin participate in the group competition. The six remaining players on Team Two’s was their most balanced formation. Wang Xinjie and Deng Fusheng, one active, one quiet. Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie, one offensive, one supportive. Li Xuan and Wu Yuce, the Ghostblade duo. Without a doubt, Team Two’s play style would be full of variations.

As for Team One, they were clearly an offensive oriented formation.

Apart from Yu Wenzhou’s Warlock, Swoksaar, their team didn’t have any other supports. Huang Shaotian’s Blade Master Troubling Rain, Zhou Zekai’s Sharpshooter Cloud Piercer, Chu Yunxiu’s Elementalist Windy Rain, Su Mucheng’s Launcher Dancing Rain. They were all offensive classes. Only their reserve player, Jiang Botao’s Spellblade Empty Waves had decent crowd control with his Wave Sword and Wave Boundary.

However, looking at them from an offensive perspective, Team One had both extremely long ranged and close ranged members. Just from their range, they had an all around offense. Their team formation hadn’t been randomly chosen.

As for their team lacking the very important support and crowd control classes, there wasn’t much they could do about it in the All Star Competition. After all, the more popular players were certainly the ones who were more offensive oriented players. It was just like how in football, the forwards were definitely more eye catching than the rear guard. And since the all stars were chosen by popular vote, they wouldn’t have such a good team composition like a normal team. Their end result had clear faults, but there wasn’t much they could do about it.

In comparison, Team Two’s had included both supports and crowd control characters inside, so their formation was more perfect.

The host and broadcast clearly recognized that this was the true climax for the All Star Event and began to build up the suspense. The commentators analyzed both side’s team formation. When the excitement hits its peak, that was when the All Star Event’s team competition officially began.

An impressive ten of Glory’s top-tier characters from their respective classes were participating in this battle. Team One’s shot caller was Yu Wenzhou. As for Team Two’s, even though Wang Jiexi’s shot calling was good, he gave the position to Zhang Xinjie. These two Master Tacticians would lead the confrontation between the two sides.

Team One arranged their troops and then directly rushed forward. Team Two’s seemed to have understood their intent. Their five players scattered and found their own spots on the map, waiting for the other team’s players to come up.

This sort of tactical intent obviously couldn’t be revealed to the opponent. However, there was a flaw in this All Star Event due to the projection!

The hosts had specially installed windows in the player booths to let the players have a taste of the projection technology. However, at this moment, the projection technology allowed Team One to see Team Two’s tactical intent. This was something that the hosts had miscalculated. They had only been paying attention to the experience the projection provided and had compromised the competitiveness on accident.

Chapter 338 – Know Yourself, Know Your Enemy

Team One quickly adjusted their advances. Those who had some sense of strategy immediately understood their intent. They discovered that the adjustments had been made to counter Team Two’s formation. The spectators didn’t know that there was such a large flaw in the booths. At the moment, they were all gasping in surprise. They thought that it was Team One’s Master Tactician, Yu Wenzhou, who was predicting Team Two’s formation like an all-knowing God.

As for Team Two’s supporters, when they saw this, they looked like captured lambs and immediately felt worried. They wished that they could rush up onstage and warn Team Two.

As Team One’s players closed in, quite a few members of the crowd anxiously stood up, when they suddenly saw Team Two’s formation change. The scattered players contracted together and were ready for the Team One’s incoming assault.

However, Team One reacted quickly as well. Their initial strategy was tossed away and they contracted as well, in preparation for a direct confrontation with Team Two.

The audience members who understood what was going on were clapping wildly. They felt that the two shot-callers deserved to be called Master Tacticians. They were like true Gods, predicting what the other side was going to do next.

How could they know that the shot-callers on both sides, Yu Wenzhou and Zhang Xinjie, were both laughing bitterly.

They were both smart, but their opponents weren’t stupid, either. In reality, the two sides could see the other side’s movements just from looking at the projection. They weren’t making any godly predictions. They were just looking at the map! Because both team consisted of top-tier players with a solid knowledge of tactics and strategies, even though they weren’t from the same team, their coordination wouldn’t be too poor. Their movements after hearing the commands were clean and crisp. It looked as if their adjustments to their formations had been practiced beforehand. The unknowing spectators only felt how amazing and spectacular they were.

Yu Wenzhou and Zhang Xinjie could see how sharp both sides were. Planning a sneak attack or flanking each other weren’t going to work. In this match, a direct confrontation was clearly their only option.

Zhang Xinjie felt like their side had the advantage in a direct confrontation. After all, their team had the balanced team composition. As for Team One’s offense-oriented team, they were better at bullying, but both teams consisted of all-stars. Their skill levels were equal, so there was no way that they would be pushed down so easily.

Thus, Zhang Xinjie stopped playing tricks. He gave an order and Team Two advanced forward in an X Formation.

The audience saw that it seemed like the fight would start soon. But who would have thought that the initially aggressive Team One would suddenly have their hands and feet bound and, instead of meeting the fight, they actually began to retreat. Their movements made the audience very confused. But what made the audience even more confused was that, when Team One began to retreat, Team Two suddenly halted.

The audience members looked at one another. What were these two Tacticians thinking? They couldn’t understand at all!

The audience was completely confused. Zhang Xinjie, on the other hand, had sweat pouring down from his head.

Why did Team Two suddenly stop? The reason they had stopped was because, as soon as Team One began to retreat, they were unable to see the positions of Team One’s players anymore from their booth windows. Team One’s five players utilized their dead angle in order to hide from them.

Zhang Xinjie would naturally be alarmed. He immediately understood that Yu Wenzhou’s strategic sight was better than his. He had thought about how normal matches and this match differed and that both sides had the ability to see the general overview of the battle through the projection. This was something that official matches definitely wouldn’t have, which was why Yu Wenzhou had specially took note of the position of Zhang Xinjie’s booth, in order to determine where his blind spot was. And now, he had used this point, giving his team, Team One, the chance to hide. Team Two was now fighting against an invisible enemy. The momentum immediately shifted. As for Zhang Xinjie, he hadn’t taken note of the position of Yu Wenzhou’s booth. It wouldn’t be good to randomly guess, either, so his only option was to have his team halt temporarily.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t hide anything and told his team of his current predicament.

“I can see from here.” Wang Jiexi replied. The positions of their booths were different, so they had different viewing angles. Zhang Xinjie’s dead angle could be seen from Wang Jiexi’s point of view.

“Then I’ll hand the shot-calling over to you!” Zhang Xinjie gave him the authority.

He may be called a Master Tactician, but that didn’t mean that their victory would be guaranteed with his shot-calling. Handing the shot-calling over to Wang Jiexi, in order to solve their current predicament, didn’t mean that they were necessarily going to lose. After Wang Jiexi observed Team One’s formation, he read and understood the opponent’s intent and Team Two naturally made their adjustments.

The adjustment was simple. Their goal was to not suffer losses. They weren’t thinking of using the knowledge of their opponent’s positions to their advantage. This was because this match truly was too transparent. The flaw in the booths made it so that both sides knew themselves and knew their enemies. Even when Yu Wenzhou used his knowledge of Zhang Xinjie’s point of view to his advantage, by switching the command over to Wang Jiexi, everything had gone back to the beginning. Neither side could deceive the other.

Even if they took Wang Jiexi into account, there was still Li Xuan and Deng Fusheng……. It wasn’t like Yu Wenzhou could account for everyone’s point of view, right? If he really did, then their movements would be very limited and they wouldn’t be able to make any sneak attacks.

These exchanges truly showed the two sides’ abilities. It was just that, to the audience members, they couldn’t really understand what was going on. Only Ye Xiu, who was an expert and who had gone up on stage before, could tell from their movements what their situation was. He couldn’t help but laugh when he saw it.

“Ah, this isn’t very fun. You can see us. We can see you. Hide and seek? They might as well just send one player up at a time and play the group competition out!”

Up until now, the two sides still hadn’t fought each other, yet. But Team One’s chat window suddenly exploded with Huang Shaotian’s chatter. These words couldn’t be seen from the projection, but they could clearly be seen on the electronic screens that were broadcasting the battle, as well as on the player’s computers.

Huang Shaotian represented everyone and directly stood out, challenging the other side to duels.

“Do you dare?”

“Are you coming?”

“You afraid?”

“Could it be that you want to fight me in a 2v1?”

No one on either side responded. Huang Shaotian was obviously ridiculing them. He was indicating that not accepting his challenge would be too shameful.

The audience clearly wasn’t as cool-headed as the pros were. They had already begun to get riled up. Team One’s supporters looked down on Team Two’s cowardice. Team Two, on the other hand, were ridiculing Huang Shaotian’s competitive attitude and how he wanted the team competition to turn into individual duels.

At this moment, the players on stage still hadn’t done anything and the audience members were already on the verge of breaking into a brawl.

Team Two stayed cool-headed the entire way through. On one hand, they were used to it. But on the other hand…… Huang Shaotian was continuously taunting them. But he wasn’t wrong though; their Team Two didn’t dare.

Dueling also depended on the team composition. As a whole, Team Two had support and crowd control classes. They were very complete. But in duels, they were against burst characters. If Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric from Team Two went up, that would just be giving Team One free points. How could they agree to duels?

But there was no escape! Huang Shaotian saw through this point and knew that they wouldn’t agree, so he continued to taunt at them. This was also a part of his style. Team Two consisted of all-stars, so they wouldn’t be so easily incited. As a result, they could only laugh bitterly. There were some from Team Two that wanted to respond back to Huang Shaotian, but Han Wenqing was currently crouching at his reserve seat.

Being taunted at like that wasn’t good for their reputation. Team Two advanced forward to pressure them, but Team One seemed to take delight in watching Huang Shaotian taunt them and retreated in response.

If Team Two had someone who liked to trash talk, then they would have spoken up long ago. But the problem was, in Team Two, not a single one of them liked to trash talk. And for Team One, they had the King of Trash Talking, so they had the complete advantage in the chat window.

Retreat, retreat, retreat. Team One only retreated, while Team Two only advanced.

Sometimes the person that was doing the trash talking didn’t know if it was working. Team Two thought that they were being very cool-headed in response to Huang Shaotian’s trash talk, but to the outsiders, they thought that they had been provoked by Huang Shaotian.

Team Two continued to push forward and, just as they were about to fight, Team One’s five players suddenly scattered. Team Two still hadn’t figured what was going on, yet, when suddenly, Team One’s players disappeared from their sight.

The five players were already used to looking out of the window to see the projection.

“None!”

“None.”

“None.”

“None here.”

“None……”

The five players communicated and immediately became alarmed. Had the other side actually figured out where all of their dead angles were?

“Hurry and retreat!” Zhang Xinjie shouted. He had already realized that they were in one of their opponents’ formations. They seemed to have intentionally lured them to this spot and created this situation…….

Zhang Xinjie retreated along with everyone else, while carefully observing the terrain around them, looking at those spots that they weren’t able to see.

“Everyone, stay in position!” Zhang Xinjie quickly reminded. He discovered that there were too many places here for the opponent to hide.

At this moment, the first attack of the match struck.

“Pshew!” Team Two nimbly stepped to the side. A Laser Beam split their formation into two.

“Ha ha ha, I can finally move!” A word bubble popped out from above Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain. Who knew where he had come from? He struck with a Falling Light Blade from up above, directly into the five players’ formation.

Chapter 339 – Each Side With Their Own Shortcomings

If this type of surprise attack agitated their team, then Team Two wouldn’t deserve to be called all stars. Huan Shaotian’s Falling Light Blade had been sudden, but Team Two didn’t react slowly. Tiny Herb Vice Captain Deng Fusheng’s Knight Angelica stepped out on his own and raised his shield to take the blow: Shield Counter.

Shield Counter’s effects were determined by the skill that was used against it. When a direct attack was Shield Countered, the damage from the attack and its effects would be reflected back onto the attacker according to a certain percentage. It could be considered quite an abnormal defensive skill.

Even though Falling Light Blade fell from the sky, against the shield, it had no way of continuing down. The reflect from the shield would give rise to a knock up effect. How could the experienced Huang Shaotian not know this? He immediately dispelled his skill and switched to a Falling Phoenix Slash, sweeping past the lone defender.

Huang Shaotian being able to use so many movements in such a short amount of time wasn’t something an ordinary Glory fan could do. The crowd had already erupted into cheers.

Deng Fusheng had no way of using Shield Counter to receive Falling Phoenix Slash. If he changed directions and his position, allowing him to use another skill, he could try again. However, Shield Counter was on cooldown right now. How could he use it again? However, he wasn’t the only player on Team Two. Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria, dressed in a black magic robe and a large wizard cap, hopped to the side. He waved his arms and a Shadow Cloak headed towards Troubling Rain.

Dark Mantle was a Grab skill and had high priority. At this moment, Wang Jiexi choosing use it against Troubling Rain’s Falling Phoenix Slash meant that he had the utmost confidence he would be able to block it.

Suddenly, a gunshot rang out. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had rushed out, firing rapidly towards them. Amidst the high speed exchange, his gun aimed towards Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria. If Wang Jiexi persisted in using Dark Mantle, then he would certainly be hit by Zhou Zekai’s firing.

Wang Jiexi immediately decided to cancel his Dark Mantle and leaped backwards. Deng Fusheng’s Angelica perfectly switched positions with him.

Angelica’s shield blocked Zhou Zekai’s firing. Huang Shaotian’s Falling Phoenix Slash didn’t receive any hindrances, but his target had already moved away, causing him to miss.

Li Xuan and Wu Yuce didn’t idle around either. They cast an Ice Boundary and Flame Boundary. Ice and fire overlapped headed towards Troubling Rain.

No matter how good Huang Shaotian was, he had no way to run from this encirclement.

Team Void relied mainly on Ghostblades. Li Xuan’s Sobbing Ghost was also considered the number one Phantom Demon. Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost was also a top-tier Ghostblade. In setting up an Ice and Fire Boundary, who could do it better than these two?

Sobbing Ghost’s Silver Tachi, Four Heavenly Dances, buffed Ice, Fire, and Dark attribute skills. The Boundary set up by his Ghostblade would certainly be stronger than a normal one.

Even for Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain, being surrounded by these two Ghostblade Boundaries immediately made the situation difficult for him. If it had just been a Flame Boundary, then with Huang Shaotian’s exceptional mechanics, dodging those fire ghosts wouldn’t have posed a problem. However, with an Ice Boundary on top of it, he didn’t immediately get turned into ice, however his movement speed had slowed down. With this movement debuff, how could he dodge these fire ghosts? A mob of ghosts instantly leaped onto Troubling Rain’s body, enveloping him in a purple fire.

With Troubling Rain trapped, Team Two prepared to surround him. Suddenly, a bang reverberated through the air and several ice walls erupted from the ground, putting up a wall protecting Troubling Rain. Chu Yunxiu’s Elementalist Windy Rain had come out.

“Retreat!” Zhang Xinjie immediately shouted. But these experienced all stars didn’t need his reminder and had already scattered. Sure enough, Windy Rain waved her hands forming a magic symbol. “Bang!” The ice walls shattered and ice shards shot wildly into the surroundings. But Team Two had backed away in time. The damage from one or two ice shards hitting could be ignored.

Amidst the rain of ice, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain rushed forward with a Triple Slash. His speed was even faster than those ice shards and in an instant, he had closed in on Sobbing Ghost.

Sobbing Ghost might be a powerful Phantom Demon, but the “Sword Saint” Troubling Rain wasn’t an ordinary Blade Master. Troubling Rain moved like a shooting star and arrived in front of Sobbing Ghost in the blink of an eye. Troubling Rain clearly had movement speed increases on his equipment.

He initiated with an Upwards Slash and this time, no one could save Sobbing Ghost as he was launched into the air. Li Xuan immediately adjusted himself in order to break the knock up, when a cannon shot fired from far away. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had sent over an artillery shell.

Team Two’s players were quite helpless against Su Mucheng’s attacks.

Their team composition consisted of a Witch, a Knight, two Ghostblades, and a Cleric. They didn’t have anyone that could match a Launcher’s range. In terms of pure DPS, their Team Two had no way of competing against Team One. They required teamwork using different strategies to outlast the other team. There was nothing they could do about the long ranged attacks, but their team wouldn’t fall into disarray just because of that.

Under Zhang Xinjie’s shot calling, Team Two’s players didn’t hurry to surround Su Mucheng and instead went to save Sobbing Ghost.

Li Xuan’s Sobbing Ghost still hadn’t come down yet after being launched up. Huang Shaotian had completed the first step and Su Mucheng had completed the second step by firing an explosion to get him away from his allies. Next up was Zhou Zekai, who executed a brilliant Delivery Gun. Their plan was to send Sobbing Ghost farther away in order to take him down first.

It seemed like trying to save him wouldn’t be easy.

Chu Yunxiu’s Elementalist continued to fire AoE magic attacks, blocking their advances. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain stuck close to them, charging in and out. His head also carried a bunch of word bubbles, adding to his annoyance. Apart from this, Su Mucheng’s Launcher chased after behind them with artillery shells. Team Two could only grit their teeth and dodge.

As an all star and the number one God of Ghostblades, it wasn’t as if Li Xuan could do nothing about the Delivery Gun. However, the problem was Delivery Gun wasn’t the only thing he had to worry about. Yu Wenzhou, Team One’s shot caller, hadn’t joined in on the intense battle previously, but at this moment, he came out. His Warlock Swoksaar calmly cast all sorts of curses and magic. His movements weren’t quick, but they were extremely accurate. In addition, his actions synergized very well with Zhou Zekai’s firing. It was very difficult to believe that these two had never played together before.

With these two top-tier players coordinating spectacularly together, Li Xuan was unable to escape. The reason he was able to hang on though was because of his character’s advantage. Ghostblades had relatively high innate Dark resistance. The Warlock’s curses and magic were all Dark attribute attacks. As a result, Sobbing Ghost didn’t take as much damage. This issue could be eliminated by increasing the tempo, however, everyone in Glory knew of Yu Wenzhou’s famous “handicapped hands”. Besides increasing the tempo, you could have him do anything else. It was a pity. His hands weren’t able to keep up. This sort of weakness couldn’t be resolved.

However, this issue only dragged things out a bit longer, that was all. Ghostblades had never been solo characters, plus, it was a 1v2. Wasn’t he already in an extremely unfavorable position?

Li Xuan urgently needed help, but help was coming late.

Even though Team Two were strong as a whole, they had one clear weakness: range.

Su Mucheng couldn’t be ignored and since she was used to supporting behind Ye Xiu, this formation was extremely favorable for her. Under Yu Wenzhou’s lead, every player’s strengths were completely brought out. For example, Huang Shaotian charging in and causing a disturbance. Causing a disturbance would make the opponents feel annoyed and who else was better at this than Huang Shaotian? He could put out two attacks as well. Those strings of word bubbles were already making some of the audience members unable to bear it.

Team Two could do nothing about their slow advance.

In the end, Li Xuan’s reinforcements didn’t arrive on time and under the suppression by those two players, his character died in battle.

Team One’s supporters immediately cheered and felt like this team competition was completely worth the ticket price.

As soon as Li Xuan’s Sobbing Ghost died, Huang Shaotian immediately ran away in order to avoid them switching their focus to him. Chu Yunxiu and Su Mucheng had changed their attack patterns as well.

To their surprise, Team Two used this time to suddenly break out from their previous restrictions and immediately blocked off Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

Escaping from an encirclement couldn’t be done with just decision making and knowledge. After all, some decisions could only be made with a high enough hand speed. This once again hit upon Yu Wenzhou’s weakness. His current plight was extremely terrible as the four assaulted him fiercely.

However, Team One’s rescue wasn’t as restricted as Team Two’s. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer Slide Kicked into the encirclement to the audience’s cries of alarm. They all thought he had thrown himself into a trap and killed himself. But then, Cloud Piercer jumped up, dodged an attack, took out two guns, crossed them in front of his head and repeatedly fired.

Sharpshooter Skill: Random Firing.

Sidestepping, turning, stretching his arms, crossing his arms, Cloud Piercer continued to shift stances as if Zhou Zekai was controlling the Random Firing.

Gunshots rang through the air and bullets flew out randomly. The four players on Team Two had actually all been blown away out of their formation. Wu Yuce controlled his Ghostblade to quickly jump back in order to get out of range, but who would have thought that after this jump, he would never touch the ground again.

The stadium once again erupted into cheers. Zhou Zekai was even using Delivery Gun, while Randomly Firing!!!

Chapter 340 – The Gods Erupt

Random Firing. This was the Boneyard Wild BOSS Blood Gunner Yagg’s Berserk skill. As for players, this was a Sharpshooter Level 60 skill.

But compared to the BOSS’s Random Firing, who knew how many times better the Great Gunner Cloud Piercer’s Random Firing was.

The Blood Gunner’s was a true random firing, but Cloud Piercer’s had order within the randomness. Being able to accurately hit targets without missing was already incredible, but even more terrifying was that during the brief moment, he completed a Delivery Gun. This was a godly performance.

Being Samsara’s home stadium, there were naturally many Zhou Zekai fans. With such an astonishing display, the largest craze today erupted.

Wild applause and cheers drowned out the broadcast. As for the broadcast, they were all delighted. The crowd’s excitement was exactly what they wanted to see from the crowd.

Zhou Zekai might not be very good at interviews, but on stage, his ability to stir up the crowd didn’t lose to any player.

Team Two’s four players had been forced back. Wu Yuce’s Carved Phantom had been directly sent flying away. The other three didn’t have an opportunity to rescue him; they were still being suppressed by the Random Firing!

As soon as Random Firing stopped, Cloud Piercer continued his barrage. He sprinted forward, chasing after Carved Ghost. The forced back three players were finally released. Deng Fusheng’s Angelica rushed forward with his shield raised, hoping to block Cloud Piercer’s bullets. Suddenly, Zhou Zekai Slide Kicked, diving past Deng Fusheng’s Angelica.

Deng Fusheng immediately had Angelica jump to the side. The moment the two passed each other, Cloud Piercer suddenly stood up and struck out with a Knee Strike.

The attack had been both fast and sudden, but Deng Fusheng wasn’t slow. He raised his shield and backed away. He didn’t try to block him off because he knew that Gunners had the skill, Punisher, which would force him to be knocked down. Against this type of skill, even using “Shield Counter” wouldn’t block its effects.

The instant Deng Fusheng felt the strike hit his shield, he moved his shield to one side and stabbed forward with a Holy Punishment. His blade flashed with light and a cross appeared on the ground. However, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was already gone. Deng Fusheng was surprised, but then he saw a shadow flit across the ground. He hastily lifted up his head to look, but blood had already splashed into his line of sight. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had leaped over his head and at the same time, the two guns in his hands continued to dance about. This time, the bullets poured down onto him like rain.

Random Firing. Random Firing again. Except this time, the Random Firing had been done in the air, making it more difficult to use. But it seemed like this sort of problem didn’t exist for Zhou Zekai. The even more difficult maneuver, hitting a single target using Random Fire, had been achieved beautifully.

Of course, a Level 60 skill like Random Firing wouldn’t have a short cooldown. However, Sharpshooters had a skill called Dual Load, which allowed them to repeat a skill that was on cooldown. Zhou Zekai had clearly used this and doubled Random Firing’s cooldown. This was what allowed him to use Random Firing in quick succession.

Random Firing was supposed to be an AoE skill, but in Zhou Zekai’s hands, it had been twisted into a single target skill. The entire attack focused onto Deng Fusheng’s Knight. Even though the Knight was the class with the highest defense, it wasn’t a small blow. Even worse, Zhoue Zekai’s attacks didn’t stop there. He ignored the target he had been chasing and after landing on the ground, he began circling around Angelica, running and firing.

The atmosphere of the crowd grew even wilder.

Zhou Zekai was actually suppressing Deng Fusheng. For such a situation to occur on two All Stars didn’t mean that Deng Fusheng was weak, but rather, Zhou Zekai was too strong. So strong that it was beyond the norm. There were already die hard Zhou Zekai fans waving around banners calling him the “Glory’s Number One Expert”. With Zhou Zekai’s current performance, he really was living up to the name. Team Two’s four players had practically been broken up by him alone. Wang Jiexi, Deng Fusheng, Zhang Xinjie, Wu Yuce, these were all famous and resounding figures, yet in front of him, they appeared as if they were just random players.

Team Two hurriedly tried to turn the situation around. Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria flew after Cloud Piercer, but was suddenly blocked by Huang Shaotian. The two fought a dazzling battle and for now, it was difficult to say who was on top.

As for Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost, which had been sent flying away by Zhou Zekai, was now being taken care of by the sole two female all stars. These two had a good sense for tactics and were also good friends. In private, the two often played together and as a result, their current coordination showed this. Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost was a rare kind in the pro scene, a Phantom Demon and Sword Demon hybrid. However, despites his all-roundedness, he was unable to keep up with the 2v1 and was slowly being pushed back.

Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric was a support class without many DPS skills. He wanted to go and save them, but he was suddenly blocked by Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar. The two began battling unhurried.

Zhang Xinjie observed the situation. Team One’s intents really had been what Huang Shaotian had been chattering about. They wanted to split them apart and fight 1v1s. After their formation was broken apart, the two formed this type of situation. Team One consisted of completely offensive characters. In a 1v1, Team Two would certainly suffer. In addition, Li Xuan’s Sobbing Ghost had already died. After quickly scanning around him, he saw that Wang Jiexi and Huang Shaotian were in a deadlock. Deng Fusheng was being suppressed by Zhou Zekai quite miserably. As for Wu Yuce, calling it miserably would be an understatement, in a 1v2 situation, he was simply taking a beating.

It had to be known that Chu Yunxiu’s biggest weakness was that she often collapsed under pressure, but since this was the All Star Competition and just for show, she had absolutely no pressure on her. Her performance right now wouldn’t lose to top-tier Gods like Wang Jiexi or Huang Shaotian. With her as the main attacker and Su Mucheng, who was an expert at coordinating with others, Wu Yuce had practically no way of fighting back.

Speaking of top-tier Gods, Team Two had one more.

Han Wenqing and his Desert Dust had originally been on the reserve player seat. After Li Xuan’s Sobbing Ghost died, his character would automatically take his place. There were many areas on the map his character could appear at. Even if they were in the middle of a battle, as long as they were in such an area, they could switch positions. However, the switched out character would be in a cooled down state. Even with health or mana recovery equipment, the character would not be able to recover until he was switched back in onto the field.

Han Wenqing and Desert Dust had already been switched in, but he still hadn’t arrived yet. Zhang Xinjie glanced at the map and discovered that the two sides were fighting in an area a distance away from any exchange area. No matter where Han Wenqing chose, it would require some time for him to arrive.

Wang Jiexi and he weren’t in any danger. Deng Fusheng was being suppressed, but he could hang on. However, Wu Yuce couldn’t wait. Against an attack on all sides like this, it wouldn’t even take 30 seconds for him to die, let alone that in a 2v1.

He originally thought that he’d be able to rush over and heal him, but as it turned out, that plan wasn’t going to work. Zhang Xinjie was growing very worried. What type of opponent was he up against? Yu Wenzhou wasn’t trying to do damage to Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock, his goal was simply to stop him from aiding his ally. This was something completely within Yu Wenzhou’s capabilities.

If this situation continued, Team Two would be in a deep trouble. Zhang Xinjie saw that dragging it on wasn’t an option. The other three also realized this, but the only person who could do something was Wang Jiexi.

Neither Wang Jiexi nor Huang Shaotian could find an advantage. Once Wang Jiexi saw that his team was in a very bad predicament, continuing to fight with his chatterbox was a complete waste of time.

He turned his broom around and Vaccaria flew off. He didn’t try and save Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost and instead went to the aid of Zhang Xinjie.

This decision made Zhang Xinjie very pleased. Wang Xinjie flew over and threw down a Lava Flask, surrounding Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar in sea of flames. Vaccaria chased after him and began attacking randomly. This sort of tactic could be considered Yu Wenzhou’s greatest bane. He could see what Wang Jiexi was trying to do and he knew what he was going to do, but no matter how well he understood it, he wasn’t able to respond. In this type of situation, Yu Wenzhou could only let out a bitter laugh as he ran for his life.

Huang Shaotian naturally understood that his team’s captain would suffer greatly against Wang Jiexi, so he hurried over to save him. But then, Wang Jiexi completely abandoned him as his Vaccaria flew around the skies like an arrow, not only messing with Blue Rain’s two players, but also randomly throwing magic and items at Zhou Zekai, Chu Yunxiu, and Su Mucheng.

In terms of damage and threat, it did very little. But similar to Zhou Zekai’s initial Random Firing, Wang Jiexi’s sudden eruption instantly threw Team One into disorder. Deng Fusheng took advantage of this moment to group up with Zhang Xinjie. Knight and Cleric, one defense one support, would have trouble killing someone, but would also be very difficult to kill. A very disgusting combo.

The almost dead Wu Yuce suddenly received support. His spirit immediately rose and tried to find a chance to regroup with Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric.

However, to his surprise, Chu Yunxiu suddenly displayed an unprecedented toughness. After Wang Jiexi resolved the other teammates’ situations, he focused his attention on messing with the two female players. But Chu Yunxiu didn’t back away. Instead, she shot forward with her defenceless Elementalist and actually planned on taking the incoming damage in order to blast apart Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost once and for all!

Chapter 341 – Ferocious Tiger Flurry

Wang Jiexi’s play style was both flashy and quick. On the other hand, most Elementalist spells required a long cast time. Even if you didn’t dodge his attacks, using magic to attack wouldn’t be easy.

However, Chu Yunxiu wasn’t the only person who was fighting. Su Mucheng served as her helper. Seeing that Chu Yunxiu was intent on charging forward, she immediately began firing back ferociously. Artillery shells soared through the air, trying to force Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria to retreat.

Chu Yunxiu seized this opportunity. As long as the attacks that reached her didn’t interrupt her cast time, she wouldn’t need to care about them. A long chain of spells fired towards Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost.

Ice, Fire, Light, Dark elemental spells. Some were main skills Chu Yunxiu’s Windy Rain chose to learn, while others were only learned for use when stalling for cooldowns. Right now, she was using all of them, creating a magic explosion that could flatten the lands. Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost didn’t have much health left in the first place, so when he saw Chu Yunxiu’s map bomb, he immediately felt a sudden surge of despair. On his team, Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric Immovable Rock had hastily run over to rescue him, but in the end, he was one step too late and Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost died under who knew which spell. After a short moment, Carved Ghost’s name faded away from the team list.

Glory Alliance’s famous Ghostblade duo had fallen. Now, Team Two only had three players remaining in battle: Wang Jiexi, Deng Fusheng, Zhang Xinjie.

It had been said that these three player’s classes comprised of the classic Iron Triangle formation with their Tank, Mage, and Cleric. It was true that this type of formation was incredible in PvE, but it was also a very balanced formation in PvP. However, they were unfortunately in a 3v5 situation. Even with this formation, perhaps only a miracle could save them.

The pros wouldn’t give up so easily though.

Team One’s biggest weakness was that they had no heals. Chu Yunxiu’s Windy Rain had forcefully pushed forward to kill off Carved Ghost and she currently had the least health on her team. Wang Jiexi could only watch as Carved Ghost died in battle and switched his focus onto Windy Rain.

Chu Yunxiu had just used everything she had, so the majority of her spells were on cooldown. Her health pool and defense were low as well. If this was a 1v1 duel, then Wang Jiexi could probably take her down in less than 30 seconds. Unfortunately, she still had four teammates. If Wang Jiexi wanted to attack her, how would Team One’s other four players not notice? As a result, Team One immediately rushed forward in order to save her. For a brief moment, it was as if Deng Fusheng and Zhang Xinjie had been forgotten.

Wang Jiexi’s awareness and decision-making were extremely good. When he saw that Team One was coming to defend Chu Yunxiu, he immediately made the decision to give up on the easiest target to kill and switched to Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain as his main focus. Vaccaria swept his broom and shot forward, directly at Dancing Rain.

Su Mucheng didn’t react slowly either. She lifted her hands and fired Anti-Tank Missiles towards Vaccaria. Suddenly, a shadow jumped out. To her surprise, it was Deng Fusheng’s Knight Angelica. He didn’t have enough time to interrupt Su Mucheng’s attack, so he leaped into the air with his shield raised. The artillery barrage was dispersed as he took the attack for Vaccaria.

Deng Fusheng and Wang Jiexi were partners on the same team. This sort of coordination was already like an instinct to them.

Vaccaria blocked the Anti-Tank Missiles and, as soon as his body began falling back to the ground, Vaccaria flew past him. In mid-air, he simultaneously leaped off his broom, while doing a Sweep. Su Mucheng didn’t have time to dodge and was launched into the air by Vaccaria.

Shua shua shua shua!

In the air, Vaccaria’s Broom danced in the air. The arcs left by his broom looked as if the broom were cleaning up the air. Vaccaria’s Broom wasn’t any ordinary item. It was also a famous Silver Weapon with quite a haughty name too, “Stardust Extermination.” Truthfully, his attacks on Dancing Rain were only normal attacks, but the dazzling visual effects looked as if he were using all sorts of skills. Every time his broom swept, it seemed as if the stars were being shattered into glittering dust.

Team One’s other teammates weren’t just going to stand around and watch. They immediately pounced forward to rescue her. Zhou Zekai had already begun firing, but Deng Fusheng once again leaped up to defend. As the bullets were being blocked, Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock didn’t stand still either. He healed and also cast Sacred Fire type skills to restrict the wolf-like pursuers.

With just this, it wouldn’t be enough to block these four Gods, but the battle dragged on……

“He should be here soon……” Zhang Xinjie thought to himself.

It wasn’t a coincidence that Team One had intentionally chosen this place to fight in Team Two’s dead angles. Team One had the ability to see the projection though and they noticed that Team Two’s reserve player had finally arrived.

“Careful!” Yu Wenzhou warned. He saw that Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was approaching from a rooftop behind them.

As soon as his warning fell, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust leapt over the rooftop. As he landed, his left fist extended out in front of him, while his right fist was next to his waist as if it were storing energy.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!!!

As soon as they saw his stance, they immediately knew what Desert Dust was about to do.

Striker Level 70 Skill: Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

His fist shot forward and the strong wind surged into a tiger’s roar as a blurry image of a tiger appeared behind him. His punch exploded towards the right shoulder of Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

Yu Wenzhou had known what Han Wenqing was going to do. Even though his hands were slow, it wasn’t so slow that there was nothing he could do. When he punch exploded forward, Yu Wenzhou was able to roll backwards, allowing Swoksaar to dodge it.

However, Ferocious Tiger Flurry didn’t end with just a single punch. Desert Dust landed on the ground and shot forward like a shooting star. His strikes came out from every direction, trapping Team One in his flurry of fists, especially Swoksaar who was in the middle of it all. This sort of chain attack was very difficult for Yu Wenzhou to deal with. After a few exchanges, his methods were blown apart as Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust continued to attack unceasingly.

“Bang!!!”

Amidst the Ferocious Tiger Flurry, a clear bang like a dragon’s roar sounded out. A blade light flashed like thunder, ripping apart the storm, slicing towards Desert Dust.

“OH!!!!” The stadium erupted into cries of astonishment. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had finally acted. This was also a Blade Master high level skill: Formless Phantom Blade!

The blade light intersected. The flurry of fists howled!

Han Wenqing couldn’t ignore it. He immediately turned the direction of his Ferocious Tiger Flurry to directly meet with Formless Phantom Blade head on. This was his favorite fighting style.

They were both Level 70 skills. It was impossible to say which one was stronger or weaker. It all depended on how the players wielded them.

One was a Sword Saint. The other a King of Fighting. No matter if it was player or character, they both stood at the top of Glory.

Huang Shaotian was at his prime. On the other hand, Han Wenqing was one of the oldest players there. Even if he refused to admit it, he knew that he no longer had the same energy as he did during his prime. He could only rely on his stubborn determination and his everlasting desire for victory to push him forward now. Even if this was the All Star Competition, Han Wenqing’s drive burned as strong as ever. Against such an opponent, Huang Shaotian was clearly feeling enormous pressure. At the very least, he didn’t have time to do any trash talk word bubble attacks.

In the end, the two sides were equal and neither could gain an advantage over the other. However, these types of skills didn’t last forever. Ferocious Tiger Flurry had exploded out first, while Formless Phantom Blade had come after. In any case, Ferocious Tiger Flurry would certainly stop first and at that moment…….

That moment came in the blink of an eye. Ferocious Tiger Flurry’s final fist was a fierce punch from his right hand, but Huang Shaotian had been waiting for this moment. He gently leaped backwards and dodged outside of the attack’s range. His blade flashed like lightning and Formless Phantom Blade continued to slice forward.

This was the scariest part about Huang Shaotian!

His ability to seize an opportunity was what made him tower above others at the peak of Glory. Even for Han Wenqing, there was no way of dodging it. His Ferocious Tiger Flurry was in its ending animation. No matter how exceptional one’s mechanics were or how determined one was, there was no way one could change how the system worked.

However, this wasn’t a 1v1 duel. This was a team battle!

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain stepped forward and his blade thrust out, but a field of white flames suddenly erupted from in front of him. This step forward had to be made. When he had dodged Ferocious Tiger Flurry’s final strike, he had to jump away one step. If he didn’t step forward, then his attack wouldn’t have hit.

By the time Huang Shaotian saw the flames, it was already too late. Due to the nature of the chain skill, his hands were working faster than his mind was. When he realized he needed to get away, his Troubling Rain had already rushed forward.

Sacred Fire.

The Sacred Fire from Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric, Immovable Rock.

The instant the Sacred Fire ignited his body, the Level 70 skill was immediately interrupted. The support Cleric had only this one pure offensive skill, which silenced the character and the player.

Even with no skills left to use, Huang Shaotian refused to let this opportunity go by. His normal attack stabbed towards Desert Dust, who was still in his ending animation. He then retreated, seeking his team’s protection temporarily.

The battle was now a 5v4.

Team One had the numbers advantage, but Chu Yunxiu’s Windy Rain had lost a lot of health and had no way of recover it. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain was still being burned by Sacred Fire and wouldn’t be able to use skills for three seconds. However, even worse was Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. Han Wenqing’s sudden attack had disrupted Team One’s rescue mission. At this moment, Su Mucheng was being suppressed miserably by Wang Jiexi’s attacks and it looked as if she wasn’t going to be able to hang on for much longer.

Chapter 342 – The Violent Ladies

In the All-Star Competition, there would certainly be a shot-caller. However, when an individual chose to go on his own, the shot-caller wouldn’t forcefully stop him. After all, this was only for fun. The audience watched it for fun and most of the players wanted to have fun, too. For example, in normal matches where a win or loss mattered, risky strategies might only be employed under very careful consideration, but in the All-Star Competition, they wouldn’t give it a second thought.

Chu Yunxiu’s previous forceful maneuver was something she would very rarely do in an official match. And this time, Chu Yunxiu once again went out heroically on her own. When she saw that her good friend, Su Mucheng, was getting bullied by Wang Jiexi, she immediately mustered up her courage and abandoned the team. Her Elementalist charged forward like a brave war god in order to rescue her.

Yu Wenzhou looked at this and saw that things were starting to get messy.

He wasn’t unfamiliar with this type of scene and he didn’t really care. He was also an old God. He had participated in the All-Stars several times and had taken the responsibility of shot-caller several times as well. When the battle got heated, some players liked to fight on their own. This was something that happened every time in the All-Star match, so no one really cared.

But this time, the first one to get heated up in Team One was unexpectedly Chu Yunxiu. This was something that surprised Yu Wenzhou. The God, who was well known for breaking down at crucial moments, seemed to be having a lot of fun today.

But when he thought again more carefully, in their team composition, Chu Yunxiu really might be the only person who would run out heroically like that.

On their team, Yu Wenzhou certainly wouldn’t and Huang Shaotian was his teammate. If the shot-caller had been someone else, then he might have jumped out to go solo. But with Yu Wenzhou taking the seat, he wasn’t going to sell off his team captain’s face. As for Su Mucheng, she was someone who was accustomed to supporting and coordinating with others. In all her years of playing, she had never displayed any individual style. Besides them, Zhou Zekai’s playing was certainly dazzling, but he himself was more of the quiet and obedient type. Playing flashily was certainly his play style, but his individual personality wasn’t the show-off type.

As for Chu Yunxiu, she didn’t seem like the sort of player to do this, but compared to the rest of them, she was the most likely. And the reality showed this. She was already beginning to ignore everyone else and play on her own.

This was already almost a type of rule in the All-Star Competition. It might be someone starting off making a scene and then get more and more serious or it might be starting off serious and then slowly relaxing…….. This time, the battle started off abnormally intense. And now, someone had finally stepped out in an All-Star Competition style.

No one would complain about this. When Yu Wenzhou saw Chu Yunxiu charge forward, he immediately had the others coordinate with her. Even though this wasn’t the best choice of tactics, no one would actually argue over something like this.

Team Two immediately understood Team One’s intent. Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie and Deng Fusheng grouped together to face them. Han Wenqing was the main attacker. Deng Fusheng would defend. Zhang Xinjie would give support. It was another Iron Triangle formation and the three played exceptionally well. For a short while, they were actually able to block Team One’s four players.

“Scatter.” Yu Wenzhou said.

Facing the Iron Triangle head on wasn’t going to work. The other side had a Knight with high defense to protect and a Cleric to heal. And what did they have? They were all DPS and they could only attack. If they were hit by their opponent, then that damage would stick with them. They didn’t have any way to recover from it.

Under Yu Wenzhou’s orders, the team still followed them like before. They immediately scattered. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain continued to charge forward. On the other hand, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer circled around to their side wing, firing while heading towards Wang Jiexi. Su Mucheng was getting closer now. The only thought on Chu Yunxiu’s mind had been to rescue Su Mucheng. There was nothing to hesitate about. She directly treated the three blockers as air and rushed forward to rescue her. As for Yu Wenzhou, he was beginning to coordinate with Huang Shaotian in order to restrict the Iron Triangle.

Team Two’s three players concentrated on meeting the attack and as they were pushed back, they remained in communication with Wang Jiexi. They couldn’t let Wang Jiexi get isolated by the enemy. Right now, even though they only had four players, because they had heals, they weren’t too worried. Zhang Xinjie was a top-tier Cleric and he was extremely adept at long, drawn-out battles.

“Uh oh….. Uh oh uh oh……” Chen Guo was very worried because the player she most, most, most supported was in a very bad spot.

Chen Guo also played a Launcher, so she was very familiar with the class. Launchers possessed the highest range out of all 24 classes, but their ability in close combat was quite poor. On the other hand, Wang Jiexi’s Witch was a class that had all sorts of different attacks. Wang Jiexi also had the name ‘Magician’. Su Mucheng had nowhere to run and was being suppressed thoroughly.

“How long can I last?” Su Mucheng asked herself. Even though this was only the All-Star Competition, it wasn’t like she’d be happy if she lost. That would be too unprofessional. Su Mucheng tried hard to hang on and saw her teammates coming, especially Chu Yunxiu, who was practically not caring about anything else other than helping her to escape. But she didn’t feel much hope for the rescue. She was even feeling a bit bad because of it.

She couldn’t help but think of someone. If it was him, would she be bullied like this by Wang Jiexi?

Uh, bully……. Using that word was a bit excessive, but her current situation really did look like that. Su Mucheng couldn’t do anything about Wang Jiexi’s attacks.

It wasn’t as if she didn’t have any confidence in her teammates. Yu Wenzhou’s tactics and shot-calling wouldn’t be any weaker than Ye Xiu’s. Huang Shaotian and Zhou Zekai’s mechanics were top-tier. And when Chu Yunxiu rushed forward to rescue her, she didn’t care about anything else but the rescue……. She knew all this, but she always felt that if Ye Xiu was there, it definitely wouldn’t be the same. Even if it was only him, it definitely wouldn’t.

Su Mucheng discovered that, in the end, she wasn’t very tough.

The times when she was tough were times where she knew that even if he wasn’t beside her, he would always be supporting her. Even if the heavens collapsed, he would definitely hold it up and she would be standing in a corner, okay.

But this time……..

Su Mucheng glanced at the audience, but she didn’t see anything. However, she understood that that spot wouldn’t have anyone sitting there. He wouldn’t be coming today, let alone suddenly jumping out onto the stage, playing in the match, and fighting the opponent like yesterday.

What she wanted to happen, wouldn’t happen.

Right now, she could only rely on herself. Yu Wenzhou? Huang Shaotian? Zhou Zekai? Even Chu Yunxiu. Su Mucheng had never thought of relying on them.

She had to rely on herself.

When he left the scene, she had already made this decision. But why did she completely forget it when she saw that he wasn’t far away?

The current him wasn’t in a very good situation. If she kept on relying on him, wouldn’t she turn into a burden?

She liked to be by his side as a helper, but she didn’t want to be a burden.

It was time to rely on herself.

Su Mucheng told herself again. She glanced at her situation and then suddenly Swung her gun.

Swing was a low-level knock-up skill. The cannon in her hands would swing up at the opponent.

It hit.

Even Su Mucheng wasn’t sure if it was because she was fired up or because she had made a lucky hit, but her perception and fingers suddenly erupted.

In any case, when Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria shot towards her Dancing Rain, her Swing accurately connected with Vaccaria.

Vaccaria was immediately launched into the air. Su Mucheng’s fundamentals were solid. She followed up with a BBQ and, even for a God like Wang Jiexi, he didn’t have time to defend.

A Knee Strike hit Vaccaria, launching him even higher into the air. She then used a Gatling Gun and the chain of bullets battered Vaccaria.

This low-level skill’s damage might not do much in the overall scheme of the battle, but after using BBQ, Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria was sent far away.

Using this BBQ, Su Mucheng beautifully performed a Delivery Gun and planned to send Vaccaria all the way to the Iron Triangle formation.

This change was too sudden. Let alone others, even Su Mucheng was surprised that her move actually disrupted Wang Jiexi’s attacks.

“What’s with the two girls today? Why are they suddenly so brave all of a sudden?” Yu Wenzhou muttered, but his hands stayed as steady as ever. Seeing that the situation had changed, he immediately set up a new formation.

“Nice!” Huang Shaotian’s spirits fired up as well. He brandished his blade and rushed forward to welcome Vaccaria.

In the end, BBQ wasn’t a skill with an enforced knockdown effect. The system didn’t enforce it. As for Wang Jiexi, sending his Vaccaria over to crash into his teammates like a meat bullet simply wasn’t going to happen.

At this moment, Huang Shaotian wanted to follow up. Seeing that Wang Jiexi was about to fall, he suddenly drew his sword and used a Falling Phoenix Slash in order to knock down Vaccaria.

Wang Jiexi had seen this coming. He could still do move a bit in the air. He forced his broom to turn and his character swirled around like a snake. The broom attack of his had an extremely long range and, in an instant, it arrived before Huang Shaotian’s Falling Phoenix Slash.

Huang Shaotian was also extremely good at adapting. As soon as he saw that his attack wasn’t going to hit, he immediately changed to a Guard and was knocked back by the broom attack.

Suddenly, a pillar of light descended from the sky, enveloping Vaccaria. The pillar of light crashed to the ground and then split into six smaller pillars of light. They swept across the field and even caught Han Wenqing and the other Team Two members in it. Everyone recognized that this was the Launcher Level 70 skill “Satellite Beam”, which dealt tons of damage.

“Girls today really are quite violent, huh?” Yu Wenzhou mumbled. Without a doubt, this Satellite Beam had been executed by Su Mucheng.

Chapter 343 – Satisfying Conclusion

When this Satellite Beam came out, Team Two finally fell into disorder.

Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria had been caught directly in the middle of the beam. Let alone flying away, if he didn’t get pressed to the ground, that would have already been considered quite impressive. Furthermore, the four revolving, smaller pillars disrupted the Iron Triangle formation.

How could Huang Shaotian and Zhou Zekai miss this opportunity? They were on the same team as Su Mucheng, so they were immune to her skills. The Satellite Beam wouldn’t do anything to them. As soon as Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain landed on the ground, he used a Triple Slash to close in and make his way into the middle of the enemy team. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was even faster. He hadn’t even arrived yet and bullets were already being fired.

Their two thoughts were one and the same. They wanted to seize this opportunity to take down Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric.

Clerics weren’t good in combat. Without any support, dodging the Satellite Beam while facing the attacks from two Gods, Zhang Xinjie’s play was as meticulous as ever. But he truly wasn’t able to defend against the two of them.

At the same time, when Yu Wenzhou saw that the enemy team was in disorder, he immediately used a high-level skill. He summoned Chaotic Rain and the skies transformed into a field of chaotic, black smoke, filled with evil intent. Anyone who saw the dark purple rain fall down would immediately feel disgusted by it. This Chaotic Rain’s special effect was that there was a chance to Confuse an enemy target inside the rain. Under the status effect, the character’s movements could not be controlled, which was naturally very troublesome to deal with.

Han Wenqing had originally planned on saving Zhang Xinjie, but as soon as he saw this skill being used, he didn’t dare go up and instead, jumped out from the attack’s range. But then, with a crash, Chu Yunxiu’s Elementalist summoned several Ice Walls in a straight line. She didn’t explode them, either. She was clearly trying to block him.

Team One’s players didn’t need any shot-calling. They naturally coordinated together simply because it was too obvious what they needed to do. Their levels of tactical insight were all very high, so they all made the same decisions.

The audience’s applause never stopped. This year’s All-Star Competition simply had way too many highlights. Almost all of the all-stars had their own astonishing moments, upping the intensity with each play. And this time, Su Mucheng’s sudden gleam of light had turned into the deciding play.

For a moment, Team Two’s four players weren’t able to find a way to fight back. Against Huang Shaotian’s and Zhou Zekai’s combined efforts, Zhang Xinjie was finally unrescuable and became Team Two’s third death in this battle.

Now, the result was obvious.

Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric had originally been Team Two’s biggest advantage. Now that they were at a numbers disadvantage and without their biggest advantage, their chances of winning were very low.

Even worse, not a single player on Team One had yet to die. If they could last until the end, it would be a perfect victory, which would be quite embarrassing for Team Two’s players.

However, this was the All-Star Competition after all. At this point, if this were an official match, they would certainly continue fighting. But for this competition, they wouldn’t take it as seriously.

However, Team Two had Han Wenqing. This veteran would never cowered at any moment.

From Team One’s perspective, they didn’t want Team Two to become too embarrassed, so they charged in and recklessly fought. In the end, Team Two was finally wiped out, but Team One had also lost three characters, so there was no perfect victory.

No one bickered about the end result. Both sides had played quite garishly. Even though no other high tide appeared, the excited atmosphere was still held. When Team Two’s Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust finally fell, the applause and cheers hit its peak. Many of Team One’s fans stood up, yelling the names of the players they supported. Without a doubt, the two words “Zhou Zekai” stood out the loudest.

“Old Han, how fierce……” Yu Wenzhou muttered again. Han Wenqing had fought till the very last moment. If Team One hadn’t taken it seriously at the end, they might have been the ones wiped out.

Amidst the crowd’s applause and cheers, the twelve players came down from their booths and returned to the center, along with the other All-Stars who had played in the individual and group competition. The electronic screen displayed the final point count. Team One had obtained the victory. Team One’s fans were happy and excited. But for Team Two, even though they knew that it didn’t count for anything, it still didn’t feel good to lose.

In the end, the team representatives received interviews and Samsara’s Zhou Zekai went up once again. This was, after all, his team’s home stadium.

The questions asked in the interview were simply courtesy words: the match was amazing, the audience was great, this year’s All-Star Weekend was successful, and he hoped he could come back again next year.

With Zhou Zekai’s style, it had taken a lot of effort to get the answers out of him. It basically went like this.

Did you find the match amazing or not?

Yes.

Did you find the crowd great or not?

Great.

What did you think of this year’s All-Star Weekend?

Very successful.

What are your hopes for next time?

That I can participate.

And so on……

Once the official part of the event was over, the rest was just an event where they gave out souvenirs and there was no lack of souvenirs with the all-stars’ signatures on them. If this was in the past, Chen Guo would have risked her life to get Su Mucheng’s signature. But now? Now that she knew Ye Xiu’s identity, Chen Guo felt a sense of superiority arise. This was because she was very clear that, with her relationship with Ye Xiu, getting Su Mucheng’s signature wouldn’t be difficult at all. As a result, she didn’t feel pressed to get it.

At the same time, her relationship with Ye Xiu also made it difficult for them to get out of the stadium. They were unexpectedly ambushed by a mob of reporters. As soon as they saw the two of them, they took out their pens, notepads, etc. and surrounded them. They were naturally there to ask about Ye Qiu’s situation.

Chen Guo had originally thought of simply replying with “I don’t now.” But Tang Rou stopped her and actually went up to politely respond to the reporters’ questions.

After hearing Tang Rou’s replies, Chen Guo suddenly understood and sighed to herself. She had been way too careless.

Saying “I don’t know” was the same as saying “No comment” to them. She clearly knew something, it was just that she wasn’t going to say it. If she did that, the reporters would certainly begin to dig deeper.

But with Tang Rou’s replies, she didn’t say that she didn’t know anything. She simply avoided all of the important parts. The one part they did make up was that the two of them didn’t know that he was Ye Qiu in the beginning. They had only sat together with him coincidentally and got to know him, thinking that he was just a normal audience member.

This was quite believable. Let alone two normal audience members, if Ye Qiu had swaggered his way over to them, they wouldn’t have known that he was Ye Qiu, either.

Helpless, the reporters could only ask if the two had any photos with him, which they naturally didn’t. And then they asked if they could describe Ye Qiu’s appearance, which came down to Chen Guo to answer. It wasn’t because she was good at describing people, but rather it was because she was one of Ye Qiu’s fans and had seen rumors of Ye Qiu’s appearance on the internet. She simply took one of them and talked about it. As soon as they heard this, they saw that it matched with other reports in the past, so they didn’t doubt it.

By doing this, they were able to escape from the reporters. The two let out a sigh of relief. However, Tang Rou was clearly more vigilant than Chen Guo was. After escaping from their claws, she would look around from time to time to see if they had any dogs following them. Once she saw that there weren’t any of these people, she finally relaxed and returned to the hotel with Chen Guo.

Thus, the All-Star Weekend ended. At the hotel, Ye Xiu had already turned off the TV long ago, once he saw that the competition was over. When the two returned, he was sitting in front of the computer playing Glory.

Chen Guo’s excitement wouldn’t die down so quickly. Now that she knew of Ye Xiu’s identity, she would naturally want to hear a God’s opinion.

“Su Mucheng’s sudden display was the final deciding factor in the team competition.” Ye Xiu picked a comment that Chen Guo would definitely want to hear. Sure enough, Chen Guo looked pleased with herself as if she had gotten the piece of candy she had wanted. She then went to chat with Tang Rou. They had talked all the way until it was time to sleep. Then they shooed Ye Xiu out of their room and turned off the lights.

The next day, they left the hotel early in the morning in order to catch their flight back. At the airport, Chen Guo looked around to see if they would coincidentally bump into any Excellent Era players. Even though Chen Guo no longer felt good about the Club anymore, her support for Su Mucheng wouldn’t fade. As for whether she would be happy if Excellent Era lost? She still wasn’t sure about this.

She would feel bad because of Ye Xiu if she looked forward to them winning. But she would also feel bad because of Su Mucheng if she looked forward to them losing.

“Though for this season with the amount of points Excellent Era has, losing or winning doesn’t really matter, right?” On the plane, Chen Guo finally found something she could accept as a reason.

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

After a complicated period since Sun Xiang joined the team, their records have turned around for the better and they were starting to rise up on the standings. However, they were simply too far behind now. If they wanted to make a comeback and make it into the playoffs, trying hard wouldn’t be enough. The teams ahead of them would have to do poorly. Entering the playoffs was already nearly unachievable in theory. Excellent Era’s fans were already talking about the next season and what their future would be then.

On the Internet, Glory’s fans were currently focused on the discussion of this year’s All-Star Weekend. From Day One’s Rookie Challenge to Day Two’s events to Day Three’s All-Star Competition, there were simply way too many topics to talk about. When Ye Xiu and the girls returned to Happy Internet Cafe, some of the more frequent customers looked at Chen Guo and Tang Rou like they were heroes of some sort. They were all Glory fans, so they would definitely watch the All-Star Weekend. The two going onstage on the second day made them very surprised. Seeing someone they knew onstage felt quite miraculous.

Chen Guo easily accepted everyone’s respects. Even after standing eight thousand meters up above everyone, her warmth never faded and she immediately began to chat with them.

“Lady Tang, how incredible! To think that you could actually beat a pro…….” In reality, they paid greater attention to Tang Rou. Normal players weren’t as ambitious as Tang Rou. Beating a pro once was already amazing to them.

“Ha ha ha, of course there are talents in my Internet Cafe.” Chen Guo wasn’t jealous. She said it very happily. Though when she said this, she couldn’t help but glance at Ye Xiu. But Ye Xiu had already snatched a computer station and was browsing the internet, not caring about their discussion in the slightest.

Chapter 344 – Chen Guo’s Determination

After chatting happily with the customers for a good while, the crowd eventually dispersed. A few of the more clever ones, who hadn’t participated much earlier, stealthily snuck up after everyone left to talk to Chen Guo, surprising her.

These customers had noticed that Chen Guo, Tang Rou, and Ye Xiu had gone to the All-Star Competition together. When Tang Rou was in a difficult situation, God Ye Qiu, who had come out to save her, seemed to be someone Tang Rou knew. From this, it was too easy putting two and two together. Chen Guo had already understood what their intent was before they finished speaking.

Luckily, they had already experienced what it was like to be surrounded by reporters yesterday, when the All-Star Weekend ended. Even those crafty reporters had been tricked. How could these customers compare to them? Although Tang Rou did most of the work, Chen Guo had still been a part of it. Using what Tang Rou had said yesterday, she sighed together with them, lamenting their chance to meet the God. As for Ye Xiu, in her eyes, he was just her lackey.

After dealing with those customers, Chen Guo still couldn’t rest. After all, she hadn’t been in the Internet Cafe for three days and, as the owner, there were still a few matters she had to take care of. She wasn’t like Ye Xiu and Tang Rou, who could simply throw their luggage to one side after returning and immediately start playing.

To be more accurate, only Tang Rou had thrown her luggage. Ye Xiu made a beeline for the computer as soon as he had arrived. He hadn’t brought any luggage with him and went with them empty-handed. All of the toiletries he used were the ones provided by the hotel. As a result, he returned empty-handed as well. If she hadn’t seen everything with her own eyes, she wouldn’t have believed that he had just come back from a trip.

For the past three days, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou had gone on, but not for very long. Overall, not much had changed. The top guilds had taken Ye Xiu’s guides for the Level 40-43 Thousand Waves Lake Dungeon to level and compete for the records. Ye Xiu didn’t care who got the final record. After getting online, he checked his friends list to see what everyone’s levels were.

Even though the All-Star Weekend had been extremely exciting, the game had been very normal during those three days. But even if the players didn’t go watch it live at the stadium, the majority of players would still watch it through the broadcast. Because of this, the leveling speed during those three days was a bit slower.

On his friends list, those from the top guilds had all leveled to 41. As for Steamed Bun Invasion and Concealed Light, they were still pitifully climbing at Level 32 and 33! In the Christmas event, the players who hadn’t been in Sin City had been tossed far away. Even worse, Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t participated in that event whatsoever.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was doing better than Steamed Bun Invasion, though. Ye Xiu saw that he was still online, so he messaged him. However, the system informed him that it was rejected. Qiao Yifan had been in City S the entire time. There was no way he had the time to level, which meant that he had handed it over for someone to level it for him.

With his background as a pro player, Qiao Yifan didn’t need to learn and understand the game starting from zero like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. Simply getting a max-level account and slowly studying it would be the same. It was just that Qiao Yifan wanted to learn from God, which was why he made One Inch Ash. But because he missed the Christmas event opportunity, he had no choice but to find someone to level it for him. And since their levels were higher, the difference in experience was greater and it was already difficult for him to catch up.

Seeing this, Ye Xiu saw that they wouldn’t be able to play together for now. As a result, only he and Tang Rou went to dungeon together. The huge gap in levels due to the Christmas event hadn’t shrunk much during these three days. The players from the top guilds, who had always been ahead of them, pulled ahead a bit more and were now all at Thousand Waves Lake. Because of this, Sin City was very empty. There weren’t even any signs of ghosts at the dungeon entrance when the two entered.

The two of them were quite familiar with the dungeon and directly finished their three runs of the day. By the time they were done, Chen Guo finished dealing with her matters and logged into the game, as well. Ye Xiu casually glanced at her screen and saw that the first thing she did after logging in was leaving her guild.

“You’re leaving your guild?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah!” Chen Guo nodded her head.

“Excellent Dynasty?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, they’re disgusting!” Chen Guo said. Chen Guo was clearly disgusted by Club Excellent Era now. Their guild, Excellent Dynasty, no longer made her feel proud, either. She decisively left the guild without any signs of reluctance. Apart from this, she also felt worried for Su Mucheng. It was as if she thought Su Mucheng was in some sort of prison.

“Do you really need to go that far?” Ye Xiu laughed, seeing what Chen Guo was thinking.

“I’ll make my own guild.” Chen Guo said, while replying back to messages. She had been in Excellent Dynasty for a long time, so she had a lot of friends there. Her leaving the guild even before saying “hi” to them caused a lot of her friends to ask her what was going on.

“Excellent Era is rotten. I’m going to make my own guild.” Chen Guo replied in this way to everyone. Her friends who received them were confused. They were doing just fine. What did she mean Excellent Era was rotten?

“Sis, is it because of Sun Xiang?” Her friends began guessing. Sun Xiang’s performance in the All-Star Competition truly was too embarrassing. Sun Xiang losing to their rival Han Wenqing made a lot of Excellent Era’s fans unhappy. To their understanding of her, such a shameful event really was enough to make her leave impulsively.

“No!” Chen Guo concluded, “In any case, I don’t want to be in this lame guild. Who wants to join me?”

For a moment, very few replied back.

Developing a guild in the Heavenly Domain wasn’t easy. Here, the competition was crueler and fiercer. The benefits from joining a top guild like Excellent Dynasty couldn’t be compared to those on their own or those in a regular guild.

In the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds weren’t only seeking for more numbers like the new server. The qualifications needed to enter one were much higher. In order to join a top guild in the Heavenly Domain, the player needed to have a certain level of skill. Many of them cherished their status. In addition, those who joined the guild were all supporters of Excellent Era. Their guild, Excellent Dynasty, also had an emotional aspect to it. This sort of loyalty wasn’t something normal guilds had.

Plus, Chen Guo didn’t give a concrete reason to. She simply left for seemingly no reason and then just asked if they wanted to join. Of course they weren’t going to respond.

If they agreed, then that’d be too careless. If they didn’t agree, it wouldn’t be good for Chen Guo’s reputation. For a moment, they pretended they were dead as if they didn’t receive any messages. Some of them even logged out of the game.

Only her most ironclad friends replied back, wanting to know why Chen Guo wanted to do so.

These were the friends Chen Guo trusted the most in game, so she didn’t hide anything, directly revealing to them why she didn’t feel good about Excellent Era. Her friends hadn’t even replied back yet, when Ye Xiu said in surprise: “You know a lot?”

Chen Guo had told her friends about all those things she and Tang Rou had analyzed that night, the guesses they had made about Club Excellent Era. And now that Ye Xiu showed his surprise, Chen Guo turned his head to ask: “Is it like that?”

Ye Xiu forced a smile.

“Hmph!” Chen Guo’s displeasure was obviously aimed at Club Excellent Era. To her friends, these speculations were too shocking. They couldn’t accept them so easily.

“You say Ye Qiu’s condition had been declining? Did you see that Dragon Raises Its Head in the All-Star Competition?” Chen Guo asked.

“Right, he can still use Dragon Raises Its Head. Declining, my ass! It really is Excellent Era scheming!” One of Chen Guo’s diehard friends shouted. This player was also one of Ye Qiu’s loyal fans. He was able to accept it very easily like Chen Guo.

“That…… You couldn’t have made so many speculations just because of one Dragon Raises Its Head, right?” Of course, some of them were more prudent. Truthfully, this was the more logical decision. The previous player had been a brainless fan like Chen Guo and had an easier time accepting news that favored his idol.

“Hmph, there’s more. But I won’t tell you. Anyways, it’s like that. I’ve already left. I’m going to create a guild and overthrow Excellent Dynasty!” Chen Guo said.

“Ridiculous.” Ye Xiu suddenly blurted out.

Chen Guo immediately turned her head to glare at him. The determination glinting in her eyes frightened Ye Xiu. Even though Boss Chen Guo was usually all ominous towards him, Ye Xiu had never seen this sort of determination from her. Topple Excellent Dynasty? Is she serious? Truthfully, for a top guild like Excellent Dynasty, someone like Ye Xiu could cause trouble for them in the new server. But to actually topple them was something even Ye Xiu didn’t dare think of.

After all, the guild was a very important part of the Club’s business. This was because the Glory Pro Alliance and the game weren’t completely separate. No matter how good the pro players’ accounts were, they were still linked to an account card like everybody else’s. In addition, upgrading their equipment and improving their skills required in-game materials, experience, and skill points.

The creation of the guild in-game could be considered as a safeguard for the pro teams, especially for providing materials.

They might be able to set the development of the guild back like what Ye Xiu was doing in the tenth server, but if they were ever in danger of being destroyed, how could the Club just sit back and watch? When that time came, the in-game guilds would ask their pros to help and the pros would come to set things right again.

It wasn’t as if this had never happened before. Pros participating in the battles because of the competition between guilds had happened many times in Glory’s history, especially after the creation of the Heavenly Domain. After all, the Heavenly Domain was a place where all the high-level accounts gathered together.

Chapter 345 – The First Step in Development

“It’s good that you’re determined……. But your goal really is a bit impractical.” After a brief moment of shock from Chen Guo’s determination, Ye Xiu returned to his usual calm self.

“Hmph, I know that. I’m just saying that this is my goal.” Chen Guo said.

“Good luck!” Ye Xiu said.

“You! You’re still planning on coming out of retirement, right?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“When you come out of retirement, don’t tell me you’re going back to Excellent Era?”

“That’s probably not going to happen.” Ye Xiu forced a smile.

“How about forming your own team?” Chen Guo suddenly said.

“That’s actually a great idea.”

“Were you planning on doing this from the start?” Chen Guo asked.

“I’ve been thinking about it.” Ye Xiu said.

“If your goal in forming a team is to get into the Pro Alliance, then that’s going to require a lot of investment!” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Players, money to register for the Alliance, a stadium……” Chen Guo began counting with her fingers.

“Wow, you seem to understand a lot.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ve been thinking about it.” Chen Guo repeated what Ye Xiu said.

“Starting yesterday or from the day before?” Ye Xiu easily saw through her.

Chen Guo could only have thought of doing this after knowing Ye Xiu’s identity. With how much she knew, she probably learned all about it during these past two days.

“What? Is there something wrong with that?” Chen Guo didn’t feel embarrassed in the slightest.

“Aren’t you a bit impulsive?”

“Of course not.” Chen Guo said, “I’ve thought about it very carefully. It’ll still take around a year before you can come out of retirement. During that time, we can start to prepare for it.”

“That’ll require you to put up your savings.” Ye Xiu said. Chen Guo’s only property was Happy Internet Cafe. Ye Xiu had been working for there for some time, so he had an idea on the Cafe’s income. Having been in a pro team for so many years, Ye Xiu also had an idea on what a pro team needed. That wasn’t something that Chen Guo’s Internet Cafe could provide. Their initial investment would definitely require Chen Guo’s savings. As for how much the boss had, Ye Xiu didn’t know.

“You don’t need to worry about that! Right now, as the boss, I appoint you as the team captain.” Chen Guo lifted her head high.

“What? It’s been created just like that?” Ye Xiu was astonished.

“Yup. This historic moment has to be recorded. Come here. Smile.” Chen Guo suddenly took out her phone.

“Hey……” Ye Xiu didn’t have time to object. Chen Guo swiftly pressed near. Tang Rou had also snuck her head in. The camera flashed and, just like that, the photo was taken.

“Don’t worry. I won’t spread it around.” Chen Guo laughed and carefully stored the photo. Ye Xiu turned his head and stared at Tang Rou, who had suddenly snuck into the scene.

“Captain.” Tang Rou saluted.

“When did you two think of this?” Ye Xiu was speechless.

“You don’t need to worry about that.” Chen Guo said, “In short, the team’s been created. We three are the first members of the team.”

Ye Xiu looked at the two of them. After a brief moment of silence, he looked at Chen Guo: “You should be the boss…… as a player, cough……”

“I’ll just be in there until you get enough players!” Chen Guo angrily said. Ye Xiu was obviously trying to say that she simply wasn’t good enough to be a player. Chen Guo obviously knew this. Plus, with her age, there wasn’t enough time for her to get any better. In the team, she could only be the manager. As for being a player, at best, she could take it up nominally as a sort of comfort.

“Okay, now that the team’s been created, the first thing you two need to do is hurry up and level up. Then, we’ll group up in the Heavenly Domain. While you guys are doing that, I’ll create a guild and wait for you guys. Our development starts with the guild.” Chen Guo commanded in a serious tone.

“Can I ask what this team will be called?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course it’ll be called ‘Happy’.” Chen Guo replied instantly.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything and turned his head to continue playing.

“Do you have any objections?” Chen Guo asked.

“No, I just wanted to know.” Ye Xiu said. Truthfully, he didn’t care what the name was. Chen Guo’s decision to set up a team seemed to be real, but he also felt that it seemed a bit out of nowhere, so Ye Xiu didn’t bother thinking about it too much. He’ll just see how things go first before making any real decisions. In any case, it’s not like they could really do anything right now. After the days go by, he’ll see if boss Chen Guo was actually serious or not!

After talking, Chen Guo’s friends finally responded.

In the end, only one fan of Ye Qiu left Excellent Dynasty with Chen Guo. As for the others, they just laughed as if it was all a big joke.

Chen Guo wasn’t going to force them. Having one already made her feel thankful. She immediately introduced her friend to Ye Xiu.

“Forest Landscape. Battle Mage. His mechanics aren’t bad. They’re just a bit worse than mine.” Chen Guo said.

“Just a bit worse than yours…….” Ye Xiu repeated, “That tone doesn’t suit you!”

In the past, there was no way Chen Guo could bear this sort of mocking tone. But now, even though she couldn’t bear it, she had to.. because she finally knew who he was. A God looking down on her skill was completely reasonable.

As a result, Chen Guo could only take a deep breath and pretend she didn’t hear it. She continued: “Right now, it’s just us two. We can’t create a guild yet. We’ll need more people.”

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. It wasn’t easy creating a guild in the Heavenly Domain. There weren’t any new players. In order to enter the Heavenly Domain, everyone that was there had to have a certain level of mechanics and skill. Those who wanted to join a guild would have already done so back when they were in their normal server. Finding people to join a new guild in the Heavenly Domain would prove to be quite difficult.

Usually, guilds were first created in the normal server. Then, once everyone reached Level 70 and entered the Heavenly Domain, they would then create a guild in the Heavenly Domain. The two guilds would then set up a link. After that link was created, guild players that were able to enter the Heavenly Domain from the normal player server would directly join the guild with the same name.

Directly creating a guild in the Heavenly Domain would require the creator to have a certain amount of appeal or it could be achieved through spending money. For appeal, Chen Guo’s circle of friends were all from Excellent Dynasty. With Excellent Era’s backing behind Excellent Dynasty, they had who knew how much more appeal over Chen Guo’s new guild. Pro characters like One Autumn Leaf and Dancing Rain all had their names registered under Excellent Dynasty in the Heavenly Domain. Members of the guild could easily search up the entire team’s pro characters.

As for money, that was a bottomless pit. In addition, those who joined would only be there while there were still advantages, so Chen Guo didn’t want to use this method.

“Hey, can I use your name?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“As if others would believe you!” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s true.” Chen Guo thought. She didn’t have any fame, but Ye Xiu was different! If she used Ye Qiu’s name, creating a guild wouldn’t be a problem. The problem was that no one would believe her. Glory had been going on for a long time. Cheating people by lying about their identity had been done who knew how many times. If she said that she was some pro player, the only thing she’d summon would be an angry mob.

Chen Guo thought and thought, but she couldn’t come up with anything. Let alone her, even if Ye Xiu personally came out, the players would still be doubtful. This was already a type of taboo in Glory.

“Even if I created one in the normal server, it’d still be troublesome. I’m in an old server, so there aren’t many new players.” Chen Guo sighed. Her Chasing Haze was in the fifth server. It had already been several years since its creation.

“Oh! I’ve got it! You create the guild in the tenth server!” Chen Guo suddenly said.

“I create it?” Ye Xiu stared blankly.

“Yeah! Creating a guild in a new server shouldn’t be hard!” Chen Guo said.

“That’s true……” Ye Xiu said, while staring at his character. Lord Grim. With his character’s fame, creating a guild would be way too easy. His fame was simply incomparable. New servers would have a lot of young and naive new players. Players like Tang Rou, who had never touched Glory before without any knowledge of the guilds backed by pros, would only know that in the tenth server, Lord Grim was number one!

“Hurry, hurry. Hurry up and create it.” Chen Guo urged.

“Okay.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. To create a team, if they wanted to develop it into a business, then an in-game guild was a requirement. Creating a guild right now was perfect. They could take advantage of being in the new server to snatch resources. It would be their first step for their future.

As a result, Ye Xiu sent out a message in the global chat that he would be creating a guild to test out what the response would be like.

There had been a long period of peace after the Christmas event. Suddenly, Lord Grim came out with a bang and flung a heavy explosive. The global chat immediately erupted into chaos. His friends list also began flashing repeatedly.

It was currently Monday afternoon. Nearly everyone online right now on his friends list were from the top guilds. All of them sent him messages in order to pry out more information.

For these top guilds, Lord Grim creating his own guild was absolutely terrible news.

Chapter 346 – Beaten Black and Blue

Lord Grim was going to create a guild!

When the news came, the top guilds spread the word at top speed to their core circles. Those who weren’t online at that moment all received notifications through their phones. Even those who had been tucked in bed all nice and sound were immediately wide awake after hearing this news.

This wasn’t small news, especially to those who were competing for the dungeon records.

If Lord Grim actually created his own guild, he would certainly have the strength to compete with them for the dungeon records, and with Lord Grim’s fame in the tenth server, it would be extremely easy for him to create a very powerful guild. Even if the players who joined weren’t good, they would still be able to support their dungeon team.

The guilds backed by Clubs had an innate advantage. However, at the same time, they also had restrictions placed on them because of their Clubs.

This was because their guilds could be considered as the Club’s and the team’s in-game representative. These guilds had to work hard to create a perfect image for themselves. Some of their more dubious activities couldn’t be exposed to the public.

For example, their great chase after Lord Grim. That was already a fairly risky maneuver by the top guilds. During the chasing, the reason their players didn’t wear their guild names was because they didn’t want the tenth server players to see who they were. Luckily, at that time, Lord Grim’s group had just been lonely souls. Even though their maneuver hadn’t been too honest, with only a few of them, they wouldn’t be able to create any large discussion.

However, Lord Grim creating a guild was very different. If they chased Lord Grim’s team like they had done before, the rest of his guild would certainly see what was going on and know that their guilds didn’t play fair and would even resort to using such despicable methods to suppress their opponents.

In the past, against such opponents, the top guilds never directly showed their true face. They would raise a few accounts that hadn’t joined a guild yet and then have them do their dirty work. However, Lord Grim’s skill and capabilities were something everyone thoroughly understood. Even their large-scale mobilization hadn’t been as successful as they had hoped. Sending a few unorganized soldiers to bother them would only be sending them to their deaths.

“What do we do?”

Everyone was worrying over this question. Amongst these, the Three Great Guilds were having the most trouble.

Currently, the Three Great Guilds and Excellent Dynasty knew what Lord Grim’s true identity was. In addition, they had all watched the All-Star Weekend’s broadcast. Ye Xiu had used Dragon Raises Its Head, a move that Han Wenqing said could only be done by Ye Xiu, and had received widespread acknowledgement for it, but they wouldn’t have expected that Ye Xiu’s starting point for coming out of retirement would begin in the tenth server. Creating a guild would be a very heavy blow to these top guilds.

As for those slightly weaker guilds, even though they also yearned for dungeon records, it could be seen from the results that those records mainly stayed in the control of a few guilds. Lord Grim jumping in to add to the mess would definitely cause these top guilds to be filled with distraught.

In addition, they knew that Lord Grim definitely wasn’t someone that they could mess with, but for those who didn’t know Lord Grim’s identity, they all had false hopes. For example, when Misty Castle’s Hazy Mist saw that Lord Grim was interested in playing in a guild, he immediately asked him if he wanted to join theirs. But in the end, Ye Xiu politely declined. Hazy Mist had even thought that it was because his offer hadn’t been enticing enough and was pondering what to do next.

Guild like the Three Great Guilds and Excellent Dynasty, who knew the truth, completely gave up on trying to rope him in. Blue River ran to the Heavenly Domain to report to his guild leader, Changing Spring. Excellent Dynasty’s Chen Yehui, on the other hand, uneasily went looking for vice-captain Liu Hao. Herb Garden’s Plantago Seed had kept his distance after finding out Lord Grim’s identity and would only come out when there was a good opportunity. His plan was the still the same, so he didn’t say anything. Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night directly went to contact Ye Xiu.

Cold Night wanted to cry, but no tears came out. The tenth server’s pioneering turned out to be so unexpectedly difficult. This time, the person who was making things difficult for them was unbelievably strong. Cold Night already felt that he wasn’t a worthy opponent, but he still had to give it a try.

“God is going to create a guild, huh! Congratulations! Congratulations!” Even Cold Night himself felt that his greeting sounded fake. How could he have any sort of feelings of congratulation in his heart? But aside from this, he didn’t know how else to initiate a conversation.

“Thanks.” Ye Xiu replied simply. He had too many messages to attend to.

“Do you have enough manpower? If there isn’t enough, I can send over some help.” Cold Night continued with his fakeness.

“No need!” Ye Xiu replied. There was even a smiley face attached to it.

Cold Night couldn’t find any other words to say. After pondering for awhile, he decided to ask the question on his mind directly: “God, what do you plan on doing after creating your guild?”

“Ha ha, you should understand!” Ye Xiu replied.

Of course, Cold Night understood. With the subject at hand, he immediately reminded: “God, you haven’t forgotten our deal, right?”

“Of course, I remember. We won’t touch your guild’s records!”

Cold Night quickly received Lord Grim’s reply. His promise was the same as the one he had initially made. He even added the same straightforward emoticon face he had used back then.

Though when he saw this reply, Cold Night wasn’t as happy as he was that day.

Not touching their guild’s records wasn’t enough. This was because if Lord Grim didn’t provide their guild with guides, their guild would have no way of competing for the records. When that happened, even if Lord Grim wanted to touch their records, he wouldn’t be able to.

The promise they had happily received seemed like insignificant words now. At that time, it wasn’t as if they hadn’t thought about the traps that came with the promise. However, Lord Grim’s levels had always been lower than theirs. As long as they controlled the records before he got to that level, then they would be fine. They hadn’t thought that he would create dungeon guides……

Cold Night didn’t know what to say. In theory, Lord Grim hadn’t broken his promise.

Heavenly Domain.

After Blue Brook Guild’s Changing Spring heard Blue River’s news, all he could do was sigh. Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts were in a circle together. For a short while, they didn’t know what to say. The news of Lord Grim creating a guild was the same as if it were going to rain. No one could do anything to stop it. If it was just a normal expert creating a guild, they wouldn’t be as worried. However, the one creating the guild was God Ye Qiu. He had burst out during the All-Star Competition and confirmed his identity with Dragon Raises Its Head. Because of this, his purpose for creating a guild obviously wasn’t going to be simply for fun. His goal would be the same as the guilds backed by the Clubs. Competing against each other couldn’t be avoided.

“We’ll wait and see what happens before we take action!” In the end, Changing Spring could only give this suggestion.

Club Excellent Era.

This time, Chen Yehui didn’t try to reach Liu Hao by phone and instead personally went to pay him a visit.

After the All-Star Weekend, Liu Hao felt as if his heart had been stabbed. Ye Xiu’s Dragon Raises Its Head had defeated Samsara’s Du Ming. However, it had also left a deep traumatic impression on Liu Hao.

Ye Qiu was going to return! This was what many people, the pros, the media, and the fans, deciphered. And this was certainly not what Liu Hao wanted to see.

At this time of uneasiness, Chen Yehui suddenly came looking for him and deliver the news of Lord Grim creating a guild.

“Creating a guild……” Liu Hao obviously understood the relationship between a guild and a Club. Ye Qiu showed that he intended to come out of retirement. Him creating a guild would implicate: “Could he be trying to form his own team?”

“It’s possible.” Chen Yehui said.

“So he refuses to give up, huh!” Liu Hao sneered.

Chen Yehui felt a bit strange. When he entered the room, he saw that Liu Hao’s expression was somewhat gloomy, but after hearing this news, he seemed to have relaxed.

“Does he really think that he can form his own team with his own hands and expect to compete with teams like ours, who have such deep roots? It seems to me like he’s grown senile.” Liu Hao said.

“With the Alliance nowadays, it’s no longer the era where it’s possible to carry a team by yourself. Experts are flooding in. More and more god-level accounts are appearing. The competition is even fiercer than ever before. It seems to me like he’ll have trouble even finding the qualifications to enter the Alliance.” Liu Hao laughed out loud.

“So you’re saying that I don’t need to worry about him?” Chen Yehui asked.

“Yeah, but don’t completely ignore him! Continue to keep an eye out!” Liu Hao said.

“But with his new guild, our development in the tenth server will definitely face a huge obstacle.” Chen Yehui was holding less and less hope for Liu Hao. He discovered that the two were gradually growing further and further apart. The two sides were no longer concerned about the same thing. Liu Hao only felt that Ye Qiu wouldn’t be able to rise back up, but during the course of all this, their Excellent Dynasty’s development would certainly take a hit, yet it didn’t even seem like that sort of thought had come across his mind.

Chen Yehui knew that the guild’s development was his responsibility. Liu Hao had nothing to do with it. He only wanted to see, one last time, if his former ally had truly cut ties off with him.

Chapter 347 – Guild Created

Chen Yehui’s tone of voice changed, carrying more toughness and doubt. This was very different from how he usually talked with Liu Hao, who was able to tell.

Liu Hao was also someone who thought hard and he was instantly able to tell why Chen Yehui wasn’t happy. He patted Chen Yehui and smiled: “Let’s go find a place to drink. We can take our time to talk things over when we’re there.”

Liu Hao didn’t want to lose his ally. Chen Yehui understood this, so he didn’t object. Thus, the two left together.

In the game, seeing the craze brought out by Lord Grim’s announcement, the players didn’t doubt that Lord Grim’s guild might quickly be the largest in the tenth server.

After the announcement came out, quite a few players had already begun paying close attention to the guild page, waiting to see when Lord Grim’s guild would be created. However, even after the day turned dark, there was no sign of Lord Grim’s name in the new guilds list.

In order to create a guild, the guild leader would present an application and 30 players would have to respond. If the guild was created, the players who responded would naturally become the first guild members. 30 players was the minimum amount of players required to create a guild. If the guild had less than 30 players, the guild would enter a 72-hour countdown. If the amount of players stayed below 30 after these 72 hours were up, then the guild would automatically be disbanded.

Oftentimes, when guilds were created, the guild leader had to try and find some way to get 30 players to respond. However, with Lord Grim’s fame, let alone 30 players, finding 300 players to join wouldn’t be hard. What everyone was worried about was whether or not they’d be able to get a spot. This was because once thirty players joined, the guild would be automatically created and there would be no chance to respond to the application.

After this period, if they wanted to join, they would have to request the guild for an invite and wait for the guild members to approve. Usually, in a guild’s initial period, if the guild didn’t have much fame, numbers were more important; the more players, the better, but after the guild was developed, players would be filtered and quality would be more important.

However, Lord Grim’s guild wouldn’t be going according to the usual scenario. He had fame and he didn’t need numbers to create a presence for himself. He could completely skip the first step and regard quality as more important. Because of this, being able to respond as one of the first thirty players was more valuable.

Unfortunately, Lord Grim didn’t seem to show any signs of acting after making the announcement. The players were puzzled and in doubt, but at night, during the peak hours, Lord Grim sent out the application and his guild suddenly popped up on the new guilds list.

In an instant!

In just that instant, the players who found out didn’t even have time to spread the news, when the application disappeared. This was because, in that instant, thirty players had already responded and the guild was automatically created.

It was only after the announcement of the guild’s creation was made by the system that the players noticed.

Happy.

The name of the guild Lord Grim created. Players began to request invites one after the other, while trying to figure out the meaning behind the name. The name truly didn’t sound tyrannical and it didn’t sound very impressive either. No one was able to deduce the true meaning behind it. In the end, they just regarded it as an expert having a different temperament than normal players.

The attention garnered from Guild Happy made Chen Guo uncontrollably excited. In her eyes, this was an extremely impressive opening. Right now, Ye Xiu was dealing with the countless requests. Seeing the mass of names, Chen Guo only regretted that they couldn’t accept them all. The limit of guild members depended upon the guild’s level. Level one guilds could only house a maximum of 100 players.

Excluding the first thirty players who responded, only seventy spots were left. Ye Xiu bitterly searched through the endless list of requests for players he was familiar with.

Tang Rou, Steamed Bun Invasion…….. They didn’t need to be said. Apart from them, old friends like Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, and co. decisively left their Full Moon Guild and requested for an invite after knowing that “Brother Expert” had created a guild.

Cleansing Mist…… After Ye Xiu singled out the name, Chen Guo was shocked. She quickly reacted: “Is that Su Mucheng?”

‘Yeah!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Sigh……” Chen Guo hated how she couldn’t play with them in the tenth server and couldn’t help but feel envious of how Tang Rou played shoulder to shoulder and chatted every day with Su Mucheng.

“Will she join our team in the future?” Chen Guo asked.

“That depends on you. You’re the boss!”

“I don’t have the money……” Chen Guo was sad. She couldn’t afford to pay a popular player like Su Mucheng. With her status, creating a pro team was definitely risky business. It was very likely that they wouldn’t be able to last long in the Alliance and would be quickly eliminated. Though luckily, with Ye Xiu, she had a lot more confidence. If she had to manage everything herself, she knew very well that their only result would be walking out.

“Ha ha, take it slow. It’s still early.’ Ye Xiu was still laughing.

Would Su Mucheng drop down a level just to join our team? Chen Guo’s mind was in shambles. With Ye Xiu, this was a possibility. However, she felt too embarrassed to ask him to do that, so she could only silently hope.

“Okay, I’ve added everyone I know……” Ye Xiu looked at this guild member list and checked again. Everyone he knew had been added in.

The guild channel was bustling with noise. The newly gathered players seized the moment to get to know each other. Those who had gotten in by being the first to respond, but were low-level, were feeling very uneasy. Seeing the long list of high-level players in the guild, these noobs were worried that they’d immediately be kicked out.

“There’s still space. Keep on adding people!” Chen Guo saw that Ye Xiu had stopped after adding all the players he recognized.

“Don’t worry! Let’s not act impulsively. Let me see who I want in my guild.” Ye Xiu said.

“The high-level ones!” Chen Guo said.

“It’d be best to consider their classes. If my guild has a hundred Clerics, that wouldn’t be good, right?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Oh?” Chen Guo understood what Ye Xiu was thinking, “Are you thinking of having the classes in the guild work together as a team?”

“I don’t think I can get them to that level, but having a relatively good balance has its advantages.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 348 – New Players

Hearing what Ye Xiu said, Chen Guo didn’t say anything more. She simply sat there and quietly watched Ye Xiu work.

Ye Xiu made a count of the levels and classes of everyone who had joined and then began skimming over the list of invite requests.

Happy was currently a level one guild and could only have a maximum of 100 players. There were 24 classes in Glory. In addition, some classes chose different paths, so they would have a very different style. For example, for Ghostblades, Sword Demons and Phantom Demons could be considered two different types of classes. Another example would be Elementalists. They had access to Ice, Fire, Light and Dark element skills, but usually players would choose two elements to focus on. The number of variations they had were even more than Ghostblades.

These types of variations couldn’t be seen through merely by checking a character’s level and class. Thus, Ye Xiu could only consider the composition of the guild members as a whole.

After Ye Xiu was clear on the class composition the guild currently had, he began carefully accepting requests. New members continued to pour into Happy, but in the end, Ye Xiu didn’t add it to max capacity. This was because Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon and their group had just left Full Moon Guild. If they wanted to join another guild, they would have to wait five days, so Ye Xiu left them a spot.

Though for ambitious guilds, five days was enough time to level up the guild. Guild members could receive all sorts of guild quests. When they completed these quests, the guild would gain experience. When the experience reached 100%, they would level up. With every level up, the guild’s maximum capacity would increase and they would unlock more guild quests and rewards. When the guild reached level five, the guild could choose to acquire a Guardian. There were different kinds of Guardians, but the most common choice was the stat Guardian, which increased the guild players’ stats. From level five onwards, the Guardian would gain one level for every five levels the guild gained.

Players who didn’t want to be involved in guild matters would join guilds because of the stat increase from the Guardian. Top guilds also had stronger Guardians because their guild levels were higher. In the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds backed by Clubs all had their guilds at the level limit: level 100. And as a result, they had a Level 20 Guardian.

As for normal guilds, they weren’t like guilds backed by Clubs, who could easily reach the limit by taking in their fans. In addition, their members weren’t as cohesive or loyal. For these normal guilds, once their development reached a certain stage, there would always be problems popping up because of their large numbers, which would cause the guild to either crumble away or be stuck and unable to progress. Only a very small number of normal guilds were able to grow large and powerful and reach the level of those guilds backed by Clubs. However, in terms of influence, there was still no way that they could compete with the guilds backed by Clubs.

Guild Happy was just starting. The guild had a long way to go before reaching the top, although their starting point could be considered to be quite good. They were only limited by the maximum capacity set because they were still a level one guild. If not, then with Lord Grim’s fame, who knew how many players he could have gotten to join? Guild Happy’s invite request was incredibly long.

Even top guilds backed by Clubs like Herb Garden and Blue Brook Guild didn’t have that type of momentum. The entire reason the top guilds were fighting for the dungeon records were to have the sort of status Lord Grim had in the player base’s eyes. The craze brought by Guild Happy showed exactly why these dungeon records were so important to developing guilds.

Ye Xiu finished choosing the members. Right now, the around ninety players were all online and were all extremely excited to be there. The chat in the guild channel was a complete storm. The players were already beginning to get together. Some were shouting to go to the Arena, some were calling people to dungeon together, some were asking others to help them finish a difficult quest…… Ye Xiu really wanted to say something to the guild, but he was having trouble finding a good opportunity to do so.

“Hello, hello.” Ye Xiu typed. He then followed up with a giant wall of emoticons to instantly clear the screen. Everyone else’s messages disappeared. Their entire screen was filled with Lord Grim’s name as well as a bunch of random emoticons.

The guild members were shocked and immediately quieted down.

“How many of you have just started playing Glory?” Ye Xiu asked.

A bunch of replies came out and, in an instant, Ye Xiu was unable to find his question anymore. He could only make a guess based on how fast the messages were scrolling down. It was practically…… 100%.

Ye Xiu wasn’t surprised at this result.

If they were old Glory players, then in the new server pioneering stage, they probably ran over to join the top guilds, which were backed by Clubs. Joining these guilds in the new server wasn’t very hard. Or they might have been like Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon, who came to the new server together as friends and would have already decided on a guild to join beforehand.

When he made the announcement, those who were able to request an invite were the stragglers who weren’t in a guild and the probability that they were new players was very high.

Seeing all of these new players, Ye Xiu switched how he would speak.

“Our guild has been created.”

“But because it’s only Level 1, we can only have 100 players max, so a lot of players who wanted to join weren’t able to join.”

“In the guild, everyone can take guild quests. The rewards aren’t bad and, after completing one, the guild will get a certain amount of experience, helping the guild to level up.”

“Only when the guild levels up will more people be allowed in.”

“From Level 5 onwards, we can have a Guardian that’ll help increase our strength.”

Sure enough, this sort of very basic knowledge of guilds was new stuff for these new players. After hearing Ye Xiu speak, quite a few were asking where to get the quests from. For content they had never touched before, new players were always filled with curiosity. They immediately called out to each other to do the guild quests together. The enthusiasm towards the guild’s development was enough to make any guild leader shed a tear.

Chapter 349 – Rapid Growth

Getting from level one to two would always be the easiest. After about half of the guild quests in the first wave were completed, Guild Happy reached level two.

As long as a player sent a request for an invite, the player would always remain on the request list, unless the player suddenly joined a different guild, in which case the player would be automatically deleted from the request list. When the guild hit level two, Ye Xiu opened up the request list and accepted another batch of members. In the blink of an eye, Guild Happy was now an almost-two-hundred-player guild.

The second wave of players acted pretty much the same way as the first wave. After the guild leader explained the basic information about guilds, they enthusiastically ran off to start doing quests.

Level up, add……

Guild Happy rapidly developed in this way. The system would also make an announcement whenever a guild leveled up. The quick leveling only made everyone more excited, and with the endless list of requests, the guild was guaranteed to reach its maximum capacity with each level-up.

More and more players began bearing the Guild Happy tag and soon, the entire Glory continent had players rushing to do guild quests. All of those big guilds saw the scene. The system making announcements one after another made them feel extremely envious.

If the normal guilds felt envious, then what would the guilds backed by Clubs be feeling? In their eyes, Guild Happy had already become one of their competitors. Seeing their rapid development, saying that “their members all had low levels” as comforting words wouldn’t change anything. They had to take steps to do something about it.

The guilds backed by Clubs had differences, as well. For these types of difficult situations, the majority of guilds were used to waiting and seeing what the Three Great Guilds would do, but this time, the Three Great Guild showed no signs of movement.

The guilds discussed amongst themselves. They knew that Lord Grim had contested with the Three Great Guilds before. Herb Garden could be said to have gotten away lucky, while Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition had taken a severe blow. Right now, they were at the Level 40 stage. In the other servers, they were great guilds with powerful influence, but now, not only were they unable to make a name for themselves, they were struggling to defend their reputation. Their pioneering in tenth server had failed quite miserably.

The other guilds weren’t doing much better, either. This was because the momentum during the early stages had been stolen away by Lord Grim. They were only doing better than Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition. Not only were those two guilds not progressing, they were actually declining.

“Could they be scared?” Many of the guilds, who liked to see what the Three Great Guilds would do, had these sort of thoughts. However, they didn’t know that the reason the three guilds weren’t moving was precisely because they knew just how strong Lord Grim was. They couldn’t help but be cautious.

The guild leaders from the Three Great Guilds had actually already convened to discuss what to do. The three leaders weren’t the tenth server guild leaders either, but rather the real bosses of the Three Great Guilds: Blue Brook Guild’s Changing Spring, Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You, and Herb Garden’s Arisaema.

The tenth server’s pioneering had frightened these top guilds. Even worse, with them there, their statuses were nothing compared to the opponent they were facing.

“Sigh, what should we do?” Changing Spring took a random tenth server account to use and met up with the other two. They could only watch as announcement after announcement came, telling them of Guild Happy’s level-ups. Their hearts were filled with anxiety.

“Right now, dealing with Lord Grim isn’t the issue. Our issue is disrupting their guild’s growth.” Jiang You said fiercely. He really hated the guy, whether that be because of his support for his team, or because of the several defeats by Lord Grim’s hands.

“No sh*t! The biggest problem now is how are we going to disrupt their progress?” Arisaema said.

Silence. If they had a plan, they wouldn’t have had to gather together to discuss.

“Kill them and strike terror in their hearts?” Jiang You said.

“It’s useless. We can’t fight them directly. How many open accounts do you guys have in the new server? At most twenty, right? Right now, their guild already has 400 players. With the number of accounts at our disposal, what good would that do?” Changing Spring said.

“And if we do that, it’d be very easy for them to guess that it was us, no?” Arisaema said.

“What to do!” Jiang You was bitter. Since they were backed by a club, they had a reputation to maintain, which restricted them from openly attacking others without reason.

“Hm, maybe we can send some of our open accounts to other guilds and have those guilds clash with Lord Grim’s?” Arisaema said.

“Maybe it’d be better to just directly plant spies into Lord Grim’s guild and stir up trouble from within?” Jiang You said.

“How could it be that easy?” Changing Spring bitterly laughed, “Don’t forget who we’re up against. What type of tricks has he not seen before? Planting spies into Happy to stir up trouble won’t work.”

“Planting spies into other guilds to cause trouble might work, though. When Lord Grim created his guild, a lot of players may have left their guilds to join his instead. There will be a lot of guilds with open spots. Let’s consider using these guilds to cause trouble. As long as we can make Guild Happy an enemy of other guilds, we’ll have good reason to wage war on them.” Changing Spring analyzed.

“We can still send some spies over to Happy and sit there temporarily. When a conflict breaks out, they’ll stir up fire from the inside!” Jiang You said.

“Plus, with Guild Happy’s rapid development, their guild members’ egos will be inflated. If we’re lucky, we might not even have to instigate anything. Their own people might cause trouble for themselves. It’d be even better if that happened.” Arisaema said.

“Yeah, yeah, let’s have our planted spies do that!” Changing Spring said.

The three continued to talk. Their minds began to gradually open up and more and more schemes poured out. They were, after all, experienced players. The reason they were able to develop into the Three Great Guilds was partly because of their team’s strength in the Pro Alliance, but also because of these three players.

In terms of the struggles between guilds, they were absolutely the top of the top experts in the field. They could only step down gracefully against Lord Grim for the dungeon records, so they thought of plans that didn’t involve direct confrontations. After a long discussion, they created the plan and the rest was up to the guilds to carry out. The three stayed in contact, while giving orders to their guilds’ players.

On Blue Brook Guild’s side, Blue River received Changing Spring’s orders. His expression immediately darkened.

“I thought we weren’t going to compete with Lord Grim?” Blue River asked gloomily.

“That was then. This is now. He’s created a guild and has become our direct competitor. It’s not possible for us to avoid him now. Do you really think him creating a guild is just for fun?” Changing Spring said.

Blue River didn’t say anything. He understood very well. It was just that he had a fairly good relationship with Ye Xiu. He had a good impression of him. Fighting and scheming against someone who was originally his friend didn’t make him feel good.

“The Three Great Guilds are all doing the same. We’ll be in touch with other guilds, too, so just relax and do it!” Changing Spring said.

Blue River closed the message in silences. After pausing for a moment, he let out a long sigh and then began doing what he had been told to do.

His first task was to sort out all of the open accounts that weren’t in Blue Brook Guild. His second task was to begin gathering intelligence to see how many players had left their guilds due to Guild Happy’s creation. These guilds would definitely be unhappy with Lord Grim and Guild Happy, which was exactly what Changing Spring and the others wanted to take advantage of.

As for Herb Garden and Tyrannical Ambition, after receiving their orders, they all began working to carry them out, as well. At this moment, the system made another announcement: Congratulations Guild Happy for reaching Level 5.

From creating a guild to reaching Level 5, their rapid development made the other guilds want to cry.

Guild Happy was celebrating. These new Glory players didn’t really understand much about guilds, but from what their guild leader said, Level 5 seemed to be a very important level. At this level, their guild could have some sort of Guardian or whatever.

A lot of players had already gone to search what this Guardian was and they naturally yearned for it. Seeing that their guild had finally reached Level 5, everyone began waiting for the Guardian to descend.

“You can get a Guardian now.” Seeing the guild’s rapid development, Chen Guo had been watching excitedly the entire time and reminded Ye Xiu when she saw that the guild reached level 5.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

The Guardian couldn’t be obtained just by hitting Level 5. A quest had to be completed.

The quest was very simple: beat the corresponding Guardian. When the Guardian was subdued, the Guardian would give the guild its blessing.

Chapter 350 – High-Leveled Characters

The Stat Guardian was the most popular Guardian amongst players and it truly did give the best benefit to a player’s stats. It was equivalent to obtaining extra stat points, which the player could then freely choose to use.

The Stat Guardian gave eight extra stat points to players for every level it gained. At its maximum level, Level 20, it would give an additional 160 points. Its impact on a character’s strength couldn’t be ignored. Even for normal guilds, the few extra points were enough to create a noticeable difference in strength between two players with the same level and equipment.

It was because of this that very few players weren’t in a guild. Even for the pro accounts in the Pro Alliance, in game, they had to have the guild’s name tagged onto them. There were not any players that did not follow this rule. This was, of course, done for those extra stat points.

Guild Happy had reached Level 5 and completing the Guardian quest became an urgent priority.

Ye Xiu didn’t try to take on a new and original path. The Guardian he wanted was naturally the Stat Guardian. After receiving the quest, Ye Xiu immediately began to gather people.

Players who wanted to challenge the Guardian for the quest would be sent to a dungeon. Inside the dungeon, there was nothing else there but the Guardian. The dungeon limited the number of players to 20.

Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, Su Mucheng and Steamed Bun Invasion would obviously be a part of this team. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was still being leveled by someone else, so they couldn’t contact him. Seven Fields and his friends still couldn’t join Happy yet, so they couldn’t be sent into a guild dungeon. Besides them, there was Concealed Light. However, Concealed Light’s skill level in actual battle truly was extraordinarily bad. Even though Ye Xiu had helped him find some ways to practice, he had not been practicing for long, so Ye Xiu had no idea how much he had improved.

Ye Xiu didn’t know anyone else, so he chose the rest based on their class and level. When forming the base for the 20-player team, the higher the level the player had, the better.

“Huh?” Blue River suddenly gave a puzzling look.

After seeing the announcement that Happy had reached Level 5, he immediately called for the open accounts to move out and apply to enter Happy. He had even personally switched to an open account to request an invite from Happy.

The infiltration went smoothly. Not long after requesting an invite, he received a notification from Happy. And almost simultaneously, the other three open accounts also received notifications. Their infiltration had been successful as well.

Blue River immediately checked what the guild channel was chatting about and discovered that most of them were talking about the Guardian. A Level 5 Guild talking about Guardians wasn’t anything abnormal. However, soon after, he received a team invite from the guild’s leader, Lord Grim, causing him to be surprised.

Blue River didn’t know what was going on, so he chose to accept. After joining the team, he found that there wasn’t a single team, but rather two teams, in order to form a twenty-player group. From this, Blue River instantly realized what Lord Grim was planning on doing. He then saw that Blue Brook Guild’s other three open accounts had also joined the team.

One of those three players was very confused. Seeing that all four open accounts were here, he hastily messaged Blue River in surprise: “Have we been caught?”

This question caused Blue River to panic, but he quickly calmed down. He told him not to worry and then went to check the twenty-player group’s structure.

Lord Grim, Soft Mist, Cleansing Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion. These names weren’t new to Blue River. Seeing these characters, Blue River felt a large amount of pressure bearing down on him. He knew that if these players were to compete for dungeon records, no one in the tenth server could compete with them. And now, they were gathered together. Although, one good thing was that Steamed Bun Invasion seemed to be very under-leveled compared to the other first-string characters and Blue River was immediately able to figure out that it was the result of him not participating in the Christmas event. Lord Grim’s team also had a Ghostblade character. Blue River remembered that the character’s name was One Inch Ash, but he wasn’t in the team right now.

Blue River opened up the guild member list and prepared to do a search. But as soon as he opened it, he noticed the default ordering for the guild member list. The first column was by rank. The second column was by level. In Happy, apart from the guild’s leader, Lord Grim, who didn’t have a class, the ordering was done from highest level to lowest level. At the top was Lord Grim, Soft Mist and Cleansing Mist at Level 39. And beneath them were those four open accounts from Blue Brook Guild that had infiltrated Happy.

Blue River understood why they had been invited into the twenty-player group. It was because they were already the highest level characters in Happy.

This type of situation was quite good for them. A higher level meant a higher status. Even though they couldn’t enter Lord Grim’s inner circle, they were still in a higher position than those low-level players.

Blue River did a casual skim over the rest of the names and was stumped for words.

The players’ levels in Happy were unexpectedly low. The character Blue River was using and the other three open accounts were all around Level 36. And the number of guild members in this level range was extremely few in this guild of 500 players. The number of guild members above Level 35 was 19. Everyone else was below Level 35 and, near the end, there were even some Level 20 players.

Blue River was astonished. He had predicted that the average player’s level in Happy couldn’t compare to their Blue Brook Guild, but he didn’t think that there would be such a large disparity. In their Blue Brook Guild, Level 35 and above players held the majority, while players below Level 35 were the minority.

With Lord Grim’s fame in the tenth server and the craze over Happy’s founding, he had the qualifications to compare with their top guilds. But in reality, it seemed like a gathering of a bunch of Level 30 players. What was the reasoning behind this?

“Could he be trying to establish the players’ loyalty to the guild by raising them up from lower levels?” Blue River could only guess. He then opened up Happy’s list of invite requests and discovered that it wasn’t that Happy didn’t want to pick the high-level players, it was that there simply weren’t any Level 35 and above players that had signed up. Those that were above level 35 had already joined a different guild or were open accounts, similar to the one Blue River was using.

Blue River was, after all, an experienced player. After a quick analysis, he was able to quickly understand the situation.

This was because of the Christmas event disaster, as well as a type of restriction due to the top guilds. In Blue River’s eyes, Level 36 players weren’t considered high-level. Right now, if a player wanted to join Blue Brook Guild, the minimum requirement was to be Level 35. The guild members who currently weren’t Level 35 had joined the guild in the early stages, but hadn’t been able to keep up with the fast leveling speed.

However, for the rest of the tenth server, Level 36 was where players would go to Fire Forest and soon graduate to challenge Sin City. For those who hadn’t participated in the Christmas event with Lord Grim, these players were at the forefront.

If Ye Xiu hadn’t used such a valiant strategy for the Christmas event and the top guilds had only leveled the normal way in Sin City, then they would only be at Level 36 as well. These players would already be considered the elites of their guild, the top players in the tenth server.

Because of the Christmas event, such an abnormal occurrence happened. If not for that, then Level 36 would have been the level range where they should be at.

After them were the Level 36 players, who would have been amongst the highest leveled players if the elites from the top guilds hadn’t leveled with Lord Grim with the Christmas event. After the Christmas event, they leveled up once or twice more.

Slightly below those were where the majority of the players from their top guilds were at.

To put it simply, there were very few players around Level 36 in the entire tenth server. In addition, most of them were in the top guilds. As for those without guilds, those who were at this level range probably didn’t want to join a guild, so they obviously wouldn’t have thought much about Happy’s creation.

As a result, in the end, these open accounts from their top guilds, possessing the level of their normal guild members, would immediately stand out in Happy.

After understanding all of this, Blue River was suddenly taken aback after seeing the list of Level 35 and above players.

In the tenth server, there really weren’t many players around Level 36 that sought after Happy. Could it be that all of these Level 35 and above players were the same as him and were open accounts that had been sent to infiltrate Happy?

Chapter 351 – A Haze of Doubts and Suspicions

The more Blue River thought about it, the more likely it seemed.

Thinking of this, Blue River opened up his friends list and planned to search for other guild leaders. But when he saw that his friends list was empty, he stared blankly for a moment, before realizing that he was using an open account, not his Blue River account. How could he have those guys as friends on this account?

Helpless, Blue River contacted Changing Spring, who was still in the tenth server, and gave him his analysis of the situation.

“Wait!” Changing Spring gave a simple reply when the message came through.

Not long after, Changing Spring messaged again. This time, the message was even simpler: “Q!”

Blue River was startled at first, but luckily, he was familiar with Changing Spring’s typing style and understood that he wanted him to get on QQ. He tabbed out of the game and opened up QQ. He immediately received a group chat invite. When he joined, he saw that the chat group was very active. There were ten people in the room, all using their in-game IDs. There was not one that Blue River didn’t recognize.

A few more people came in after he joined. In the chatroom, there was more than one person representing each guild. Similar to their Blue Brook Guild, besides the tenth server’s guild leader, the true guild leader had also joined the group chat.

“Has everyone gotten a feel for the situation?” The first to speak was Herb Garden’s Arisaema.

“Let’s not say the account IDs. Just say how many you have inside, so we can have a clearer picture of the situation.” Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night suggested.

Seeing these two speak, Blue River could tell that the other guilds were in the same position as him. They also realized that the high-level players in Guild Happy were their players.

“We have four on our side.” Cold Night took the lead.

“Same. Four.” Blue River followed.

“Three.” Herb Garden’s Plantago Seed said.

“Two.” Samsara’s Lonely Drink was here as well. Team Samsara had high ambitions for the season. Their guild wasn’t the strongest in-game, but they were putting in great amounts of effort towards their development.

“One.”

“One.”

The other two guilds had one infiltrator.

After adding the numbers up, there were 15 all together. And right now, Guild Happy had a total of 19 Level 35 and above players. Apart from Lord Grim, Soft Mist and Cleansing Mist, there was only one high-level player that had nothing to do with them.

The chat group’s members sent out :O faces one after the other.

“If the other side hasn’t figured it out yet, then we’re in a good spot.” Herb Garden’s Plantago Seed said.

“I get what you mean.” Blue River said, “But how couldn’t he have figured this out? All of us requested for an invite after Happy reached Level 5. That other high-level player might have joined before this, but this time, with so many of us running over all of a sudden, it’d be strange if he didn’t feel something was wrong, no?”

“But look. All of us have been invited into the party. This party is clearly for challenging the Guardian, which means he’s not suspicious of us yet.” Plantago Seed said.

“That’s not necessarily true. Maybe he just wants to use us to beat the Guardian.” Blue River said.

“Then, he’ll never be able to get the Guardian.” Plantago Seed replied.

Everyone heard this and immediately understood. Plantago Seed meant that if they wanted to, they could intentionally feign that they were unable to defeat the Guardian. Even though their accounts would have some losses, these open accounts had been prepared to be sacrificed anyways, whether they succeeded or not.

“I say… Even if we don’t try for the Guardian, they’re more than good enough to beat it on their own. Losing a few times would at most damage their image a bit, which isn’t even close to what our goals are, no?” Cold Night said.

Everyone began contemplating again after hearing this. Doing things like this wouldn’t cause a lot of damage……

“But if we do things like this, it might even strengthen their trust in us.” Herb Garden’s guild leader, Arisaema, suddenly said.

“True!” Changing Spring approved, but didn’t give any reasons why.

Everyone in the group chat was an experienced player. Even though they didn’t hear the reasoning, just by thinking about it, they were able to figure out the reason.

The difficulty for the Guardian was fixed. It depended upon the guild’s level and had nothing to do with the players’ levels. If there were twenty Level 70 players, beating the Level 1 Guardian wouldn’t be difficult in the slightest. But for Level 35-39 players, they couldn’t be too careless when fighting the Level 1 Guardian.

When the level cap in Glory was Level 50, normal guilds had to gather together twenty Level 50 players in order to defeat the Guardian. It was just that as players became more and more experienced, the level requirement decreased. For guilds backed by Clubs, twenty Level 30 or so players were more than enough to defeat a Level 1 Guardian now.

But Happy was different. Apart from these moles, who harbored ill intentions, the guild could be considered to be a guild completely comprised of new players. The situation would be the same as when Glory first opened. New players weren’t good enough to beat the Guardian, so Level 35-39 players beating the Guardian would actually be a difficult task.

In order to avert Lord Grim’s suspicious and gain Lord Grim’s trust, it might be best to act like new players and get stuck on the Guardian a few times, erasing any doubts that they were experts from the top guilds.

“Not a bad idea. Let’s do that!” Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You said. Soon after, everyone agreed. In-game, the Level 35 and above characters were invited into the party. Along with Lord Grim, Soft Mist, Cleansing Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion, this put the party at exactly 20 players. At this moment, Lord Grim was telling them the strategy to defeat the Guardian and was almost done explaining.

They obviously knew the strategy. Even if they needed to, they wouldn’t listen. They had to pretend to be new players!

Chen Guo’s spirits were raised when she saw that the guild finally had a few Level 35 and above players. It was already late at night, but she didn’t want to sleep yet. Not just her, almost everyone in Guild Happy was still online. Everyone wanted to see the Guardian fall. As a result, they continued to receive guild quests, while paying attention to the announcements.

Ye Xiu finished explaining the strategy, but the party channel was completely quiet. He had no idea if they understood what he had said. When Chen Guo saw this reaction, she immediately began feeling uneasy.

She had been in other guilds, before she had joined Excellent Dynasty, and participated in the Guardian quests. She knew very well that the BOSS’s strength couldn’t be looked down on. If the party failed the challenge, all of the penalties for dying would be assumed. The cost for taking the challenge would also be wasted. This challenge required money in order to try. In addition, the success or failure of the challenge would be announced in the world chat. Failing the challenge would undoubtedly hurt the guild’s morale, as well as damage the guild’s image.

To the guilds backed by Clubs, they felt that these penalties weren’t serious enough. But in Chen Guo’s eyes, they were more than enough. Even though a God like Ye Xiu was presiding over the challenge, Chen Guo was still worried.

“Are you sure about this? Maybe it’d be better to wait until you’ve reached a higher level.” Chen Guo said.

“Relax!” Ye Xiu replied with a smile.

“Look at these slow-witted idiots. They didn’t react at all! Did they understand anything you said?” Chen Guo looked at the chat record in the party channel. It was all Ye Xiu’s messages. The others were completely silent. Chen Guo suddenly thought of something else. She stretched her neck out and asked Tang Rou: “Little Tang, how much of it did you understand?”

But as Chen Guo expected, Tang Rou was completely puzzled and she shook her head. For someone who had never seen a Guardian, Ye Xiu’s explanation for beating it was too much for her to digest.

“See! This isn’t good!” Chen Guo was worried, “These guys are all new players. They don’t understand anything you’re saying and they’re not asking either! New players who pretend they understand when they actually don’t are the scariest type. How are you guys going to beat it?”

“Don’t worry about Little Tang. Her mechanics are enough to get her through. She can learn while fighting it. There won’t be a problem.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“I wasn’t talking about her. I’m talking about those guys.” Chen Guo pointed to the names on Ye Xiu’s party list.

“Oh, these guys? They’re even less of a problem.” Ye Xiu didn’t turn his head, but the corner of his lips were clearly raised. When Chen Guo tried to look closer, the weird smile on his face had already disappeared. All that was left was his usual calm appearance.

“What’s going on?” Chen Guo felt that there was something she was missing.

“I can’t be certain that there aren’t any new players in the bunch, but it’s very unlikely that all of them are new players.” Ye Xiu grinned.

“How can you be so certain?” Chen Guo asked.

“Because of their levels!” Ye Xiu said.

“Is it really only because of their levels?’ Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“That’s not a good reason!” Chen Guo said.

“There’s an abnormality in level differences in the tenth server.” Ye Xiu said. He then shifted the subject: “You probably didn’t know that every guild backed by Clubs have a batch of open accounts, right?”

“Open accounts?”

“Accounts that haven’t joined a guild.” Ye Xiu said.

“What are those for?” Chen Guo clearly didn’t know.

“To do bad things. For example, to become undercover moles.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was startled. She had heard many stories about undercover moles.

“So you’re saying that these characters are all moles from these top guilds?” Chen Guo said.

“There were never very many Level 35 and above characters. Even rarer are those without a guild already. With so many coming out all of a sudden, besides these open accounts owned by these top guilds, there aren’t very many other possibilities.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 352 – Each With Their Own Motives

“Then if you clearly knew that these high-leveled players were spies, why did you let them join?” Chen Guo asked.

“They’ll help me beat the Guardian! Higher leveled players are always better than lower leveled players.” Ye Xiu said.

“But what if these guys don’t try on purpose?” Chen Guo couldn’t relax.

“Ha ha, even if they don’t try, they wouldn’t play too badly. If it’s too obvious that they are trying to lose, wouldn’t they be exposed? Don’t forget their identities. They’re spies. Getting exposed right after getting in just for our Guardian? That’s definitely not worth it! Spies can only be used once you know.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo didn’t know what to say. She could only look at those high-leveled characters with sympathy. They probably thought that their infiltration had been successful.

Seeing that Chen Guo wasn’t going to ask anymore questions, Ye Xiu turned his head and asked his team another question: “So that’s pretty much it. Is there anything you didn’t understand?”

“It doesn’t really matter. We’ll just do what you tell us to do!” Steamed Bun Invasion’s reply was as simple as ever.

“Got it. Got it.” The others also replied. They were trying really hard to act the part of new players.

“Good.” After seeing everyone’s response, he clicked. The originally two teams of ten players each were split into seven. Six teams had three players, while one team had two players, Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng.

“We’re going in.” Ye Xiu said and then the twenty player group was quickly sent into the Guardian’s instance dungeon.

This dungeon only had one BOSS. As soon as they entered, they saw the outline of the sleeping Guardian through the thick fog.

“Teams 1, 2, and 3 go left. Teams 4, 5, and 6, go right.” Ye Xiu ordered. Each team had an obvious number labeled onto them.

Thus, three teams went left, While the other three teams went right.

“Stop.” Ye Xiu called.

The six teams had no choice but to stop. These orders were too simple. Even if Blue River and the others were pretending to be noobs, they couldn’t make such a mistake. If they made such a mistake, they wouldn’t be noobs, they’d be idiots.

“Each side make a line. Melee classes in front. Ranged classes in the back. Maintain a 24 unit distance between each other. Do you guys know how to calculate these units? Hover your mouse over the other players and look at the coordinates shown. Then check your coordinates and calculate.” Ye Xiu patiently explained.

The spies didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. It seemed like Lord Grim really was treating them like noobs and teaching them every little detail. If they were noobs, this should have been something to be happy about. Except to these players, listening to this sort of extremely basic knowledge only made them want to cry.

“Yes, yes. Just like that. Bamboo Street, move back a tiny bit. The guy on the right, move one step to the left…….” Ye Xiu began instructing them as if he were a kindergarten teacher teaching small children.

The spies were tossing and turning from side to side. They had to continue pretending to not know anything. They couldn’t reveal that they weren’t noobs. How much time should they take to get into position? If they got into position too quickly, it’d be bad if they appeared too experienced, but if they got into position too slowly, wouldn’t they look like idiots?

They were in a knot. Some intentionally acted stupid, but their mistakes were quickly caught by Ye Xiu. After a few minutes, everyone was finally in the correct position.

“Good, no one move. Wait for my orders.” Ye Xiu said.

They were all silent. They were already impatiently thinking of how to get themselves killed by the Guardian and hurry up and get out of this dungeon.

“Pull it!” Ye Xiu sent Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist a message.

“Yessir.” Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist lifted her cannon and fired Anti-Tank Missiles.

The three Anti-Tank Missiles shot forward. The spies on both sides were jumping with joy on the inside. The battle had finally begun. Quite a few were already planning on moving forward.

“Jump back three steps!” But how could they have expected that Lord Grim would give an order all of a sudden?

This order was also extremely simple. If they made a mistake, there would be no excuses they could make. Thus, the spies had no choice but to follow the order and jump back three steps. Players, who had fought against the Stat Guardian before, were very unhappy right now. This was because they knew what these three steps back indicated…..

“Bang bang bang!”

Three cannon shots. The explosions from the Anti-Tank Missiles seemed very miniscule compared to the enormous silhouette of the Guardian. An angry roar burst out and the silhouette stood up. Just by looking at the Guardian’s bodily proportions, it was very easy to see that the Guardian and the players weren’t in the same weight class.

OW!!

Another angry roar. As if its body was weightless, the Guardian suddenly jumped out from the fog and landed in the space between the two teams. Everyone’s screens shook. This was Glory’s visual effect during an earthquake.

The dust and earth that was lifted up surged throughout the surroundings like waves. However, Ye Xiu had already ordered everyone to jump back, allowing them to dodge the shockwave.

Those who were familiar with the Guardian had wanted to act like they didn’t know what was coming. That way, they’d get swept away by the shockwave and then have the Guardian step on them with its feet to kill them, but Lord Grim had accurately predicted the distance of the shockwave. His super simple orders made it so there was no room for them to make mistakes.

“Wait for my commands before you attack!!” Ye Xiu repeated. The spies couldn’t disobey and had no choice but to sit on the sidelines like obedient children.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim swung his Thousand Chance Umbrella in front of him and began shooting.

These tiny shots made it seem like they were completely ineffective against the Guardian. However, these were just visual effects. The damage that should have been dealt was dealt. Lord Grim jumped back, continually firing. Cleansing Mist also stayed beside him and continued to fire at the Guardian.

Watching, the spies were having trouble understanding what was going on. If Lord Grim was supposed to establish the aggro, then why was the Launcher still attacking? What type of strategy was this?

As they continued to be puzzled, the Guardian rushed forward. With its gigantic body, each step traversed several units. In just a few steps, the Guardian arrived in front of two players. It lifted its foot and stepped down towards them.

Chapter 353 – Even If You Want to Die, You Can’t

The spies on the two sides were in complete silence, hoping very much that Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist had been killed by the stomp. But Lord Grim’s fame in the tenth server wasn’t baseless. If he had gotten killed so easily, then the guilds that had been crushed by him would feel even more humiliated.

Those who knew of Lord Grim’s identity, like Blue River, were already quite certain that the Launcher, Cleansing Mist, was Su Mucheng. The synergy between the two of them were considered at the peak, even in the Pro Alliance. So while others were puzzled over their strange strategy, Blue River felt sad. He knew that they were able to use strategies that many normal players were unable to do, or even hope to understand, because the gap between their skill levels was simply too large.

Sure enough, everyone’s worries, hopes and doubts were for nothing.

Amidst the earth waves caused by the Guardian’s stomp, the two characters were high up in the air. Their guns were pointed towards the ground with an Aerial Fire, allowing them to dodge the Guardian’s stomp, as well as the shockwaves brought by it.

The two characters landed behind the Guardian. Even though the Guardian wasn’t slow, its enormous body still made it slightly sluggish. Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist’s attacks in this short moment made all of the surrounding spies wide-eyed with awe. Quite a few of them gasped in admiration, although Blue River and the others, who knew his identity, were somewhat calmer.

The Guardian finished turning around. This time, he didn’t lift his foot to stomp down. He swung his arms and whirled a strong wind. But Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had been prepared. They easily avoided it and then circled around behind the Guardian again to continue attacking.

It went on like this for awhile, making everyone who was watching dumbstruck and in awe. The Guardian’s sluggishness was only relative. In reality, its movements were quite agile. But these two, with their quick fingers, turned what wasn’t supposed to be a weakness into a weakness.

The spies were in an uproar. Even though they didn’t know who was who, they still knew the ones from their own guild, so they began to discuss amongst each other.

“D*mn! Lord Grim’s way better than I thought!!”

“Who is that Launcher! She seems even better than Lord Grim!!”

“Are these guys even from the same world as us?” Even though it was somewhat exaggerated, it was quite close to the truth.

In a short moment, the spies all forgot why they were here and were only gasping in admiration at their brilliant play style. After awhile, they recalled their goal, but with where they were at right now, even if they wanted to die, they couldn’t.

However, everyone noticed that despite Lord Grim’s and Cleansing Mist’s amazing playing, beating the Guardian by themselves wasn’t possible. Even if they didn’t make any mistakes, they would eventually run out of mana. And without mana to use skills, they had no way of revolving around the Guardian like they were doing now.

The Guardian was set up for 20 players to kill. Just from this, it was easy to see that it was much stronger than a BOSS from a five-player dungeon. No matter how exceptional they were at lasting a long time, it wasn’t possible to completely finish the dungeon with just two players. Furthermore, these two’s attack tempos were very quick. Their mana consumption was certainly more than ordinary, so it would be even more difficult to endure for so long.

This battle required everyone’s strength. Thinking of this, the spies calmed down. These two really were incredible. But even so, their goals could still be reached. No matter what happened, as long as they joined the battle, then finding an opportunity to kill themselves should be easy, no?

They were all pretty much thinking like this. At this moment, Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist finally changed up their actions. The two characters used Aerial Fire and landed in front of the line of spies on the left side.

The Guardian chased after them. None of the spies panicked. On the contrary, they were quite hopeful. Feeling good about dying was a very rare experience.

They were all squirming with longing. As soon as the Guardian’s attack descended, it wouldn’t be good if they took the initiative to kill themselves, but they could at least pretend that their reaction speeds were too slow to survive!

Closer. Closer!

The Guardian had already reached in front of them. Just as it was about to attack the line of players, it suddenly turned around.

“Attack!” Lord Grim suddenly shouted.

The spies stared blankly as the Guardian’s back turned to face towards them. With such a large opening exposed, they had no choice but to attack. But the Guardian completely ignored them. It continued to stride forward. The spies naturally chased after it to attack. They hoped the Guardian would turn its head to look at them, but they knew that it wouldn’t.

This was because they could already see that Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist had already begun working separately. Lord Grim stood on one side, while Cleansing Mist stood on the other. Right now, the Guardian was heading towards Cleansing Mist.

Only now did the spies realize that they hadn’t known where the Guardian’s aggro was the entire time. In the beginning, Cleansing Mist had pulled the monster, but then Lord Grim had snatched it away. Afterwards, the two both jumped at the same time. When the Guardian tried to catch them, the only thing the spies could remember was that it was chasing them around. Who exactly was it going for? Impossible to tell! They couldn’t see it.

But now that they separated, it was very clear that the Guardian’s aggro was locked onto Cleansing Mist.

Right now, the aggro wasn’t in their direction. They could only chase and unleash their attacks at the Guardian’s back. But no matter what they did, the Guardian refused to turn around. Soon enough, they all became the team’s DPS and the reflection from the spies’ screens showed their depressed expressions.

Some tried to take the initiative and attempted to create an opportunity for themselves. But who would have thought that as soon as they moved forward, Lord Grim would appear in front to block them. He then gave an order: “Do not go past me.”

It was a very simple order. If they couldn’t even follow this, calling themselves a new player wouldn’t be a good enough explanation. The only explanation would be that they were idiots. It would also make it obvious that they were intentionally trying to mess things up.

Helpless, they could only obediently follow Lord Grim’s directions and attack.

“Stop!” Lord Grim shouted again. Another simple command that they couldn’t disobey. Even though some of them pretended that they hadn’t heard it and continued to attack, Lord Grim called them out by name and even messaged them personally. There was no way that they could keep pretending. And these few extra hits weren’t enough to create enough of a disturbance.

“Retreat back to your original positions.” Lord Grim said.

They could only retreat. Some wanted to pretend that they didn’t remember where they were originally and stand in the wrong spot, but they soon discovered that they weren’t able to fake it. This was because their troops weren’t completely pure.

Soft Mist, the Battle Mage from Lord Grim’s friend group, accurately stood at her original position. And then, those who stood in the wrong spot were immediately corrected by Lord Grim with Soft Mist as the reference.

The spies were very sad! This was because they saw that not long after they retreated, the Guardian unleashed a powerful skill, which would have hit them! Unfortunately, the opportunity to kill themselves passed by just like that.

The spies on the left line looked towards the other side. They watched as the Guardian ferociously charged towards that side and watched as the spies on the right side begin to think the same as them previously. Suddenly, their hearts thumped as they realized something!

Bang!!!

Just when the spies were trying to figure out what to do next, gunfire exploded onto the Guardian’s body. Lord Grim hadn’t retreated like the spies on the left line. Instead, he had continued to attack and after the barrage, the Guardian turned around.

And sure enough!!

The spies cried out in their hearts.

And then, the spies on the right line did what they had done previously. They furiously chased after and attacked the Guardian’s back with Cleansing Mist as the person they couldn’t go past. Everything was just that simple. It could be your first time playing Glory, but you had still played for around 30 levels. As long as you were a human being, there was no reason you couldn’t do such a simple task.

The spies were in complete dismay. They discovered that they really had become free laborers. With the situation they were in, there was no way they could die, unless Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist made mistakes.

However, they had already witnessed their skill. And after separating, their aggro control appeared to be even more precise. The two could actually make the Guardian run back and forth between the two teams. If the battle continued like this, the Clerics might not even need to use a Heal……

They were all frightened now. Even though on the surface, it seemed like nothing had changed, but in the chat, they were already in complete disorder.

Right now, even if they wanted to die, they couldn’t. To possess such terrifying control, just who were these two?

Chapter 354 – Firm Decision

However, without any definitive proof, thinking that a normal player in the game was a top-tier pro player exceeded their imagination, especially for the more experienced players of Glory.

Every single one of these spies were experienced veterans though, so in the end, they didn’t dare think to assume two players’ true identities.

Everyone still carried one last line of hope. After all, this sort of precise control was very demanding for the player. A single error could cause the whole situation to go amiss.

And losing control over a monster’s aggro was the main reason for a team wipe, so if something like that really did happen, then pretending to be noobs and dying would be a lot easier.

Only Blue River and the others, who knew of these two’s true identities, felt truly hopeless.

Who were these two? These were the two players that had consecutively won Best Duo in the pro scene. With that type of synergy between them, they wouldn’t deserve that title if they slipped up while dealing with an NPC.

Blue River still received messages from other spies though, who were still patiently analyzing the situation.

Lord Grim’s true identity was knowledge that only relatively high ranking members of Blue Brook Guild knew. When they faced him, they often had feelings of cowardice and fear.

These feelings had already overwhelmed Blue River. However, he couldn’t share his knowledge with them and could only watch as they patiently waited for an opportunity. He strengthened his resolve and decided that he too would hope that a miracle would occur. Correct! In Blue River’s eyes, hoping that this duo would make a mistake was the same as hoping for a miracle.

“Attack!”

“Retreat!”

“Attack!”

“Retreat!”

Those were pretty much the only words that came out of Lord Grim’s mouth. Their attacks were led by him and Cleansing Mist. Their retreats were led by Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion. The two didn’t make any mistakes. He goes, then she goes. Everyone had already gotten used to the routine. Making a mistake now would be extremely embarrassing.

Miracle. A miracle is a highly improbable event.

Blue River was hoping for a miracle, but the majority of the spies held a normal attitude. In their eyes, it would be a miracle if the two didn’t make a mistake.

And the result.

The Guardian’s health continued to drop. Those who were hoping for a miracle didn’t receive one. Those who were afraid of a miracle, watched as the miracle began to unfold.

The spies no longer had the time to continue waiting for the two to make mistakes and began to employ more active approaches. They would go all out in order to force the Guardian’s aggro to go out of control. The spies who tried to do this were initially afraid of arousing Lord Grim’s suspicions because of their unrestrained attacks, but in the end, none of them were called out for it. As a result, all of the spies began to think along the same line: don’t worry about aggro, just put out as much damage as possible.

However, Lord Grim’s and Cleansing Mist’s aggro control wasn’t disrupted. The two continued to pull the Guardian back and forth. The spies discovered that their unrestrained damage dealing only increased the speed at which the Guardian was dying.

Not one spy there wanted that to happen. Seeing that their method wasn’t working, they immediately abandoned it. Attacking resolutely wasn’t good. Attacking too slowly would arouse Lord Grim’s suspicions. The bunch of spies were having great difficulty figuring out what to do. With none of their schemes working, they attempted to do something again. Finally, after seeing that the battle was coming to a close and Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist didn’t look to be making any mistakes any time soon, the spies from the top guilds were now discussing in private and reporting their situation to their higher ups.

Blue River also noticed that their QQ group chat had gone into a huge commotion. With the battle shifting from one side to the other, he had the time to look over at the chat occasionally.

He hastily skimmed over it, but didn’t see anything substantial. Though in game, he received a message and the group chat quickly came to a conclusion.

The notification explained that there were already so many spies. Sacrificing one or two wouldn’t be a problem, but they had to break Guild Happy’s momentum and have the tenth server see that Lord Grim’s guild could also encounter problems.

As for the plan itself, they had to pick which spies to sacrifice, in order to intentionally mess up the situation and create a chance for a team to wipe.

In the end, because Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition had four spies inside the guild, the two guilds would sacrifice one spy each. After receiving the message, Blue River told the other three spies, but who would have thought that the three would fight over who would be sacrificed? As the guild leader, Blue River naturally had his own pride, so he didn’t join his subordinates in fighting for the spot. Plus, he knew that he was only temporarily using this account. Two people were not allowed to use the same account at once. He still had to take care of his main account. What guild leader would personally become a spy?

In the end, Blue Brook Guild rolled a die to see who would be the sacrifice. Tyrannical Ambition pretty much did the same to choose their sacrifice as well.They then communicated with their higher ups. The order came down to immediately begin!

There wasn’t much time left. Under the gazes of envy from the other spies, the two sacrifices began to wreak havoc. Even though being a spy in game wasn’t as thrilling as in real life, apart from a few abnormal people, most people didn’t like doing this type of thing. Being a spy meant becoming friends with someone and then selling them out. Whether it was for justice or not, doing it always felt bad.

The two sacrifice just happened to be on the same side, and since the two sides took turns attacking, this allowed them to work together to attempt to disrupt the flow. It just happened that their team was chasing after the Guardian and attacking right now. The two confirmed the command and they no longer hesitated. Anything Ye Xiu told them not to do, they would immediately do. The first thing they had to do was pass the line that Ye Xiu told them not to pass.

Amidst the spies’ hopeful gazes, they suddenly heard two system notifications. Two guild notifications popped up in their guild chat.

Player More Seasoning has been kicked out from the guild by guild leader Lord Grim.

Player Clearly Smooth has been kicked out from the guild by guild leader Lord Grim.

The spies’ attacks clearly turned sluggish all of a sudden. They almost completely stopped attacking.

The decision had been too decisive.

More Seasoning and Clear Smooth had only passed Lord Grim by one unit, but Lord Grim didn’t even attempt to ask what was going on and directly kicked them out of the guild……

The Guardian challenge could only be done by guild members. With them being kicked out from the guild, the two were immediately kicked from the dungeon. They might not have died, but they had been sacrificed for nothing.

The spies calmed themselves down with great difficulty and then immediately reported the situation to the higher ups. Blue River heard the QQ group chat go into a frenzy again. The discussion seemed to be even crazier than before.

“There’s no time left……” Blue River quietly said. The Guardian was almost dead.

Blue River could see it very clearly. How could the others not know? The Guardian would be dead in a short moment and there was nothing they could do to stop it.

“Should we stop?” Another private message came. Some of the spies’ attacks had already gone sluggish, enough to make others suspicious.

“Don’t……” Blue River decided and immediately told them not to.

“There’s no point.” Blue River said.

It’s not that they didn’t know kicking players who were causing trouble would destroy their plan.

They just didn’t think that Lord Grim would be so decisive. They thought it was quite unexpected. Lord Grim always communicated with them when they made mistakes, so the two spies took advantage of this fact to use the best way to cause a ruckus. Who would have thought that as soon as they broke his rules, they’d be kicked. It was something no one expected.

Even if they chose more sacrifices, they would be decisively kicked out in the same way. Since the Guardian had so little health left, they weren’t necessary to beat it. After all, Guild Happy still had four actual members. Slowly whittling down the Guardian’s last bit of health wouldn’t be a problem.

Blue River completely gave up for an even deeper reason. He felt that if Lord Grim could be so decisive, then he might have figured out that they didn’t have good intentions long ago. So many high leveled players joining at once was already very suspicious. This was why everyone wanted to act like new players and get wiped out in order to erase any doubts.

But who could have thought that the two’s coordination would be so good, from their positioning down to the very details. With all of the orders so simple, intentionally breaking them was difficult to do. Even for More Seasoning and Clear Smooth, who had been kicked out in the very first moment, if they had been allowed to rush forward, how much harm could their betrayal do? No one had any confidence in their answer.

It was good now though. They didn’t need to worry about anything anymore. The Guardian’s health was so low and it would soon kneel to the ground.

The goal for the Guardian challenge wasn’t to kill it, but rather to make it kneel. From this acknowledgement, Guild Happy would receive the Guardian’s blessing. When the guild reached Level 10, the Guardian would be stronger and it would not submit to the guild. At that time, they would have to try the challenge again and defeat the Level 2 Guardian.

Amidst the Guardian’s wild laughter, the world and Guild Happy received an announcement, congratulating on the guild’s success in beating the Guardian and were awarded the stat Guardian’s blessing.

The guild celebrated. After understanding the strength of the Guardian’s blessing, the players had already studied what to do with their new points.

Some carefully looked at their extra points, but didn’t want to use them yet. They would put it to one side for now in case.

Some were in high spirits and immediately allocated their extra points.

Blue River and the others! They could only feel depressed, but they had to pretend they were happy. Plus, they had participated in the Guardian challenge, so they should be even happier. After being in Happy for only a day, these spies already needed to display an attitude that was completely different from how they were feeling. Luckily, this was in game. If it had been face to face, they would have already been exposed.

“Guild leader, why did two of our players suddenly get kicked out? It seemed like they were part of your team?” Someone suddenly asked.

Chapter 355 – Who’s Leaving? Who’s Staying?

As soon as someone said this, a lot of people began to wonder as well. Although, for the spies, they all froze as if they had been struck by thunder.

Who would have thought that Lord Grim would be so quick and decisive? Could he have seen through them from the start? If that were the case, then the others who had come in together with them, were in the same position that they were in.

The only difference was that those two had acted out of line and exposed themselves. As for the others, even though they didn’t put on a very good performance, they at least did as they had been told. Had they been detected by Lord Grim or not? This was what made everyone feel uneasy.

The spies once again began chatting.

They had planned on killing themselves from the very beginning. Failing the Guardian challenge was only their secondary objective. Their main objective was to pretend that they were new, inexperienced players in order to avert any suspicions towards them.

But these guys had messed this up. Under Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s lead, where it wasn’t possible to make any mistake, they all still actively looked to make mistakes. That was the complete opposite of their main objective.

The past was the past. They no longer thought about it, but then suddenly, someone raised the question, making everyone once again recall their identities and think of Lord Grim’s decisiveness at that time. It was as if cold water had been splashed on their heads and they immediately woke up.

Messages continued to be typed in the chat and the question had been lost amidst the storm. However, it would never be erased from the spies’ minds. The spies all stared intently at their screens and at the chat to see if Lord Grim would reply. They all hoped that Lord Grim wouldn’t see the question.

Lord Grim didn’t speak in the guild chat, but rather in their party chat.

“Good work everyone.” Lord Grim’s name suddenly appeared.

“It was nothing. How could that have been difficult?” The spies lied. Even though from a killing the Guardian perspective, “it was nothing” was the truth, but from the spies’ perspective, the battle had been very difficult for them.

“Then what now?” Lord Grim said.

“What now?” They didn’t understand.

“Stay or leave. It’s up to you guys :)” Lord Grim even added a smiley face.

The spies stared stupidly at their screens. They understood now. They hadn’t dispelled any of Lord Grim’s doubts. They had been compromised from the very beginning, yet even so, Lord Grim had still bravely brought them to fight the Guardian. Lord Grim had been confident because he had the skills to create a situation where it wasn’t possible for them to make a mistake.

The party chat instantly quieted down. Lord Grim didn’t dissolve the party either. For a short moment, no one said anything.

This time, even the private messages to the spies had quieted down and instead went directly to their higher ups. The QQ group chat set up by the top guilds immediately went into a frenzy again. Blue River was already distraught with anxiety and didn’t want to be involved any longer.

“This Lord Grim! How cunning!!” Samsara’s tenth server guild leader Lonely Drink hatefully spouted. This was the impression that Ye Xiu had left him since the very first time they had met and it would never die. He completely ignored the fact that their plans had been too obvious and went straight for the “It’s not our fault. Our opponent’s just too cunning!” analysis.

“These characters are useless now. There’s no point in keeping them if Lord Grim already knows.” Herb Garden’s head guild leader Arisaema said.

“But there’s one thing that everyone should know.” Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You said.

“Speak.” Blue Brook Guild’s Changing Spring typed in his usual manner, telling everyone that he was still there.

“Even though the majority of the players in the party are ours, there’s still one person who’s not with us. He’s an actual high leveled player who wanted to join Happy.” Jiang You said.

“True.” Cold Night naturally helped his boss and immediately provided proof for it from the chat logs. The proof listed the number of spies from each guild. In that 20 player team, there was actually one person who wasn’t theirs.

“What I want to know right now is whether or not some guild is hiding him from us.” Jiang You asked.

“Definitely not.” Lonely Drink said.

The other guild representatives confirmed that they weren’t hiding anything either.

“If that’s true, then I believe we can have the majority of our characters leave the guild, but have a small portion of them stay and establish a good relationship with this player. That way, if this guy really isn’t a spy, then he can be a good cover for us. If necessary, he can help vouch for us.” Jiang You said.

“Might that be…… a little bit excessive?” Arisaema said, “This time, our biggest issue was that we didn’t consider everything. Our character’s levels were clearly very high for characters of the tenth server. Lord Grim would have certainly anticipated that we would send spies into his guild. And with so many high leveled players coming in at once, how could he not be suspicious? Now that everyone’s been exposed, what’s the point in trying to continue struggling to stay in? I think it’d be better to just have everyone leave and then later on, have more suitable characters infiltrate.”

“Oh really? Then how about you guys have everyone leave first?” Jiang You said.

Arisaema was about to make the decision, when his mind suddenly spun: “Ha ha, if we’re going to leave, then everyone has to leave together. Aren’t we all in this together?”

Everyone immediately understood the hidden details.

Honestly speaking, Jiang You’s plan to win over a cover for them wasn’t necessary, but could he have intentionally put out the plan in order to get others to object?

For example, Herb Garden. After hearing Jiang You speak, he nearly had his characters leave……

Even though the spies had failed, no one knew which accounts were from which guild.

Three open accounts weren’t much to these top guilds. If they really needed to, they could sell them off. However, in the battle between guilds, no one would miss an opportunity to win an advantage. If they hadn’t noticed this detail, then later on, if they used their exposed open account again, it wouldn’t matter too much if others had found out. Even worse would be if they pretended to not find out and then set a trap.

When everyone thought about this, they immediately went silent. After a moment of silence, the most quiet speaker there, Changing Spring, unexpectedly spoke: “Who’s leaving? Who’s staying?”

Chapter 356 – Thanks for the Help

It hadn’t been easy for Changing Spring to get a word in, but as soon as he did, the group chat fell silent.

The group chat was silent, and on Guild Happy’s side, the spies were feeling exceptionally awkward.

Ye Xiu’s words had already been thrown out and they didn’t have any ideas on how to handle them. They looked towards their leaders, but their leaders hadn’t come to a decision yet, either. For now, the party hadn’t been dissolved yet. Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist and even Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were still inside. Even though the spies didn’t know what these people were doing, the spies felt like they had been exposed.

When a spy personally reveals himself and says, “I’m a spy”, that would often be his moment of glory after a successful mission. But when others pointed at him and say, “You’re a spy”, it that would be, without a doubt, one of the most awkward spots a spy could be in.

Everyone clearly understood what Lord Grim’s words meant. They had been completely found out. But even so, Lord Grim didn’t force them to leave, which meant that he had absolutely no fear of their existence within the guild. Exposed spies were of practically no value anymore. The reasoning behind it was very simple, which was why the spies were quite puzzled about why their seniors were having trouble coming to a decision. How would they know that their leaders were all trying to cheat each other in the group chat?

Blue River was an exception to this. As Blue Brook Guild’s tenth server guild leader, he was part of the group chat. Now that he was experiencing miserable feelings from both sides, he suddenly felt very tired.

He had been in the guild for a long time and had seen these types of competitions between guilds. Even when making alliances, they still had to be vigilant and approach matters cautiously. As one of the core members of the guild, he also took the same style in handling matters. It was just that after he arrived in the tenth server, the top guilds had been completely suppressed by Lord Grim the entire time. But even when matters got to this step, the top guilds still didn’t forget to fight amongst each other. It was only for a small matter like two or three open accounts, but they still felt compelled to scheme against each other. All of this made Blue River feel powerless.

“I’m staying.” Blue River suddenly typed in the group chat.

Everyone was startled.

What was that supposed to mean? Everyone was somewhat puzzled. Did that mean that Blue River was personally over there as a spy?

Even Blue River himself was somewhat puzzled. Even he himself wasn’t sure what he meant by saying, “I’m staying.”

A chat notification appeared on his QQ window. Blue River opened it and saw that it was from his guild leader, Changing Spring. The message was as simple as ever: it was a single big question mark.

“I’m tired.” Blue River also replied back simply.

The other side didn’t reply back. The group chat continued to remain silent and the spies in Happy continued to feel awkward.

This situation continued for a while, when Blue River suddenly saw a system notification. Someone had already left Guild Happy. That someone was naturally from their group of spies.

One, two, three……

Players from their party continued to leave. Blue River didn’t move. He then received another message from Changing Spring: “What do you mean by ‘I’m staying’?”

It was surprising that Changing Spring’s message contained so many words. If this was a normal situation, Blue River would have definitely gone to find a friend in the guild and laugh. But at this moment, he just wasn’t in the right mood. After a short pause, he replied, “I’ll wait and see.”

I’ll wait and see! Blue River had no way of saying how he was feeling right now, but these four words seemed to have come straight from his heart. This was what he wanted to do: to not even bother thinking about what to do and simply let nature take its course.

Blue River waited for a bit again, but he didn’t receive a reply from Changing Spring. As for their party in game, in the end, everyone had left, including the two open accounts that had gone on with Blue River. The two were supposed to take orders from Blue River, but from out of nowhere, they received orders from somewhere else and after saying bye to Blue River, they also left.

Members leaving one after the other had caused quite a shock to Guild Happy. After they found out that the players who had left were all high-level players that had joined to kill the Guardian, they were all very puzzled and were asking around in the guild chat.

“It’s nothing!” Ye Xiu added a smiley face.

“They were friends that had joined temporarily to help us beat the Guardian.” Ye Xiu explained to the guild members.

“Oh!” Everyone suddenly understood.

“Guild leader, you’re so amazing! You know so many high-level players!” Some of the guild members were already taking this opportunity to flatter their guild leader. Without a doubt, in their eyes, Level 36 players were at a high level and to have so many high-level friends was certainly something praiseworthy.

“Hah, that’s nothing. Our guild leader’s level is even higher than theirs.” Someone disdained and switched to a different angle to flatter Ye Xiu.

The guild chat returned to its harmonious state. The high-level characters had left the guild and no disturbances appeared. Only one person was very confused: “What? I’m not…….”

Only six players remained of the original twenty in the party. Apart from Ye Xiu’s group of friends, there was Blue River and that very confused brother.

Blue River understood him well. This was because he knew that he wasn’t a spy from their guild. He obviously wouldn’t have understood what Lord Grim meant previously and had no idea that Lord Grim had glossed over the fact that they were all spies.

Should he do the same and pretend he was confused?

The thought crossed Blue River’s mind. He then discovered that this was what Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You had proposed. It was just that the others had considered it as unnecessary. Did he unknowingly walk along this path?

Blue River wanted to let nature take its course. But when things came to head, he found out that he still had to use his brain. Just like now. It’d be weird if he didn’t say something! Those who didn’t know what was going on should be puzzled like that other brother. He should do the same! Although, Blue River really felt too lazy to pretend any longer.

Whatever! In the end, Blue River really was too lazy and so he didn’t say anything. He took his account, added the extra points from the level one Guardian and then left the party to level.

Right now, he didn’t know what he wanted to do. It was just that he didn’t have any interest right now in being a spy and making a name for himself with this open account in Guild Happy. He knew that, right now, he didn’t want to touch his Blue River account. The one that represented their Blue Brook Guild.

“Oh? There’s still two people left. Were these two sent by the guilds?” Chen Guo saw that after beating the Guardian, almost all of the high-level characters left. Only these two remained.

“How would I know? I’m not God.” Ye Xiu said.

“This one seems like he isn’t fake, but where’d he run off to? What is he planning on doing?” Chen Guo commented on the two characters.

Ye Xiu shook his head.

“You’re really shameless though. You actually used spies from other guilds to help you in beating the Guardian.” Chen Guo said.

“It’s fine! It’s fine!” Ye Xiu said, while using his mouse to click on a few names on his friends list.

“Who are these guys?” Chen Guo asked.

“Herb Garden, Tyrannical Ambition, Blue Brook Guild, etc. Their tenth server’s guild leaders.” Ye Xiu introduced them to Chen Guo. Chen Guo knew these guilds well in the Heavenly Domain, but she didn’t know anything about them in the tenth server.

“Though with your strategy, you’d still be fine even if they weren’t there.” Chen Guo said.

“No way. Did you see my character after beating the Guardian?” Ye Xiu said.

“Hm?”

“I was almost out of mana!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah?” Chen Guo seemed to have figured something out.

“Without these high-level characters, this strategy wouldn’t have worked. My mana wouldn’t be enough to whittle down the Guardian’s health the entire way.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo understood now. To others, it just looked like the other party members just needed to put out damage. But if their damage output wasn’t high enough and the battle dragged on for too long, the two characters, who controlled the aggro, would have run out of mana and been unable to continue.

“Then… If you didn’t have these guys, how would you have done it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Uh…… Then, we’d have had to wait until we got to a higher level.”

“So you’re saying that thanks to these spies, you were able to beat the level one Guardian?”

“Basically!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Even though it feels very shameless, it…….. Feels quite amazing! Were any of them from Excellent Dynasty?” Chen Guo said.

“Maybe you can go across the street to ask?” Ye Xiu said.

“I really want to.” Chen Guo nodded her head honestly.

“Ha ha ha. Forget about it. A casual thanks is good enough.” Ye Xiu said. He clicked on a few names from his friends list and sent them his sincere thanks. Chen Guo could already imagine how these guild leaders would feel when they received the message.

“F*ck your sister!”

And just like Chen Guo expected. Cold Night, Plantago Seed, Lonely Drink and the other guild leaders went insane after receiving these messages. The spies they had sent out had become laborers for their enemy. In addition, Lord Grim’s words didn’t mention any spies. He actually regarded them as helpers that the top guilds had kindly sent to help him. People who didn’t understand the situation wouldn’t find any problems with Lord Grim’s thanks. Only the top guilds and their crafty players would feel even more furious over his thanks.

“LORD GRIM!!”

That night, players from all over the place furiously cursed his name.

Chapter 357 – A Lone Log Can’t Prop Up a Tottering Building

The event with the Guardian and spies had come to an end. On the surface, Ye Xiu didn’t seem to care too much about the remaining two players in the guild, but in his heart, he still paid a lot of attention to them. A single outstanding spy was enough to destroy a guild. Before a guild was backed by a Club, they would be extremely weak. Sometimes, what would seem like a very trivial matter could cause a guild to collapse, let alone, when someone had infiltrated specifically in order to destroy them.

Even though Ye Xiu didn’t say anything to the two characters that hadn’t left, he took note of their names.

This was because he still lacked a way to completely reveal all the spies in his midst. Ye Xiu also had no idea whether or not there were any spies amongst the low leveled players. Though when he had made the guild, Ye Xiu had made preparations for this, especially since his goal was to eventually form separate teams within the guild. This sort of struggle would never end. If they needed to, they might need to use these types of methods too. There wasn’t any right or wrong, just or unjust in this. This was basic strategy in a fight between guilds.

For now, Ye Xiu decided not to think about these matters and looked over the guild chat. The majority of players had gone offline to rest after seeing that the Guardian challenge had been successful. The ones who were still online were pretty much the all-nighters. There was no way they could be like the top guilds and have their accounts played on by multiple players as a type of work. These all nighters, who were willing to spend this amount of time in their lives, could very likely be their guild’s main force.

The guild chat’s discussion topic was naturally about the Guardian’s blessing that they had obtained after the completion of the Guardian challenge. Players of all kinds of classes were talking over how they should allocate these extra points. Quite a few were browsing through various guides on the web, while debating with others.

This sort of low level talk was beneath Ye Xiu, although for these noobs, Ye Xiu still felt like he should help guide them so they wouldn’t go off on the wrong path. After seeing just a few minutes of their discussion, Ye Xiu already saw several flaws in quite a few of the players’ arguments. He had no idea where these noobs found such trash guides, yet they were treating them like treasures and spreading them around.

“Hey hey, the one called Prideless!” Ye Xiu couldn’t bear it any longer and finally called out a name.

“Here!” Prideless was one of the very active players in the discussion. When he saw that he had been noticed by the guild leader and had even been called out by name, he felt extremely happy and immediately replied.

“Where’d you find that guide? It’s wrong!” Ye Xiu was quite direct, simply because the nonsense Prideless was spouting was too far off. It didn’t even seem like it was right.

“Ah?” Prideless was startled.

“Most Ghostblade skills are magic based, so adding Intelligent isn’t wrong, but whether you’re a Phantom Demon or a Sword Demon, putting points into Intelligence can’t be the only choice. Sword Demons have a few Physical Damage attacks. In addition, a lot of the time, you’ll be using normal attacks to connect combos, so adding a few points into Strength is a must. Now as for Phantom Demons, they have several skills with crowd control effects. Spirit increases the effectiveness of these crowd control skills, so Phantom Demons also need to add a few points into Spirit. The guide that you posted doesn’t even consider the basic characteristics of your class. If it’s a magic based class, then put everything into Intelligence? It’s not quite that simple!”

“Ah……” Prideless stuttered, but wasn’t able to say anything to defend himself. He was having trouble understanding what Ye Xiu was saying.

“And that Battle Mage guide……” Ye Xiu switched the topic and pointed at a different guy who was also spouting nonsense. Ye Xiu knew even more about Battle Mages. With just a few words, he had made the guy go speechless.

“There’s more! There’s no point in saving up your extra points from the Guardian’s blessing. If you add it wrongly or want to change it, you can just leave the guild and then join again.” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry when he saw that these guys were telling everyone to not randomly allocate their points. When the player left the guild, these extra points from the blessing would be automatically taken away, so they could basically reset it whenever they wanted to.

“And the team that’s going to dungeon. What type of party composition is that?! You’ll definitely die from exhaustion. Get two magic classes in there!” The more Ye Xiu looked, the more problems he discovered. Some of these players saw that their dungeon count had reset, so they immediately went and formed a party with their new guildmates, but didn’t pay attention to the party composition and just added whoever wanted to join.

There were many classes in Glory. Different matchings had different strategies for them. For different dungeons, there would always be the most efficient, safest, etc. party compositions.

For new players, being able to easily beat a dungeon was quite impressive. In Glory, every time you entered a dungeon, the dungeon count would decrease whether you succeeded or failed.

Ye Xiu had only been playing with experienced experts. Even without them, by having him in the party, they would never fail a dungeon. But for new players, dying in the dungeons was a very common occurrence. This was also one of the main reasons why the players from top guilds were so far ahead of normal players in levels.

With experts carrying the party, beating a dungeon would be much quicker and easier than having those who were studying it for their first time. Even if these dungeons all had detailed guides, if new players wanted to turn the guide into a reality, they would usually die several times trying. And every time they died, let alone not receiving the dungeon rewards, they would lose experience. With this back and forth situation, how would these experienced veterans not level faster?

In the past, Ye Xiu had only the few around him to care about. He could carry Tang Rou, Steamed Bun Invasion, or whoever else was on their team to beat any dungeon with ease, but now that he had a guild, there were several hundred members. Thus, he could only talk and talk in the guild chat and fix any problematic areas.

Ye Xiu was too preoccupied with this to do anything else and spent a good two hours talking in the guild chat. And this was when the guild only had a small number of players, yet there were still so many issues. When all five hundred players got on, what would that be like then?

Ye Xiu thought of this and felt his head go numb. Creating a guild in itself was already troublesome. This was why pro teams always had someone else specially deal with it. How could pros personally run over to do this sort of work?

Ye Xiu didn’t want to do it either, but he didn’t have anyone else to help him. Tang Rou was skilled, but she might not be any better than some of these new players in this area. Steamed Bun Invasion was more familiar with games, but letting him manage a guild? That would only happen if his head got smashed against a tree. Su Mucheng and Chen Guo could help, but because they had their own work to do, the amount of help they could offer was limited.

After thinking and thinking, Ye Xiu’s gaze stopped on the two Level 36 characters in his guild.

These two hadn’t gone offline yet. They seemed to be all nighters.

When they were fighting against the Guardian, Ye Xiu had actually been paying attention to everyone’s movements. Those cheap tricksters, who weren’t trying or weren’t following orders on purpose, couldn’t get past Ye Xiu’s experienced eyes. This was what made him even more confident that they were spies. The huge rush of high-leveled players coming in all at once wasn’t the only reason.

However, even though Ye Xiu had perceptive eyes, he had still been fighting, so there was no way he could have caught everything that they tried to do. For example, Ye Xiu couldn’t remember how these two characters performed. This was another reason why he couldn’t be sure of these two players’ identities.

“If they really are spies, could I maybe use them?” Ye Xiu pondered. Spies were always extremely loyal to their guilds and were definitely experienced Glory veterans. Even though they might not have the ability to manage a guild, Ye Xiu didn’t need such an experienced manager yet. He just hoped that they’d help him share the responsibility in guiding these noobs. This was something any Glory veteran could do.

But this assignment would be very different from the Guardian. Assigning them such a task would be the same as making them a core member of the guild. This was something that any spy would want to do. Once they entered the inner circle, they would be able to set up a reputation in the guild. If they really were spies, then it’d be very dangerous.

How should I do this? Ye Xiu quietly pondered. In the end, he clicked on the two names and requested to add them as friends.

One of them quickly accepted it, while the other didn’t respond, even though he was clearly online.

The one who didn’t respond was Blue River. Right now, he didn’t know what he was doing. He was using an open account and wandering around randomly in Glory. When he saw the notification and opened it, he was surprised to see that it was a friend request from Lord Grim.

“What’s the meaning of this?” Blue River discovered that life truly was hard. All he wanted to do was run around and daydream, but something always had to pop up.

He thought about it and then in the end, he decided he didn’t care anymore. He accepted the friend invite and then sent a message: “What’s up, guild leader?”

“You busy? If you’ve got nothing to do, why not come to the Arena and compare notes with me?” The other side responded as if they were good old friends, making Blue River surprised again.

“Could he have recognized me? No way!” Blue River mumbled and then replied: “Alright, where to?”

Chapter 358 – Getting Straight to the Point

Blue River asked as he returned back to the city from the wilderness. He headed straight for the Arena. When he found the room that Lord Grim had set up, he found that Lord Grim and the other Level 36 player were sparring.

It only looked like a battle though. After taking a closer look, he felt that calling it a “battle” would be too praiseworthy for Chicken Feather. It was a completely one sided match. With Chicken Feather’s skill, Blue River couldn’t bear to watch anymore. In his eyes, this Chicken Feather really was someone who had just started playing Glory.

And his opponent? God Ye Qiu with ten years of experience…….

Not long after Blue River joined the room, Chicken Feather fell to the ground, defeated. He even sent out a sad face emoticon afterwards. Blue River reckoned that this Chicken Feather probably couldn’t even recognize how terrifying his opponent was or perhaps even thought that he was just slightly worse. It was similar to how Tang Rou was initially. She wasn’t good enough to tell how large the skill gap was.

Ye Xiu was very disappointed too. He had fought with Chicken Feather very diligently, but after three rounds, he was already certain that this Chicken Feather truly was a new player at Glory.

A new player pretending to be an expert and an expert pretending to be a new player, it couldn’t be hidden from Ye Xiu’s experienced eyes.

“Again?” Chicken Feather had already lost three rounds in a row, but was still eager to give it another try.

“Take a rest for now! I’m going to fight with Peerless Looks for a bit and then we’ll see.” Ye Xiu said.

Peerless Looks was the ID of the account that Blue River was currently using. The class was a Blade Master. He knew Lord Grim was God Ye Qiu, so he didn’t have any hopes of beating him in a fight. He simply continued on with his “go with the flow” attitude. If Lord Grim had wanted him to fight, then he’d fight!

Blue River accepted Ye Xiu’s invite and the two entered the stage.

“Start?” Blue River asked after entering.

“Go ahead!” Ye Xiu didn’t say too much.

Blue River didn’t hesitate. At this moment, he didn’t want to ask like he was a new player. He wasn’t staying on this account in order to be a spy. He was simply using it to mess around.

His blade light flashed and Blue River began with a simple Sword Draw.

Lord Grim was taking it very seriously too. He begun moving before the blade light flashed and easily dodged the attack.

“How quick!” Blue River gasped in admiration. When he had used Sword Draw, Lord Grim had definitely been within range, but by the time his sword strike had flown out, his sword strike had missed Lord Grim by two full units. This couldn’t be done solely through his reaction speed. He had clearly predicted that Blue River would initiate with this move.

Blue River wasn’t surprised that this had happened though. He didn’t think that he had any chance of winning, so he was very relaxed. Sword Draw missing wasn’t anything to sigh about. He moved one unit to the side and then sprinted forward with a stab.

“Dong!” Lord Grim had taken out a sword and Guarded against Blue River’s attack. After Guarding, he retreated backwards. The sword in his hands shifted back into an umbrella and as he slid back, three Anti-Tank Missiles fired out with a bang.

“Too quick……” Blue River was helpless. His opponent was better than him in every way. He didn’t have any time to react to the three Anti-Tank Missiles. He tried to dodge, but he was too slow and was pushed back by the explosion from the missiles.

Blue River rolled on the floor, an experienced maneuver.

“Oh, not bad!” Lord Grim suddenly said.

What was not bad? Blue River didn’t see anything praiseworthy. Could it be because his roll had been done beautifully?

In truth, Blue River hadn’t predicted that Lord Grim would use a method to continue attacking. His roll had simply been done out of habit. Whenever he encountered a situation such as this, he would instinctively do a roll.

How could he now? This type of instant reaction made Ye Xiu feel that the person in front of him might not be a new player.

Though if he wasn’t a new player, it was very likely that he was a spy from some guild.

Ye Xiu thought this as he attacked.

Overall, against a God level player, Blue River’s situation wouldn’t be too much better than Chicken Feather. However, Blue River still had more knowledge. Even if he lost, he would at least know how and why he had lost. He wouldn’t be like that Chicken Feather, who didn’t understand the difference in the skill levels and only knew that he had somehow lost.

Not long after, Blue River was sent flying and unable to stand back up.

The first round had ended. It hadn’t even been a full minute since the match had began and Lord Grim hadn’t lost a single drop of blood yet.

Blue River felt his face burning. Even though he knew that he was up against a top God, he had still been confident that he could hit him a few times and at least prove himself to be better than that Chicken Feather, but from the looks of it, he seemed to be the same as that Chicken Feather and had gotten beaten up too. It seemed that he had overestimated himself.

“Again?” Ye Xiu asked.

Ye Xiu already felt like he had seen enough. This person definitely wasn’t a new player and was quite familiar with the Blade Master class too. Some of his moves had clearly been out of habit. In game, he would definitely be considered an expert.

But apart from that, Ye Xiu was somewhat puzzled. He had been able to see all this in a mere one minute and the reason he was able to was because this person didn’t hide anything. This was what Ye Xiu couldn’t understand. If he was a spy sent by another guild, wasn’t he afraid of being exposed? Or could he have been employing a reverse psychology tactic?

“What do you think?”

Ye Xiu was still thinking, when the other side replied.

“That’ll be it then. Let’s leave!” Ye Xiu said and left the Arena.

Blue River was baffled. Why had he been suddenly called out to play a round of PvP?

After exiting the Arena, Blue River quickly received a message from Ye Xiu: “How many years have you been playing Glory?”

“Uh, quite a few years.” Blue River replied.

“Which guild?” Ye Xiu asked.

”

So direct…… Blue River coughed up blood, but he was too lazy to hide himself. Since he was going with the flow, he might as well answer the question: “Blue Brook Guild.”

“Blue River?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No way? How’d you know???” Blue River was shocked. He was quite sure that Ye Xiu had the ability to tell that he was an experienced player from his previous performance, but being able to actually identify him was truly too terrifying. Even though he was also an in game expert, he was still only a measly character compared to a pro. He had a hard time believing that such a God would care so much about him and even recognize his style.

“I didn’t……. It was a random guess.”

“Such an accurate random guess…….” Blue River was speechless.

“Blue Brook Guild…… There are only three Blade Masters there that I know and that Poplar Bleach doesn’t seem like the type of person who would be a good spy.” Ye Xiu said.

“So he knows Poplar Beach.” Blue River corrected and asked curiously: “Then who’s the last person?”

“Huang Shaotian……”

“Oh……” Blue River wiped a bead of sweat from his face. Huang Shaotian obviously couldn’t be a spy.

“What’s up with you? What type of spy acts like that?” Ye Xiu had already begun scolding him.

Blue River’s cheeks were streaked with tears. This was such a weird conversation. He didn’t know how to reply.

“You’ve already been caught, so why did you stay in my guild?” Ye Xiu continued to ask.

“I was bored, so I just stayed.” Blue River replied.

“Bored, hm? Then I’ll give you some stuff to do!”

“What stuff?” Blue River asked.

“Help me manage my guild.” Ye Xiu said.

He instantly froze.

Blue River pinched himself to confirm that he wasn’t dreaming. He then opened up his chat log and looked carefully again to see that he hadn’t seen wrongly. He then froze again. He couldn’t understand where such a weird thought came from.

“Hello? Hello?” Ye Xiu was still urging him.

“Help you manage your guild?” Blue River asked back.

“Yeah!”

“Why?” Blue River was very curious.

“Because you’re bored!” Ye Xiu’s response made Blue River want to slam his head against the wall.

“Not that!” Blue River typed, “You know who I am and yet you want me to help manage your guild?”

“Yeah!”

“What do you mean ‘Yeah!’? What’s your reasoning behind this?”

“Look.” Ye Xiu began to help Blue River analyze, “My guild has just been created and everyone is a new player, so they don’t understand a lot of things. They very much need a qualified veteran to help them out.”

“I’m a spy!” Blue River stressed. With this line, Blue River felt that he might be the weirdest spy ever.

“Mm, but you’re a spy who’s been caught.” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River stared blankly. He suddenly understood a bit of what the God was thinking.

He…… was getting straight to the point!

Chapter 359 – Babysitter Blue River

Blue River froze for a good while before finally replying back: “…… why should I help you manage your guild?”

“Because you’re bored…..”

The other side responded with the same answer as before, making Blue River grab his hair in frustration. In this strange situation, he reckoned that if news of this spread, everyone would think that he was mentally insane. He was a spy who had lost faith in what he was doing and even had his true identity exposed, but the other side had unexpectedly handed him an important task. If he didn’t know that the other side was a God and that he was just a little shrimp in comparison, Blue River would have suspected that there was some sort of conspiracy theory revolving around him.

“There really isn’t that much work to do.” Ye Xiu began to say, “If you look at the guild chat, you’ll see that some of these new players are super nooby!”

“I saw.” Blue River hadn’t really paid too much attention to the guild chat, but once Ye Xiu finished what he had said and Blue River looked, he saw that there were actually a lot of noob discussions going on. Ye Xiu had worked hard these last two hours trying to correct them, but even after correcting them, the new players continued to let loose with their noobish thoughts. Ye Xiu’s knowledge and theories were being corroded by these noobs.

The person leading these bunch of players wouldn’t really be considered a leader, but more like a babysitter…..

This was something that Blue River was very experienced with. This was exactly the type of work a guild leader in a new server would do. It was just that when he came over to the new server, he also brought along a few helpers, so that they wouldn’t be like Guild Happy, which didn’t have any experts at its core.

Well, it did have experts, but only having God Ye Qiu teach a bunch of noobs was a bit too much.

When Blue River thought about how there were five hundred noobs, he also shivered, but he quickly slapped his forehead: Why am I even thinking about this? I’m the Blue Brook Guild’s tenth server guild leader! How could I run over to another guild and be a babysitter?

Blue River thought, while cautiously looking left and right.

Blue River couldn’t let his co-workers know about this weird event.

Meanwhile, on the other side, Lord Grim continued to send messages one after the other. His messages were very clear. They were clearly explaining to Blue River how he should begin his task.

“Hey, hey, I never said I’d help you.” Blue River replied.

“Oh, then hear me out. Doing this can help you manage your Blue Brook Guild as well.” Ye Xiu said.

“One person playing on two accounts and managing two guilds. That’s got to be a first.” Ye Xiu messaged once again.

Blue River immediately began imagining the scene, but he quickly recovered. What the heck? Why does it feel like I’ve agreed with him?

“How much does Blue Brook Guild pay you every month?” Ye Xiu messaged.

Money was a touchy topic, but it had to be mentioned. In truth, players like Blue River could be considered as someone who played games for a living. It was just that, when compared to pro players, their jobs were more stable. They were basically Club Blue Rain’s employees with their work being to play Glory.

The entire industry in Glory was maturing, including both the Pro Alliance and their professional guilds. Guilds that were backed by Clubs were one of the types of professional guild, but apart from those, there were also other types of professional guilds that didn’t rely on a Club backing them.

Some of these might actually be workshops that existed as guilds in the game. Substitute leveling, trading items, materials, etc. would all be covered by this business.

As for guilds backed by Clubs, they weren’t as professional as these work studios. The only ones that were paid by the Clubs were its upper level core members. The rest were fans that gathered together to support and contribute to their favorite teams through the guild.

Blue River was one of Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts and the guild leader in the tenth server, so Ye Xiu was very certain that Blue River was paid for by Club Blue Rain. As for how much their salary was, Ye Xiu could only make an assumption. Each guild had different rates, but there wouldn’t be too big of a difference between them.

Blue River didn’t expect Ye Xiu to ask this question, but from this, he was able to see the other side’s ambition. Only a guild with a pro team could hire employees to manage their guild.

Not waiting for Blue River’s answer, Ye Xiu sent another message; “Well, it doesn’t matter. We don’t actually have any money, so go work first and then we’ll pay you back later.”

Blue River coughed up blood. In the end, he just wanted free labor! Blue River trusted that Ye Xiu would keep his promise though. Even though this guy sometimes made him want to grind his teeth, Blue River always felt that he was a trustworthy person.

“I think that’s it? Is there anything else?” Ye Xiu asked again.

“Hey, hey. What the heck! I never agreed!” Blue River struggled.

“There’s no need to be polite!”

“What? Polite!? I’m the guild leader for Blue Brook Guild. I don’t have time to help you manage your guild!” Blue River said.

“But you have the time to play on a different account and blindly stroll around in my guild?” Ye Xiu replied.

After a short pause, he added: “And you’ve already been exposed too.”

Blue River couldn’t answer back. He didn’t really care about anything right now. He even implied that when he spoke to Changing Spring. As for how the Club would react when they found out he wasn’t doing any work, he unexpectedly hadn’t thought of that. After all, he wasn’t just some random fan who was working for fun. He was taking their money and it was his responsibility to put in effort. The words that he had said to Changing Spring hadn’t been a resignation. It was just that Blue River felt very tired and wanted to take a break and wander around without having to care about anything.

But it hadn’t even been two hours since he had started and Lord Grim had already handed him a bunch of stuff to do as if he actually was Guild Happy’s manager. Lord Grim had even given him the power to add and kick people from the guild. Blue River had no idea what to do at this moment.

“Look, look! These two noobs have started arguing and neither of them is right.” Ye Xiu messaged.

Blue River opened the guild chat and looked. Two Elementalists were discussing which path to take. Both were sticking to their own views and it turned out that both views were complete nonsense.

Blue River’s knowledge of the game obviously couldn’t compare to Ye Xiu’s and he certainly wasn’t proficient in every class like Ye Xiu was, but he was more than qualified enough to correct some noobs. Blue River glanced at it and in the end, he couldn’t help but speak up and instruct the two noobs.

When the two noobs saw this “Peerless Looks” talk, they thought he was another noob who had joined in on the debate, but then they saw that he had said that both of them were wrong and quite impolitely too.

Though after seeing Peerless Look’s level, they immediately became obedient. In game, being high leveled didn’t necessarily mean you were an expert, but that was what a lot of noobs thought.

Once Blue River started, he couldn’t stop. He began organizing the members who were still online to do quests and run dungeons, assigning everything clearly and orderly. Blue River was clearly much better at this than Ye Xiu was. After all, playing in a guild was something that Ye Xiu had done before he joined the pro scene. It was something that he hadn’t done in many many years.

“Who’s this?” Su Mucheng and Tang Rou asked curiously. At this moment, Chen Guo had already gone to sleep.

“Blue River. Blue Brook Guild’s tenth server guild leader.” Ye Xiu told them.

The two heard this and had weird expressions on their faces.

‘Why would someone from Blue Brook Guild help manage our guild?” Su Mucheng asked.

“I don’t know why, but this guild leader ran over to our guild to be a spy and was caught by me. In any case, I know who he is, so we can just let him work. See, he’s very good. Much better than I am.” After seeing how Blue River was handling things and that the guild chat was now neat and orderly, he could only feel inferior.

“So is he a deserter?” Su Mucheng asked.

“No idea! But I reckon that something’s up with him. A guild leader running over to be a spy is already very unusual. Even when everyone else left, he still stayed. When he was called over to fight, he didn’t even try to hide that he was a spy. When I asked for his identity, he just said it. We’ll see.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hey hey!” Ye Xiu received a message from Blue River.

“What’s up?”

“What’s up with this guild title you gave me? I’m not a babysitter! Get rid of it! Get rid of it!” Blue River had been talking in the guild chat the entire time! Then he suddenly discovered that his character had a title on his head that said “Guild Happy’s Number One Babysitter”. Every guild member by default had the title “Guild XX Member”. To those who had the power to, the word “member” could be changed. A lot of guild experts gave themselves impressive titles. Ye Xiu had changed Blue River’s title to “Number One Babysitter”. Even though it was quite fitting, Blue River was clearly unhappy with it.

“Hm? You don’t like it? Then what should I call you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Nothing! Just use the default!” Blue River liked to stay lowkey.

“Okay……” Ye Xiu didn’t make it difficult for him and immediately switched the title back to the default title. Blue River began talking in the guild chat again.

“Keep up the good work! After a few days, there’ll be more people here to help you.” Ye Xiu messaged Blue River.

“After a few days?” Blue River didn’t understand.

“Around five days!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Five days…… so it’s like that. No wonder you’re at ease with me being here. I’ll only be working for five days!” Blue River replied.

“How could that be? As long as you’re willing, you can keep working for as long as you’d like!” Ye Xiu replied.

Chapter 360 – Steady Development

Five days.

Blue River immediately understood after hearing this.

Most of the high-level players had already joined guilds, especially the old players, who knew of the importance of the Guardian, and would usually join a guild early on. But some of them might be moved by the fiery opening of Lord Grim’s guild. Though if they wanted to join, they couldn’t do so immediately. They had to wait five days after leaving the guild.

As a result, after five days, Guild Happy would have a batch of useful players join, whether that was a lot or only a few. When that time came, he might not be the only spy though, since it would be a perfect opportunity to get high-level spies into the guild.

Blue River had thought of a lot of things, though he was still stumped for words when Ye Xiu causally told him that as long as he wanted to stay, he could.

Was God Ye Qiu really not on guard against him?

He didn’t even know whether or not to be on guard against him because, right now, he didn’t know what was going on with himself. He had accepted Ye Xiu’s task for some strange reason. When he was busily typing in the guild chat, he really didn’t have too many thoughts. He was simply doing what Ye Xiu told him to do.

But if this was his normal self, would he have used this opportunity to gain trust and become an actual spy?

Blue River stared blankly. He felt like he was stuck at a crossroad. Should he go left or should he go right? It seemed like he would need to choose soon.

One person, two accounts, managing two guilds.

Blue River suddenly thought of what Ye Xiu had said previously. That had obviously been said as a joke. A normal player might be able to do something like this. But he was a professional with Club Blue Rain’s name. With Club Blue Rain paying him, how could he help someone else do their work?

Whatever! There’s no point in thinking about it so much! I’ll just go along with it for five days and then go from there!

Blue River shook his head. He wouldn’t think so much and just continue being busy in the guild chat.

Five days. It couldn’t be considered as a long time, but it couldn’t be considered as short, either.

In Glory, five days was enough to set many dungeon records.

This was something that many guilds cared about, especially after the creation of Lord Grim’s Guild Happy. Rumor has it that many of the guild leaders had woken up during their sleep from nightmares.

In reality, what everyone feared didn’t happen. After five days passed, when the level of Guild Happy’s players increased another stage, Guild Happy didn’t take down any records. There were even some who were initially filled with high expectations for Guild Happy, thinking that there would be lots of exciting gossip to hear, but were all disappointed after five days had passed.

Day five. Guild Happy leveled from Level 5 to Level 12.

For a guild that always had the maximum number of players possible, this leveling speed wasn’t actually anything impressive. And after getting past Level 10, the excitement from the new Guild Happy members had died down a lot. The main thing was that Guild Happy had already already reached Level 12, but they still hadn’t challenged the Level 2 Guardian.

A lot of talk, but no action!

There were already many criticisms of this type from the outside world. But for top guilds like Tyrannical Ambition, this situation was quite rage inducing. Not challenging the Guardian at Level 10, could it be because Guild Happy wasn’t strong enough to do so? Could the reason Guild Happy had been able to beat the Guardian at Level 5 be because of the spies they had sent out?

When the top guilds thought of this, the guild leaders didn’t have any other thoughts than kicking people.

But it was currently a good time to send out spies. Five days. The players who had left their guilds to join Guild Happy could finally do so. This was something the top guilds were certain of. This was because there was no lack of players that had left their guilds to do this.

Among these, Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition stood out. These two guilds had been crushed by Lord Grim before. Quite a few new players in these guilds had begun doubting their guild. These new players didn’t have that sort of fan loyalty yet. Seeing what seemed to be an even better Lord Grim create a guild, many of them immediately thought of running over to him and quickly left.

When they discussed whether they should send out spies or not, the guilds couldn’t help but think of the guild members that had left and felt unbearably sad.

The spies had to be sent out. This time, the top guilds didn’t need to worry about whether their spies would become their enemy’s free labor force. Even if they weren’t there, the other side could still create a high-level 20-player team.

On Guild Happy’s side, the new wave of new players had been predicted five days ago. Most of the new players this time had left their guilds to join Guild Happy.

Not fighting the Guardian after Level 10 had made Guild Happy become worried. This was the truth. However, the reason that Guild Happy’s numbers weren’t growing as fast after Level 10 definitely wasn’t because of this. Even though the guild members’ excitement had waned, ensuring that they could reach the max limit of players with every level up wouldn’t be difficult. There were still many many players on Guild Happy’s request list.

The reason that the numbers weren’t growing as fast was entirely because of Ye Xiu. It was preparation for this batch of players.

The players who joined hadn’t hesitated to leave their guild. Some of them were from top guilds as well, so it was very easy to see how passionate these players were.

Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon’s group had switched over from Full Moon Guild and had even dragged a few of their good friends over as well. They might not be experts, but they were certainly experienced veterans.

These players did not have high levels, but Ye Xiu welcomed them kindly nonetheless.

Their levels fit together perfectly with everyone else. Having them level up with these new players would be a big help.

As for those players with levels around Lord Grim’s level, having them carry the low-level new players to beat dungeons would be okay once or twice for a few days. But after awhile, they wouldn’t be happy.

The veterans like Seven Fields who were at the same level as these low-level players could carry this burden. Their leading would be better than having these new players looking at guides and stumbling around in the dungeon until they passed it.

Though the one who had worked the hardest was still Blue River.

During these five days, Ye Xiu almost never saw Blue River on his main account. He saw him with his open account every single day, helping Guild Happy with everything.

This experienced manager quickly made the players who didn’t understand a guild’s value, see the advantages of a guild.

They had organized themselves for leveling, dungeoning, and questing purposes. All of these increased their efficiency and reduced the difficulty.

Feeling these benefits, the impression towards guilds by the players who had liked to play alone naturally increased.

A Level 12 Guild could have a maximum of 1,200 players. On the sixth day since Guild Happy’s creation, they finally reached that maximum. Ye Xiu then locked the guild requests.

“What are you doing?” Chen Guo didn’t understand Ye Xiu’s actions. These days, she had been even more attentive towards Guild Happy than Ye Xiu. Whenever she played, her attention was on Ye Xiu’s screen half the time.

“We have enough players.” Ye Xiu said.

“There’s still a lot on the request list!” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu shook his head: “It’s enough. We’re still only a normal guild. Our players aren’t as loyal as those guilds backed by Clubs. Our development can’t be too quick. We actually have a bit too many players right now. Without Blue River’s experienced managing, who knows what would have happened.”

“It can’t be that bad, right?” Chen Guo thought differently. Guild Happy’s development had made her very excited. In her eyes, Guild Happy getting to a maximum of 10,000 players wouldn’t be difficult. When the time for the Heavenly Domain challenge passed, ten thousand players joining the Heavenly Domain would create a huge scene. She had been expecting this scene to happen, but then Ye Xiu suddenly closed off the guild request list.

“You’ve played the game for so long. You should have seen a big guild fall many times!” Ye Xiu said.

“There were reasons for those.” Chen Guo said.

“If we don’t control it, those sorts of reasons will pop up.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what do we do?”

“Right now, it’s still in my range of control. We’ll slowly grow in this way! After we officially create our team, participate in a few matches and win some fame, the nature of our guild will gradually change.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh……” Chen Guo nodded her head and didn’t argue. She really didn’t know enough in this area to discuss things with Ye Xiu.

“Then what now?’ Chen Guo was concerned over this.

“We’ll beat the Guardian first!” Ye Xiu said and began pulling in people. Quite a few high-level players had joined.

“There will definitely be spies from the top guilds among these, right?” Chen Guo said.

“Of course, but it doesn’t matter. There’s nothing we can do about it.” Ye Xiu said casually. The 20-player team was quickly created. After saying what they were going to do in the guild chat, no one objected. The Guardian’s blessing was something that everyone wanted to have.

With Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s aggro control, the difficult Guardian challenge transformed into an easy and relaxed battle. And this time, not everyone could be a spy. Everyone listened to directions and tried their hardest. The Level 2 Guardian seemed to be even easier than the Level 1 Guardian and it was quickly defeated.

Chapter 361 – Lacking Characters

Beating the Level 2 Guardian naturally meant that they would receive a Level 2 Guardian’s blessing. The guild members online celebrated in the guild chat.

Blue River was one of the players that had participated in the Guardian challenge. When he saw the great celebration that was going on in Guild Happy’s chat, he suddenly felt a huge sense of accomplishment. He hadn’t felt such an emotion in a very long time with Blue Brook Guild. Over there, he felt like he was only doing work. The number of new guild members and their satisfaction felt like performance reports. He hadn’t shared such simple joys with the new guild members in a very long time. He had always walked with the top players and would fight for dungeon records with a bunch of old birds every day. For these old birds, the fun in the games had turned monotonous.

“Good work, everyone.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim said to everyone who had participated in the Guardian challenge.

Everyone replied back politely.

Some of these might be spies from other guilds…… Blue River thought quietly. Even though he hadn’t logged into his Blue River account very much these past five days, he still knew what was going on in Blue Brook Guild. He had others beside him in the guild. They didn’t understand what Blue River was doing, but they didn’t ask him any questions. Nothing really happened during these five days either. Should they send more spies into Guild Happy? Changing Spring had personally dealt with the issue. No one had run over to ask Blue River though.

As for the character Blue River was playing on, his position in Guild Happy was very high. Apart from the extremely famous Lord Grim, he was certainly the second most recognized character in the guild.

Blue River managed the guild neatly and orderly. Whether it was for leveling in the wild, for dungeoning, or for doing quests, Guild Happy already felt the effects from his management.

Even Blue River was having trouble adapting with Guild Happy’s rapid development. Every time they leveled, another hundred players would immediately join.

The fame for the guilds backed by Clubs came from old players who loved Glory’s competitive scene. They supported their teams and players and would naturally support their guild.

The guilds backed by Clubs still had to follow the game’s rules though. But in reality, in gathering places for old players such as the Heavenly Domain, there were branches of Blue Brook Guild. These were obviously fans of Team Blue Rain as well. In-game, it was a very convenient way of gathering fans together. Their cohesiveness depended on the team’s existence while the benefits from guilds weren’t necessary.

As for Guild Happy, they were still a normal guild. Even though their guild leader was actually God Ye Qiu, this truth hadn’t yet been revealed. And in reality, in the new server, his identity would only be the same as the Clubs’. His name wouldn’t actually prove to be too useful.

New players had only just touched Glory. Teams? Pro players? They had only just started understanding them and so it would take them awhile to get interested.

The reason Guild Happy could expand so quickly was entirely because of Lord Grim’s fame, which had come from him having crushed the top guilds. However, the cohesiveness from this type of fame couldn’t compare to the loyalty of team fans. Even for a guild created by a famous player, Blue River wasn’t too optimistic about unrestrained expansion.

He had originally planned on reminding Lord Grim, but after the guild reached Level 10, he saw that the number of players who joined had slowed down. At Level 12, after the last batch of players joined, Blue River saw that the guild closed off any other requests to join the guild.

Blue River hit his head. These sorts of things didn’t need to be reminded of by him.

Some of the management matters had been given to him simply because Lord Grim didn’t have that much time on his hands. But for this God with ten years of experience, as expected, he didn’t make such a mistake for the guild’s general direction of development.

The five days had already passed. He couldn’t actually stay with Guild Happy or maybe he should……

Just as Blue River was thinking about this, he suddenly received a message.

“Old Blue!” The message was from Lord Grim.

“I’m younger than you!” Blue River coughed up blood. Ye Qiu’s age was well-known. He wasn’t as old as him, so why was he called “Old Blue”?

“Oh, Little Blue!” The message returned with a change in the name. But even so, Blue River still felt that it was weird. He endured it though and didn’t argue.

“Let me introduce these guys to you.” Ye Xiu gave Blue River the names of Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, Drifting Water, Sunset Clouds, and their four friends that they had brought along from Full Moon Guild.

“What’s this for?” Blue River asked.

“These guys aren’t new players. But their level isn’t very high, which means that they can play together with the new players. How do you think they should be organized?” Ye Xiu replied.

“I…… I’ve still got a lot of stuff to do back in Blue Brook Guild!” Even though there really wasn’t much going on in Blue Brook Guild recently, how could this old brother just call on him so naturally like that! He was still a spy! A spy!

“Oh, then you can do it after you finish that stuff.” Ye Xiu replied.

Blue River almost fell off his chair. He didn’t know how to reply, when the other side followed up: “I suggest you use two computers with two accounts open. What do you think? Would that be too hard?”

“……” Besides ellipses, Blue River didn’t know what to say.

Several system notifications popped up. Blue River opened them up to check. There were eight, the eight players that Ye Xiu had referred to him wanted to add him as a friend. Ye Xiu had clearly told them to say hi to him.

Blue River couldn’t do anything but accept them. They were all old players, so they knew what they needed to do. After saying hi, they directly went to the main subject.

Blue River had managed the guild for the past five days, so no one was more clear than he was on what to do with these eight old players. After getting to know their schedules, he quickly assigned them to a suitable position.

As for the significance of these eight players, Blue River and Ye Xiu both knew that they were the same as them. They were basically babysitters for the new players. If the size of the guild was slightly smaller, anyone would do. But with Guild Happy’s terrifying development, Blue River had to work hard by himself. Now that there were eight others with suitable levels too, Blue River felt very grateful for them.

“They can’t be the only old players who have joined, right?” Blue River could tell what Ye Xiu was thinking. When the guild reached Level 10, he stopped adding players, but didn’t close off the guild requests either. From this, Blue River knew that Ye Xiu was preparing to accept the players who had left their other guilds. The new batch of players clearly had higher levels than the others in the guild too. When Blue River swept across the names list, he could even see a few names he had recognized. They were originally from their Blue Brook Guild and had switched over to Guild Happy. Blue River didn’t know what to feel about these players.

“Yeah, there should be quite a lot. You can slowly feel them out!” Ye Xiu replied.

“…….” Facing someone who asks another to work but didn’t actually work himself, Blue River couldn’t feel happy.

“Are you planning on competing for the dungeon records?” Blue River switched the subject. In truth, this was the reason why the top guilds were hostile towards Guild Happy. From a common sense perspective, Guild Happy didn’t have a reason not to compete for the dungeon records. But after managing the guild for so long, he discovered that Guild Happy didn’t have the conditions necessary for competing for the dungeon records.

Level! This was their main problem.

In the entire guild, only Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, and Soft Mist had levels that could compare with the top guilds’ first string players. They could compete with the top guilds in the forefront tenth server dungeons.

But aside from them, they didn’t have a fourth person.

Lord Grim originally had Steamed Bun Invasion, but right now, his level was too far off. As for that Ghostblade, One Inch Ash, Blue River couldn’t find him in the guild’s name list.

No matter how good God Ye Qiu was, with only three players, it wasn’t possible for them to compete for dungeon records. And there was no way that they’d be able to find any accounts at this level in the new server. Blue River could even say how many players were at this level: 99! At that time, there were 99 players who were cooperating in Sin City. In addition, Blue River could even write down all 99 players’ names if given enough time. They were all elites from the top guilds. These players definitely wouldn’t help Guild Happy out.

“There aren’t enough players who meet the needed conditions. Our levels aren’t high enough.” Ye Xiu’s reply told him of this problem.

“Can your Blue Brook Guild lend me two accounts?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Don’t even think about it!” Being a babysitter in Guild Happy was already weird enough. He really had no way no way of explaining about letting him use two accounts. His Blue Brook Guild friends thought that he was just addicted to being a spy and didn’t know what exactly he was up to.

“That Blue River account hasn’t been on these past few days right?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah, it hasn’t…….”

“What a waste. How about I use it?”

“F*ck off! That’s the guild leader’s account! Guild leader account!!!” Blue River couldn’t endure it anymore. In the past, he had always taken note of God Ye Qiu’s professional identity, so his tone had been respectful. But the more he came into contact with him, the more he felt like there was no reason for his respect.

There really is no reason to respect him…… After Blue River shouted at the God, he suddenly felt quite good.

Chapter 362 – There’s Still One More Trick

In the tenth server, the highest level that players could be was Level 42. There were differences in the experience within this group, but the differences weren’t too big. The main reason for their level advantages was because of the alliance with Ye Xiu in the Christmas event.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng and Tang Rou could be considered a part of the top players in the server. But since they couldn’t be online 24/7 like the characters from the top guilds, they were among the bottom and were only at Level 41 right now.

The guild leader account Blue River was also amongst these top players.

This account’s level had been outstanding. But because it hadn’t been played on for five days, it was immediately left behind by the other elite characters.

Ye Xiu’s mention of this account was a reminder to Blue River. Since he hadn’t been on his main account for five days, his character’s level hadn’t really changed. Even though the guild leader didn’t necessarily have to be the highest level in the guild, levels were still the most direct symbol for one’s status in the game. Having a higher level as a guild leader gave more power to their words. Blue River’s account was still at the top of the guild, but if he continued to neglect using it, that would soon no longer be the case.

“I have to go back to Blue Brook Guild to take a look.” Blue River thought. He sent Lord Grim a message and hastily logged off his account Peerless Looks. In the blink of an eye, he logged back in with his Blue River account.

“How fast! I wasn’t even done talking yet!” Lord Grim had chased after him.

“What else is there?” Blue River asked. As soon as he logged on, he received quite a few greetings. Spies were a very secretive matter in the guild, so not many players knew that Blue River had been using “Peerless Looks” to infiltrate Guild Happy. The majority of guild members thought something had happened to him in the past few days. Seeing Blue River suddenly return, they quickly asked him if anything had happened, making Blue River feel very moved.

Blue Brook Guild was still his home. With so many friends and memories…….

Blue River replied to everyone with a tinge of emotion. Ye Xiu once again messaged him: “Among those that are high up on the level standings, do you think there are any that can be dug out?”

“No way.” Blue River decisively said without looking at the standings. These characters were definitely loyal to their guilds. How could such carefully groomed characters be pulled away so easily?

“Not even one?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Uh…….” Blue River had been very confident initially, but Ye Xiu’s question had made him hesitate. Nothing was absolute! He didn’t understand other guilds as well as his own. How could he be certain that others might not feel the same way?

“You might not be so sure of other guilds, so go check on the ones from your guild.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, you even know that they’re from our Blue Brook Guild!” Blue River replied with an emoticon of a crumbling face.

“If their hearts aren’t there, then there’s no point in forcing them.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Whose heart isn’t there!” Blue River replied, but he felt a bit lacking in confidence. Because in these past few days, his heart wasn’t really there. But after logging into his Blue River account and receiving the concern of everyone in his guild, he still felt that he belonged to Blue Brook Guild.

“It’s just analogy.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Even if the player’s heart isn’t there, the character is still going to stay!” Blue River wasn’t lying. These characters were all being leveled by using the guild’s resources from up to three players. The character was considered the guild’s; not a single person could just take that away whenever they wanted to.

“There isn’t any exception?” Ye Xiu asked again. Blue River hesitated again because when he looked at his guild’s member list. He discovered that there really was an exception in their Blue Brook Guild.

Thousand Creations…….

This guy loved to KS and he was the only one who had leveled his own character. The guild didn’t really provide too much help for him. However, his skill in the game was truly top notch, so whenever an important activity happened, Thousand Creations would usually be brought along.

For the Christmas quest, Thousand Creations had been specially called him over, too, so he leveled up like crazy. Afterwards, he continued with his play style. His leveling speed couldn’t compare to those characters that could be on 24/7, but he was still among the very top.

“I know how you guilds groom your elite characters. But because Glory requires that you use an account card to log in, there’s a limit to your method of leveling. There can’t be too many characters that can be leveled this way. From the looks of it, the highest leveled ones are definitely being leveled in this way, but the ones that are just on the border are probably leveling on their own, no?” Ye Xiu said.

That…… Blue River felt powerless against Ye Xiu’s message because his analysis was completely correct. For example, by looking at the level standings, Blue River had been dropped off of it because he hadn’t played for five days. As for Thousand Creations, who was being leveled by only one person, he was on the very edge.

“So from the level standings, you can test it out starting from the bottom to the top!” Ye Xiu said.

“How are you going to test them?” Blue River couldn’t help but ask. Even though Ye Xiu’s decision made sense, his decision still stood that there were players that had the qualifications to take their accounts with them. This didn’t have anything to do with the player’s loyalty to the guild either. Trying to rope these players in would be very troublesome, so Blue River was curious as to how he was going to achieve that.

“Sigh, there really isn’t any other way. My only choice is to use my old name and tell them that I’m Ye Qiu to see whether or not they’ll follow me over.” Ye Xiu replied.

“F*CK!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!” Blue River’s hand shook and he typed a string of exclamation marks. How could he have forgotten about this move?

Ye Qiu’s identity…….

Thinking about this and checking the name list, Blue River’s eyes turned black.

Thousand Creations!! How could he not understand his own guild’s players? Even though Thousand Creations was a member of Blue Brook Guild, his favorite player was still Ye Qiu!

Any player whose favorite class was the Battle Mage would have Ye Qiu as their idol. With such power, he’d be the same as their guilds who were backed by Clubs who used their teams to attract fans!

It couldn’t be said that them support a team and liking a player from another team were conflicting.

Especially for players like Ye Qiu, or Huang Shaotian, or Han Wenqing, Zhou Zekai, these players who represented the top of their respective classes. Battle God, Sword Saint, King of Fighting, Great Gunner……. How could people who played these classes not idolize these pros?

“Uh…… if we start from the bottom, the first one is you…… So it isn’t convenient for you to come over with your guild leader account?” Ye Xiu began.

“…….” Blue River was silent.

“Next up is…… Thousand Creations. Hey, I think I recognize this guy. He’s from your guild, right?” Ye Xiu gave a live report of what he was doing to Blue River.

Blue River was speechless. He didn’t know what to do……. Should he go warn Thousand Creations first? But how should he go do that? Was he just going to tell Thousand Creations that in a bit, Lord Grim’s going to tell him that he’s Ye Qiu and that he can’t trust Lord Grim because he’s a dirty liar?

The problem was…… It was actually the truth. If he actually said that to Thousand Creations, then he’d be the dirty liar……. But then again, how was Ye Qiu going to prove that he was actually Ye Qiu?

Blue River still didn’t know what to do! He suddenly received a message. At first, he thought it was from Lord Grim, but when he opened it, he saw that it was actually from Thousand Creations.

“Lord Grim said he was Ye Qiu!! Did you know that?” Thousand Creations messaged.

“Ah?” Blue River was startled, “Where’d that question come from?”

“That guy added me as a friend and said that he was Ye Qiu. He said that if I didn’t believe him, I should go and ask you.” Thousand Creations said.

“GOD D*MMIT!!!!!!!!!” Blue River’s hands trembled. He hadn’t thought that he’d become Ye Qiu’s proof. What should he say? What should he say??

“What’s wrong?” Thousand Creations replied quite quickly.

“Lord Grim isn’t anything special!” Blue River replied.

“Oh? He’s pretending to be Ye Qiu?” Thousand Creations asked.

Blue River struggled for awhile, before finally replying: “Yes! He’s a dirty liar!”

“Uh…… Guild leader. Are you saying this because you’re afraid that I’ll run over to Guild Happy?” Thousand Creations suddenly replied.

“How could that be!” Blue River stared blankly after replying, because Thousand Creations wasn’t wrong.

“Because he said……. He said that you wouldn’t help him prove his identity because you’re afraid that I’ll abandon you…….” Thousand Creations said.

“How could he be so shameless!!!” Blue River was about to go mad.

“Guild leader……. Is he really Ye Qiu?” Thousand Creations asked.

“What about you…… if he really is him? Are you going to leave?” Blue River asked.

After a long pause, a message finally flashed. Blue River looked and saw Thousand Creations reply: Leave.

“He’s not!” Blue River decisively replied.

“Guild leader……” Thousand Creations could already see the reason for his answer.

“Fine……. He’s Ye Qiu. He really is…… Quite a few already know this. If you want to go, then go!” Blue River sighed.

“Thanks, guild leader :)” Thousand Creations added a smiley face and in the next second, a guild notification appeared in Blue Brook Guild’s chat: Player Thousand Creations has left the guild.

Chapter 363 – One More

In the end, Thousand Creations left the guild. Blue River had been prepared for this though, so he wasn’t too surprised. It was just that the way Ye Qiu had used him to prove himself made Blue River want to cry.

Thousand Creations leaving the guild gave Blue River less worries. He was familiar with the players in his guild, so apart from Thousand Creations, the rest weren’t big fans of Ye Qiu. This meant that using his identity to pull them in wouldn’t work. For example, Bound Boat had known of Lord Grim’s identity long ago.

Blue River thought that everything was good now, when a bunch of messages suddenly popped up. He opened them and looked. Most of them were old veterans of the guild asking what was going on with Thousand Creations.

A cold sweat ran down Blue River’s back. The top elites weren’t fans of Ye Qiu, but it was hard to say whether or not the others were. Blue River also couldn’t tell them all that Thousand Creations had left in order to follow Ye Qiu. This answer could very likely send another batch of talents running off.

“It’s nothing much. He just chose to.” Blue River could only give them an evasive answer.

Luckily, Thousand Creations wasn’t a very popular character in Blue Brook Guild. It was just that he had been with them for so long, so most players still recognized him. When he suddenly left out of nowhere, it was natural for them to question it. The only reason they wouldn’t want him to leave would be because of how the loss would affect the guild’s strength. Aside from that, it’d be hard to say if anyone else cared about Thousand Creations leaving.

“Is there anyone else in the guild like Thousand Creations? Just tell it to me straight so that I don’t have to try them all one at a time. It’d be very embarrassing if I had to do that.” Lord Grim messaged.

“Do you even know what it means to be embarrassed…….” Blue River didn’t even have the strength to comment sarcastically.

“Of course.” Lord Grim said, as if he had standards.

“That’s it……. You’ll know if you look. Players who idolize you usually play as Battle Mages.” Blue River replied.

“That’s true.” Lord Grim added a nodding head emoticon, but he quickly followed up: “But it seems like you guys have a Launcher?”

Blue River began to sweat like mad. How could he forget that there was still Su Mucheng! In terms of skill, Su Mucheng couldn’t be considered as top tier, but through her appearance and methods of publicity, her influence didn’t lose to God-level players. Su Mucheng had the absolute majority of fans, who played as Launchers, as her fans.

Blue River panicked, but let out a sigh of relief when he looked at the name of the Launcher in his guild list.

“Yeah, there’s a Launcher, but even if you call out Su Mucheng, he won’t leave.” Blue River replied.

“Oh? From your guild?”

“Yeah.”

“How about you kick him out of the guild?”

“F*ck off!!!” Blue River growled. After five days of being a spy, Blue River had gotten a lot more irritable, though he couldn’t pinpoint why……

“It looks like there really isn’t anyone else from Blue Brook Guild.” Ye Xiu had been very serious when he studied the list of high leveled players. He understood that his identity really only worked for Battle Mages. If this was a few years earlier, he might have been everyone’s idol, but in the past few years, Glory had been continuously developing while more and more experts from all different classes were emerging. It was currently the golden age. His influence couldn’t compare to how it was before.

If he just wanted to expand, relying on this method would work. However the problem was, Ye Xiu needed players who were at least Level 40 in order to challenge the Level 40-43 Thousand Waves Lake dungeon record. This was where most of the competition was amongst the top guilds right now.

“You can’t find anyone?” Chen Guo asked.

“For these players that have higher level accounts, even if I can persuade the player, I can’t get their account. What we need are the high-level accounts. The player really doesn’t really matter.” Ye Xiu said.

“What about others?” Chen Guo asked.

“There’s only this one left.” Ye Xiu clicked on a name near the bottom of the top 100 players. His name was Horse Shooter, a Launcher from Misty Castle.

“Launcher……” Chen Guo immediately understood Ye Xiu’s intent when she saw the class. She had been watching Ye Xiu the entire time and didn’t feel that using his identity as a God was shameless. She actually felt quite good about it. If she had been Ye Xiu, she would have directly announced to the world: “I’m Ye Qiu. If you like me, then follow me.”

“I have to get Mucheng to do it. Though…….” Ye Xiu hesitated.

“Hmph hmph! She’s definitely not as shameless as you!” Chen Guo said.

“I’ll let her figure it out!” Ye Xiu said and told Su Mucheng what to do.

“Okay, let me try.” Su Mucheng’s reply was very simple.

Su Mucheng had been even faster than Ye Xiu. It hadn’t even been a few minutes, when she replied: “Done.”

Ye Xiu opened up the level standings and saw that Horse Shooter no longer had a guild name next to him like Thousand Creations. He had clearly left the guild already.

“How’d you do it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It was nothing. I added him as a friend, then said that Guild Happy was recruiting with Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng taking the lead and asked him if he was interested.” Su Mucheng replied.

“And then?”

“He was obviously very amazed. I then told him that I’m actually Su Mucheng!” Su Mucheng said.

“And then he believed you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course not. I then gave him a cellphone number and told him to call it if he didn’t believe me.” Su Mucheng said.

“You gave him your cellphone number?”

“Huang Shaotian’s. He likes to talk, no? So I had to give him this opportunity.” Su Mucheng said.

“Hey……” Ye Xiu began to sweat. It was still a private number. In particular, for Gods like Huang Shaotian, randomly giving out his number wasn’t good.

“I’m just kidding! I just video chatted with him for a bit and that was enough.” Su Mucheng said.

“Okay, okay…….” Ye Xiu suddenly understood. It wasn’t that he hadn’t thought of using this method, but it was just that it wouldn’t work for him. No one knew his appearance, so what would a video chat do for him? Su Mucheng was different, though. Pictures of her were everywhere.

“Okay, after five days, we’ll be able to form an elite team. We can use these five days to start practicing.” Ye Xiu announced.

“Will that class comp work?” Chen Guo asked.

“Not really…… But it’s better than not having enough people.” Ye Xiu was helpless. This team had two Battle Mages and two Launchers. It was quite a mess.

At this moment, Blue River took another sweep at the level standings and saw that Horse Shooter didn’t have have a guild name next to his name like Thousand Creations. He immediately understood that Ye Qiu had gotten him. Truthfully, Blue River had noticed him and guessed that he would be Ye Qiu’s next target. It turned out to be true. Using Su Mucheng’s fame, they were able to recruit a Launcher. Now, Guild Happy had a high-level dungeon team.

Thinking of how the dungeon records could only have been made with the dungeon guides, Blue River felt like the future for the top guilds in the tenth server were looking very grim. How were the top guilds going to compete? Blue River racked his brains. He had already forgotten that as the tenth server guild leader of Blue Brook Guild, this was supposed to be an issue that he should be trying to solve and not just thinking about it as if he were an outsider.

The level standings weren’t something the top guilds paid much attention to like Blue River did, but there were still players that noticed.

Two characters not having a guild wasn’t something that the top guilds thought too hard about. Seeing that these two high-level characters didn’t have guilds, the first thing they did was try and pull them in. As a result, Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter were receiving invites from all the top guilds in the server.

But after receiving their replies, as if lightning had struck them, the guilds immediately understood the truth.

These two high-level characters had gone to Guild Happy???

Like Blue River had initially thought, these guild leaders hadn’t thought that these high-level players were able to be dug out by Guild Happy, and from the reports given to them by spies in Guild Happy, they knew that Guild Happy wasn’t able to compete with them for the Level 40-43 Thousand Waves Lake dungeon because they didn’t have enough high-level players. This was the result of Lord Grim’s work in Sin City. If he hadn’t come out, the top elites from their guilds wouldn’t have pulled so far apart from the rest of the playerbase. It could be said that Lord Grim had suffered the consequence of his own actions.

The top guilds were happy about this, but who would have thought that Guild Happy would be able to persuade two high-level characters to join? This news made them feel very uneasy.

What the heck was Blue Brook Guild doing? What the heck was Misty Castle doing?

The guilds that had their characters leave immediately received a bunch of hate. They obviously didn’t know of Ye Xiu’s method of persuasion. They just felt lucky that he didn’t persuade their players.

“In five days, Lord Grim will bring his team to compete for the dungeon record!” The top guilds were all discussing about this issue.

“Five days…… Will we be able to pull our levels apart?”

“Not by much! Lord Grim’s team doesn’t need the highest level characters to take down the record. Unless we can pull far apart enough to reach another dungeon, one or two levels won’t make a difference.”

Everyone was silent. No one knew what to do.

As a result, the guild leaders created a group chat again and began tackling this difficult issue.

“How could Blue Brook Guild and Misty Castle let these high-level characters go?” This question started the discussion.

“The answer to that is very scary. Are you sure you want to know?” Blue River said dully.

Chapter 364 – Next Stage

Many of the participants in the group chat already knew what Blue River was going to say. The leading top guilds were especially quiet, but then, Samsara’s Lonely Drink stood out. Seeing that no one was speaking, he typed in an angry face emoticon to express his feelings and then asked: “What’s the answer? I want to know what’s so scary about it!”

“Happy’s guild leader, Lord Grim, is Ye Qiu.” Blue River didn’t try to decorate his words. They were very blunt.

The people who knew this continued to stay silent, but Lonely Drink continued to jump out: “Ye Qiu? Which Ye Qiu?”

“Which Ye Qiu do you think?”

“F*ck, no way!” It wasn’t hard to imagine what Lonely Drink’s expression was and he wasn’t the only one, either.

After a moment of cold silence, Lonely Drink once again spoke up.

“If Lord Grim is Ye Qiu, then that Launcher Cleansing Mist is……..” Lonely Drink was already beginning to carefully pick his words.

“Yeah, you’ve probably guessed correctly.” Blue River replied.

“Sweat……. So what?” Lonely Drink had been the most aggressive towards Lord Grim, but at this moment, everyone felt like he had suddenly weakened.

“Nothing really.” Blue River’s words were as if he had nothing to do with it: “Guild Happy has Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng. That’s the reason why there were people who left to go join Guild Happy.”

“Guild leader Blue River, you seem to know a lot.” Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader Jiang You suddenly said.

“Same to you.” Blue River replied.

“What….. You guys already knew about this?” Lonely Drink had just realized that he had been the only one asking questions. The others just sat there like spectators.

In truth, there weren’t that many who knew of this; it was just that everyone in the chat group was of high status. No one answered Lonely Drink’s question though, whether they already knew of it or had just learned of it.

“Don’t tell me……. No wonder the overall guild leaders of the Three Great Guilds all ran over to manage the tenth server. It was because the opponent this time wasn’t normal.” Lonely Drink said.

Changing Spring, Arisaema, and Jiang You going over to the tenth server was something that only their respective guilds knew of. They obviously didn’t tell outsiders. It was just that more perceptive people could tell.

“Don’t blame me for being too blunt. With opponents such as Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng, even with you three here, it still won’t even be close to enough, right?” Lonely Drink clearly wasn’t in a good mood. These guys seemed to have known everything all along, while he was the only one completely in the dark. To them, his previous actions made him look like an idiot. Lonely Drink obviously wasn’t happy about that.

The others understood what he was thinking, but they didn’t bicker. Herb Garden’s Plantago Seed came out to mediate the situation: “Aren’t we going off topic? The main issue is that we originally thought that Guild Happy wouldn’t be able to compete with us for dungeon records, but now it looks like the situation has changed. That’s what we should be trying to figure out, no?”

“Ha ha ha, you’re right! This issue really is very troublesome. You guys hurry up and think of a solution.” Lonely Drink said.

Everyone was stumped for words at first, but quickly recovered. This troublesome issue didn’t really matter much for Samsara. This was because during the last Christmas event, Guild Samsara hadn’t been in the list of guilds working together with them, so their first-string characters weren’t in the same level range as them. They had already been left behind in the Level 40-43 dungeon record competition.

There was also one other guild that was like Samsara: Excellent Dynasty.

Speaking of Excellent Dynasty, everyone was even more puzzled about their situation. In the Christmas event, if Lord Grim hadn’t interfered, Excellent Dynasty would have definitely taken the lead, but due to the interference, not only did Excellent Dynasty’s lead fail to appear, their numbers advantage didn’t bring up anything good and they ended up like Samsara. They had invested the most into the tenth server, but right now, they were still rushing towards Level 40. In terms of their investment and return, they were doing even worse than Samsara.

Samsara doing poorly wasn’t important. However, Excellent Dynasty was the guild Ye Qiu came out from. His previous account, Battle God One Autumn Leaf, and Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain were both under Excellent Dynasty’s name. It was already unexpected that Ye Qiu would be so unfriendly with them, but to torment them to such an extent?

Ever since learning of Lord Grim’s identity, this question had constantly been on their minds. They had invited Excellent Dynasty to this group chat this time and had even revealed Lord Grim’s identity. They wanted to see how Excellent Dynasty would react, but it turned out that they didn’t react at all and only Lonely Drink stood out.

“Guild leader Chen, what do you think?” Excellent Dynasty’s people weren’t speaking. Their biggest rival guild’s leader, Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You, directly called out Excellent Dynasty’s Chen Yehui.

“Oh? I have the same line of thinking as Lonely Drink. This dungeon record issue is very problematic. You guys should think of a way to solve it.” Chen Yehui said in a dull voice.

Nothing new came out from him. If the others were in their situation and their guilds wouldn’t be able to gain anything out of this, they’d sit there watching the drama, too, but this wasn’t what everyone wanted to know! They wanted to know why Ye Qiu and Excellent Dynasty were on bad terms with each other. There was definitely gossip to be had in this……

The disagreement between Ye Qiu and the team was a rumor that had been circulating around for a long time, despite both side’s avoidance of the subject. Ye Qiu’s retirement had been extremely sudden, too. An abrupt retirement during the middle of a season and then the rookie Sun Xiang immediately taking his place made this seem like a purge.

It seemed like they wouldn’t be able to get anything out of Chen Yehui, but with Ye Qiu’s conduct in-game, it seemed like the rumors really were true.

For the other large guilds, this was good news. If not, with Excellent Dynasty having such a top tier God looking after them, besides dying and giving up, what else could they do?

The situation wasn’t like this, though. Excellent Dynasty and Samsara were currently at the foot of the mountain looking up at the tigers fighting because they hadn’t been able to gain any benefits. Everyone knew that neither side would be able to dupe the other.

As a result, a new group chat quickly formed. This time, the people who were only there to watch the drama weren’t invited.They didn’t want these drama-watchers to know of their plans. If not, then who knew which of those drama watchers would try to take advantage of it.

“What should we do?” A formal discussion began in the group chat. The group didn’t forget to make sham gestures of politeness.

“I say that we need to rely on killing!” Jiang You said. As someone who liked Tyranny, he liked to use the simplest methods to resolve his problems.

After a moment of silence, Arisaema helplessly said: “You’re right. There really isn’t any other way…..”

“How do we go about killing them?” someone asked.

“From the looks of it, the current level structure in the tenth server is pretty much set. Our leveling speeds are already at their peak. Even a God like Ye Qiu wouldn’t be able to level any faster. So as long as our characters don’t make a wrong move, Happy will only have these five high-level characters.” Arisaema analyzed.

“So you’re saying we should target these five?”

“No need. We only need to choose one. As long as we kill him until his experience drops by a significant amount, that’ll be enough.” Arisaema said.

“Right.”

“First, we need to be able to guarantee that everyone’s characters won’t leave. Can everyone guarantee that?” Arisaema asked.

“That won’t be a problem on my side.” Blue River said.

The others hesitated. They couldn’t be confident that they could guarantee it.

“Or just promise that no more problems will occur.” Arisaema said it in a different way.

“We’ll do our best!” someone finally replied.

“Good. Besides this, there isn’t anything else we need to be concerned about. You guys shouldn’t be a stranger to hunting down one character. The other guild members need to watch out for Happy’s movements and defend against any rescue attempts. I bet that they won’t dare to initiate any large-scale guild battles. With their levels and skill, they would only be looking to die.” Arisaema said.

“I say that since we’re all in this together. Why not just eliminate Happy directly?” Jiang You said.

“That wouldn’t look good for us.” Changing Spring forced himself to speak at critical moments, so he usually only spoke during these moments. Everyone agreed with his reasoning. They had to consider their own guilds’ image, too. Teaming up with other guilds was fine, but they had to have a good reason to. And right now? They didn’t have a good reasons. If you said that you were going to wipe them out because they were a threat, didn’t that make you a bully? Their guilds couldn’t do this sort of thing.

“Then, who will our target be?” The discussion moved onto the next stage.

“Thousand Creations.” Changing Spring unexpectedly spoke out.

Chapter 365 – No Friends to the Left or to the Right

Changing Spring was usually too lazy to speak up in chat, but everything he said had been reflected on carefully.

Why did he say ‘Thousand Creations’? Others on the side might need to take some time to think, but Blue River instantly understood the reasoning and felt a chill in his heart.

Thousand Creations’s personality was unsociable and eccentric. He didn’t really have any friends in the guild. Outside of the guild, because of his love for kill stealing, the reason he hadn’t become a notorious rat to the public was because the tenth server had only recently opened.

However, Thousand Creations’s skill level was the real deal. Changing Spring had seen this, which was why he had put in a great amount of effort to get him to join his guild. After spending so much time together, there were moments where he stirred up trouble, but he would always perform outstandingly at crucial moments. Even without all of his merits to the guild, he had been with them for so long, so there was still a bit of a relationship.

As soon as Changing Spring saw that Thousand Creations would not help his guild anymore, he immediately used the black marks on Thousand Creation to make him the target.

This choice coincided with his previous words of “the effects wouldn’t be good” because dispatching troops to kill Thousand Creations could be considered for a just cause. When Thousand Creations came over to the tenth server, his personality hadn’t changed and he would kill steal from time to time. Even though he hadn’t aroused any public anger yet, if they went after Thousand Creations, there would still be many who would stand out and call it a justified act.

But for Blue River, pushing down Thousand Creations just like that didn’t feel right to him. Although, in the end, Blue Brook Guild was led by Changing Spring and he had the right to command what to do in the tenth server.

“His moral conduct is improper. We have reason to kill him.” Changing Spring added to give everyone a reason for choosing Thousand Creations as a target.

“Oh? If it’s just him alone, then even with Happy Guild taking him in, we can still act out. This might even develop into a reason to go to war!” Jiang You’s eyes lit up when he heard this. He still liked his idea and wanted an excuse to fight against Guild Happy. If they fought, Guild Happy definitely wouldn’t be their opponent. Right now, the top guilds had to pay attention to their image, so they couldn’t simply attack whenever they wanted to.

“Yeah, but this condition alone isn’t enough. It can be considered as one reason to attack, though.” Herb Garden’s Arisaema gave his approval.

With the approval from the guild leaders of the Three Great Guilds, the plan to kill Thousand Creations was pretty much decided on, so in the end, Blue River didn’t say anything. He didn’t have anything that he could criticize Changing Spring about anyways. He should perhaps even be admiring Changing Spring because Changing Spring was clearly more suited to leading. As Glory’s competitive scene developed, these guilds, backed by Clubs, became more and more professional, and Changing Spring had already grown from a player who only regarded the game as a game into a professional who regarded the game as work.

He no longer felt that same type of pure joy from playing the game. He now considered the game as work and instead felt feelings of satisfaction and success.

Up until now, Blue River still hadn’t been able to reach this point. During the past few days with Guild Happy, he had found it fun playing with others, even for simple events like beating the Level 1 and 2 Guardians. He was certain that if he had been Changing Spring, he wouldn’t have even batted an eyelid. Let alone for a Level 1 or 2 Guardian, he wouldn’t even care for a Level 20 Guardian. To him, it was just another necessity required to develop the guild. Beating it wasn’t something that needed to be mentioned. What was there to be happy about for something so insignificant?

With the target chosen, the following steps were something that everyone had much experience with and not too much needed to be said. They only needed to make arrangements for organizing the hunting squad and deploying them. Blue River watched attentively, not saying a single word. From time to time, he would switch back to the game and look at Thousand Creations’s name on his friends list.

Honestly speaking, he didn’t have much of a relationship with Thousand Creations, but Changing Spring’s coldness still made him feel too uncomfortable.

“Should I warn Thousand Creations?” Blue River was conflicted. What to do! He saw as the details were worked out in the group chat and knew that the operation would begin soon. The guild only needed to tell those online who to kill and they would do it. With the top guilds working together and watchers scattered throughout the server, Thousand Creations’s whereabouts were already known.

“Should I or should I not……” Blue River had already opened and closed the chat window with Thousand Creations several times now. He was extremely conflicted on what to do.

In the end, Blue River finally came to a decision. He opened up the chat window with Thousand Creations and typed two words.

“Be careful.”

Blue River didn’t say much. It was only two words, but he believed that Thousand Creations would understand. As soon as the message was sent out, Blue River felt as if a large burden had been lifted from his heart. When he looked back at the discussion going on in the group chat, he suddenly felt as if none of it was related to him.

“I know. Thanks.”

At this moment, Thousand Creations sent back a reply. He didn’t ask for any details. It was simply an “I know.” From the looks of it, it seemed like he had already known this was going to happen.

“You already knew?” Blue River couldn’t help but to ask.

“Yeah!” Thousand Creations replied.

“What do you know?”

“The top guilds will definitely move against me.” Thousand Creations said.

“It seems like you’re quite understanding of the situation?” Blue River was a bit surprised. Even though he hadn’t interacted with Thousand Creations that much, they had known each other for a long time, so he at least had a general idea of his personality. For Blue River, Thousand Creations was simply someone who was good at fighting, but wasn’t someone who had the mind to understand a lot about the battle between guilds. He hadn’t thought that he’d have seen through all this.

“Nah. It was Ye Qiu who told me.” Thousand Creations replied.

Blue River was startled. He had forgotten about this God. If Ye Qiu already knew this was going to happen, that meant he probably had plans for Thousand Creations, no? Even though he didn’t know what the plans were, he knew that they would definitely be difficult to deal with. Should he or not……. Should he or not……

Five minutes hadn’t even passed and Blue River was once again conflicted.

He had wanted to tell the top guilds that Lord Grim already had preparations against them, but just before he was about to speak out, he suddenly realized that he wasn’t clear on what to report because he had no way of explaining himself. He couldn’t just say he had warned Thousand Creations and then in return, Thousand Creations leaked important info to him.

Blue River couldn’t come to a decision before the group chat’s discussion ended for the time being and everyone returned back to the game.

“Is it starting?” Blue River messaged Changing Spring.

“Yes.” Changing Spring replied bluntly.

“Be careful. The other side might have made preparations……” Blue River said it in the end and then let out a deep sigh. He knew that if his words were looked into carefully, he would no longer have any friends to the left or right. However, he still felt that he would feel bad if he didn’t say it.

“I hope so.” Changing Spring replied, which made Blue River astonished. He soon understood that the top guilds wanted to go into a large scale battle with Guild Happy. If Guild Happy protected Thousand Creations without restraint, then that would be exactly what the top guilds wanted.

Both sides were trying to outwit each other…….

Blue River sighed and discovered that he was having a bit of trouble keeping up with everything. Even though he had still figured it out, he had been slow.

“Move out!”

At this moment, whether it was the overall guild leader or the guild leader of the server, all of them gave out the order and the operation began.

Thousand Waves Lake.

It was a Level 40-43 leveling area, which had a glittering lake with blue waves rolling about.

But as long as it was a leveling area, no matter how beautiful the scenery was, it would still be filled with danger. At the edges of the lake, savage monsters roamed around. In the lake, numerous water beasts at the Level 40-43 range lay hidden. In the middle of the lake was a small island. This was the Level 40-43 Thousand Waves Lake dungeon and the competition location for the tenth server’s first-string players.

Thousand Creations was currently wandering around the edges of the lake and randomly killing monsters.

There were very few players here because there were only a total of 99 players that were at this level range. Even if all 99 players were there, with them scattered around the vast lake, it was very unlikely for them to coincidentally meet.

However, the top guilds had already begun shadowing Thousand Creations long before he set out for the leveling area. The shadowers verified that Thousand Creations was the target and then gave out his coordinates.

“Coordinates 2568, 4653. The target is currently over there.”

The players, who were following Thousand Creations, quietly reported back and then spread the word to the dispatched troops.

Changing Spring and Blue River, these guild leaders, personally joined in on the operation and were currently headed towards the target. With the two face-to-face, Changing Spring was no longer so cold.

“Has anything happened recently?” Changing Spring asked Blue River.

“Nothing much. I’m just a bit tired.” Blue River said.

“So you’ve been on that other account the other time? How’s Guild Happy doing?” Changing Spring asked.

“Their development has been going very steadily.” Blue River said.

“With Ye Qiu leading, I doubt they’d make any low-level mistakes.” Changing Spring said.

‘Yeah.” Blue River nodded his head.

“He really isn’t easy to deal with.” Changing Spring sighed. Blue River didn’t follow up though.

“We’re almost there.” Comrade Bound Boat said. For this operation, the top guilds sent out their elite members. This was because Thousand Creations himself wasn’t easy to deal with and they also suspected that Ye Qiu had something prepared against them. They hoped to use this opportunity to create a huge wave, the bigger the better, and directly topple Guild Happy.

“Over there. It’s Thousand Creations!” Thundering Light saw Thousand Creations.

Chapter 366 – Waiting for the Ambush

The shore of Thousand Waves Lake mostly had amphibians as monsters crawling around. Thousand Creations was currently hunting these monsters. Changing Spring’s group consisted of a total of five players, just like a standard dungeon party. They were hiding in a small forest along the shore. But no one rushed out after Thundering Light shouted, though.

“Let’s observe for a bit before we do anything.” Changing Spring said.

All five took his advice and crouched down together amongst the trees. Blue River looked around and saw a few brushes on his left rustle slightly, so he lifted his body a tiny bit in order to take a look. He saw a character ID floating up above the brushes and recognized it as one of Herb Garden’s elite members.

“Herb Garden’s over there.” Blue River said to the group.

“Good. It seems like the other guilds’ players have arrived.” Changing Spring said.

“With such a large place, it doesn’t seem like it’s possible to do any large scale preparations!” Bound Boat whispered.

“Could they be in the water?” Thundering Light guessed.

“They can’t hide in there for very long.” Changing Spring said.

In Glory, all characters were born with the ability to swim. However, when they dive into the water, they would only be able to hold their breath for so long. If they continued to stay underwater after running out of air, they would eventually drown themselves. How long they could stay underwater depended on the character’s Stamina. However, no matter the case, it wasn’t possible to stay underwater forever, so it would be very easy to tell whether or not there was an ambush waiting in the water. Thousand Waves Lake had numerous ripples along its body of water, but there were no signs of any heads popping out.

“What do you think?” Changing Spring spoke in the channel.

This was said in the team channel, where each party that was inside was from a different guild. Each guild had sent out around five players and all of them were amongst the top hundred, highest-level players in the tenth server. As for guilds without these high-level players, they weren’t interested in participating in the interference of Guild Happy at this time.

“We haven’t found anything.” Herb Garden replied.

“Nothing here.” Tyrannical Ambition followed.

“Same.”

“+1.”

“+2.”

The several guilds were each at different positions, encircling Thousand Creation. Everyone was looking around for anything suspicious, but they didn’t find anything.

“Could Guild Happy not have made any arrangements?” Someone said.

“If it were me, this is a very bad spot to make any arrangements! What level are their guild members? If they were to come here, let alone be able to PK, the monsters alone would make it difficult for them.” Another player said.

This was very logical. Thousand Waves Lake had Level 40-43 monsters, while the majority of players in Guild Happy were still in Level 30 range. Even with the newly added, higher-level players, they were still at an average of Level 36 or 37. Weren’t the only ones who could level here be their players? Aside from them, all other tenth server players would be underleveled here.

“Seems like we were overly worried.” Herb Garden’s Arisaema concluded.

“D*mnit!” Jiang You couldn’t help but curse. If they had known that the other side hadn’t made any preparations, they wouldn’t have needed so many people. It was true that Thousand Creations was a top-tier player in the game, but the players that were here wouldn’t lose to him. A small party was enough to accomplish this without any casualties, yet they had sent out tens of players to come.

“Wait a moment.” Changing Spring unexpectedly said.

“Let’s wait a bit longer. Our movements might have been too quick and perhaps Guild Happy hasn’t finished their arrangements, yet. We should wait a bit longer. We might be able to catch them in an ambush while they’re arriving.” Blue Brook Guild’s Bound Boat explained what Changing Spring meant.

Everyone listened and felt that he was right. They weren’t worried at all for Guild Happy’s ambush. In fact, they were more afraid that the other side wouldn’t ambush them. Right now, everyone was quiet. They were somewhat impatient, but if they waited and something big happened, their trip wouldn’t have been in vain.

As a result, everyone continued to stay silent for a while longer. Thousand Creations was no longer the focus anymore. Their focus was on their surroundings for any signs of movement. More importantly, they conveyed orders to the entire guild to pay attention to Guild Happy’s movements. In particular, if they saw Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Soft Mist or any other elites from Guild Happy, they were to immediately report back.

However, after half an hour, not a single report came back.

“Alright, everything should be good now!” Arisaema said.

“Our opponent is still Ye Qiu. If he noticed something wasn’t right, he wouldn’t be this slow right?” Jiang You said. Even though they didn’t feel good about Ye Qiu, they couldn’t underestimate Ye Qiu’s ability.

“Yeah……” Changing Spring had no choice but to agree.

Only Blue River was startled. This was because he clearly knew that Ye Qiu had predicted this would happen. But why did it seem like he hadn’t made any preparations? He couldn’t understand. In his eyes, without any good methods to counter them, he still could have had Thousand Creations go offline temporarily. There was nothing they could do about that. However, nothing was going as he had imagined it would go. He had warned Changing Spring previously, but Changing Spring had clearly regarded Blue River’s warning as a type of analysis. Changing spring didn’t know that this warning had come directly from the target. Blue River didn’t know what to do or say. If he explained himself, he would reveal his misdeeds and it would truly be quite awkward!

But this time, they didn’t give him any time to stay conflicted. Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You had run out of patience long ago. Seeing that no one had any new suggestions, he immediately said: “Then what are we waiting for? Let’s move! We’ve already wasted so much time for this little punk. Have those at the respawn point get ready.”

After sending out the messages, the guilds began to move. If it was only Thousand Creations as their opponent, there would be nothing they would need to worry about. They could kill him however they’d liked.

The guild players came out from their hiding spots and rushed out. They didn’t present themselves as powerful or shout anything out. For something as easy as this, there was no need for it. It would only make them look stupid.

The long-range Gunners began firing and Thousand Waves Lake’s silence was broken. The monsters crawling around were immediately alarmed. They didn’t need to be concerned about them, though. The only thing they needed to focus on was Thousand Creations, who reacted very quickly. Hearing the gunshots, he immediately ran and jumped into the lake.

“He really is Thousand Creations!” Blue Brook Guild’s players couldn’t help but say after seeing Thousand Creations’s quick reactions.

“Humph……” Blue Brook Guild’s Lunar Grace immediately humphed in disdain. She was a female player and was disgusted by Thousand Creations’s bullying. She knew why the other Blue Brook Guild members commented with a hint of lament. It was because Thousand Creations’s nasty hobby had trained him to be very alert. In the Heavenly Domain, there were quite a few players who wanted to kill him as soon as there was any sign of him, so he was very used to people coming to PK. In addition, because of his agreement with Blue Brook Guild, the guild wouldn’t help him out of these types of situations, so he was used to dealing with this alone. There were times where he survived and there were times where he died. Though in the end, Thousand Creations had a lot of experience with this sort of situation.

As soon as the offensive began, Thousand Creations didn’t hesitate and immediately rushed into Thousand Waves Lake. He had clearly known that there weren’t any ambushes waiting there.

But the guild players weren’t worried. Going down was just going down. Everyone could do it. They could just continue chasing. So what? They were all experienced experts, too. The guild leaders were all better than Thousand Creations, too, so there was nothing to be afraid of.

“Don’t let him escape!” Jiang You impatiently roared. He was still using the Crowd Lover Elementalist and waved his staff as he chased. A Frost Ball shot out from his staff and chased after Thousand Creations.

The other guild players also used their methods. Those who could attack, attacked while those who had crowd control, used their crowd control. Those who had to close in to attack had to spring faster. Players rushed at him in many different directions. They predicted Thousand Creations’s movements and made preparations for where he would go.

“Over there.” Jiang You’s Frost Ball hadn’t connected, but he continued to chase, while directing others to attack.

They were all experienced veterans. They didn’t need to hear all the details. They only needed to know the timing. As soon as Jiang You’s words came out, Tyrannical Ambition’s four other players split paths. Two players headed straight into the water, while the other two headed towards where Thousand Creations was predicted to go in order to cut him off.

The other guilds had their own thoughts. In only a short moment, half of the players had already gone into the water. The originally rippling surface of Thousand Waves Lake began to spray out splashes, as the players ran into the lake like torpedoes with their target as Thousand Creations, who was swimming frantically.

“Long-range people, block him!” Jiang You shouted. He was more direct and didn’t care about the other guilds hearing. In any case, if there was something that he needed to do, he would order it.

The long-range Gunners didn’t dive down in a hurry and instead, fired at Thousand Creations.

This was a maneuver that required experience. In the water, the characters would never be still and would be constantly bobbing up and down. In particular, with so many players jumping in, the waves were large and the bobbing would be more intense. In this situation, aiming accurately was very difficult. As a result, they stayed on shore, where the land was steady and fired happily before doing anything.

As if sensing the threat, Thousand Creations suddenly plunged downwards and his character dove into the water. The others looked and did the same. If not, then when Thousand Creations went down, they wouldn’t be able to see where he would be going.

Who knew that at this moment, a huge wave suddenly rose up along with a boom right after. The wave swept up one of the players high up into the air……..

Chapter 367 – Waves

What’s going on!!

Everyone was practically in the same area, which saved them some time because they wouldn’t need to type out their messages in the team channel and instead, could directly shout their words for everyone to hear. The instant the player was lifted into the air by the waves, the scene erupted into shouts, as if a pot had exploded.

But no matter how many shouts there were, they wouldn’t be able to cover up the rapid firing that followed after.

“Ta ta ta ta ta……..” Amidst the sounds of shooting were also the sounds of the waves surging forward. Countless bullets broke out from beneath the water, flying straight for the player who was tossed into the air.

“There are players beneath the water!!!” someone shouted. Thousand Waves Lake only had amphibious creatures and water beasts. It was impossible for them to have any gun abilities. Only players could have done it.

“No way!!” someone cried out in astonishment. They had been carefully observing their surroundings for about half an hour and they hadn’t seen any signs of players underwater. But somebody suddenly appeared in the water and this person definitely wasn’t Thousand Creations. How did he escape from everyone’s eyes?

“This…….. This……..” Bound Boat from Blue Brook Guild suddenly stuttered.

“Say it.” Changing Spring continued to chase as he shouted.

“This seems like a type of rarely seen technique!” Bound Boat said.

“What is it?”

“I can’t remember the name, but it was specially used for battles in the water. The character hid underwater and would come up for air from time to time, using the wave’s spray as a cover. When it first appeared, it was used for sneak attacks in underwater battles. But because it required users to be very close to the surface of the water, as long as one was careful, it would be extremely easy to see through it. The practicality of it was greatly weakened, so it slowly died out.” Bound Boat said.

“I seem to remember something like that……” Changing Spring was surprised.

“Even though the technique has died out, it’s still a pro-level technique…….” Bound Boat said.

“So that’s Lord Grim!” Changing Spring said darkly.

During their discussion, the other players went underwater to find the reason why, when suddenly, they saw blood spray out as three players were sent out of the water.

In underwater battles, many of the skills’ effects are different in water than they are on the ground. The players weren’t able to tell what skills had been used to send those three players out of the water. But they were, at least, able to see what was lurking underwater.

“Lord Grim!”

“Cleansing Mist!”

The submerged players cursed in the team chat, “F*CK!” After receiving the information, all the others cursed as well, because the weight of these names were too heavy. Ye Qiu, Su Mucheng. In the pro scene, they were considered to be the very best duo. Even though they had dozens of players, they still weren’t confident in fighting these two. For a moment, the players who had been standing happily above the water stopped moving, as if they had agreed by chance. Against these two, they weren’t sure whether they should fight or not. They hoped to receive clear orders from above.

“Splash! Splash! Splash!”

“Splash!” After three consecutive splashes, another splash sounded as a fourth player was sent out of the water.

In the water, there was also a Quick Recover move. However, the effects were different. It wasn’t a roll on the surface of the water. All it did was stabilize the character and slowed the character’s speed after hitting the water, so they weren’t like a rock that would drop to the bottom of the body of water.

Quick Recovering on the ground was something these elite players were very adept at. However, in the water, there really weren’t many of them who had gone through specialized training for it. All four players failed their Quick Recovers, one after the other. Four splashes as the four shot towards the bottom of the lake. This effect was similar to that of getting knocked down onto the ground. Only after a while did the four finally stabilize themselves and began heading towards the surface of the water. But then they suddenly saw numerous bubbles float up and turned their heads only to see a laser beam shooting towards them. Su Mucheng’s Launcher had sent out a Laser Rifle.

It was a game, so unless stated otherwise, any skill could be used in the water. It was just that the effects would be different because of the difference in the environment. Most of the skills simply had reduced speed in the water.

However, the Launcher’s Laser Rifle didn’t seem to have this reduction and was as fast as ever. The movements of the characters were slowed in the water, though, and they couldn’t move as quickly when compared to the times they were on the ground. How could they dodge this attack?

The light from the underwater Laser Rifle could even be seen by those above the surface of the lake. The refraction and reflection of the glowing light made the scene look like a light show. It looked even more impressive underwater than it was on the ground.

These four players were blasted into tanghulu. They weren’t dead, but the damage they took wasn’t light.

The four were already confused and disoriented, when suddenly a figure quickly swam to their sides and sent out a skill.

The four could see the skill coming at them slowly and felt like they could dodge for sure. But they had forgotten that even though their opponent’s skill moved slowly, their movements were slow as well. Their eyes and hands were quick, but their characters’ movements lagged behind. The skill that they thought they could dodge with certainty, connected.

“What’s going on over there?” The players above the water didn’t know what was going on.

They just saw the four characters drop into the water, get hit by the Laser Rifle, and then saw the part of the water continuously surge, as if it were boiling.

It looked like they were dumplings going into the pan; the laser rifle was the fire and the water was now boiling…….

“Help…….” Just when they were still pondering over how these dumplings were being cooked, someone in the team chat suddenly asked for help. Honestly speaking, they didn’t see clearly which individuals had been turned into dumplings. They only saw that the situation seemed off. There was no need to question it, though. Even though their bosses hadn’t told them whether or not to continue fighting, with players crying for help, how could they just sit idly and ignore them?

The players in the water dove down and looked towards that direction. All they could see was that that area of water had already become like a flood. They couldn’t even see how many people were over there. They hastily swam over there, when suddenly, they saw a flash of white light. Everyone was startled. They looked at their team list and sure enough, one of them had left the team, meaning he had been killed.

“Hurry forward!” With one now dead, everyone immediately understood the situation. As a result, this player began to urge them to hurry up.

But during this time, white light continued to flash again and again amidst the storm of waves. Finally, the waves stopped and the lake water stilled. All that was left was a single character standing: Lord Grim.

The four died just like that?

Everyone stared blankly. They were suddenly afraid of going up to fight.

They had originally been going up to rescue them, but now that there was no one to rescue, if they went up now, wouldn’t that just be asking to die?

Everyone stopped and couldn’t help but look around left and right. But after looking, they realized that they had around thirty players. Against one person, why had they been so scared?

Thinking of this, everyone began to feel embarrassed. Even if the opponent was God Ye Qiu, with so many of them, there really was no reason to be afraid.

Some of them were still thinking, while some had already begun shouting in the team channel: “There’s only one person. It doesn’t matter who it is. Everyone go forward!!”

As soon as the message dropped, several players began to shoot forward. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim didn’t wait there like an idiot, either. After killing four players, he was beginning to run out of air, so he immediately headed towards the surface.

“Stop him! Don’t let him go up to the surface!” Someone figured out what he was doing and immediately realized that Lord Grim didn’t have enough air. As long as they stopped him from going up to get air, they wouldn’t even need to fight to win. They could just let him drown himself to death.

Two figures immediately appeared above Lord Grim, blocking his path to air. These were two Ninja classes. They used the Shadow Clone Technique to instantly move to their location, in order to block him.

Lord Grim’s hands extended out and threw a grenade. The explosion wasn’t as large in the water, but the waves began to surge again and the two Ninjas, along with Lord Grim, were sent up above the water. It was just that while the two Ninjas were blown up above the water, Lord Grim had swam up to get air.

Lord Grim didn’t stop to rest. Sending a spear to the left and a sword to the right, he attacked the two Ninjas. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist seemed to have been waiting, bobbing up and down with a cannon on her shoulders. This sort of bobbing up and down wouldn’t affect a pro player’s accuracy, though, as the cannon shots caused the two Ninjas to continue to roll up above the surface of the water.

“Hello? Don’t just stand there watching!” Ye Xiu suddenly shouted.

On the surface of the water, a character’s head stuck out, staring blankly at the scene. On his head was the name ‘Thousand Creations’.

“These are for you!” Lord Grim suddenly shot out his palm and one of the Ninjas flew towards Thousand Creations.

“Since you know how to bully little noobs for monsters, you can do harsher things, too, right?” Ye Xiu said after sending Thousand Creations an opponent. His Lord Grim suddenly jumped, though it wasn’t very high because he was in the water. But with this, he was able to dodge the numerous attacks from below him. He then spread out his hands and tossed another hand grenade.

“F*CK!!” The players who had just gotten their heads out of the water saw the hand grenade dropping towards them and hastily tried to run, but how could they move so quickly in the water?

“Bang!” Another wave lifted these bunch of players to the side. “Splash!” And Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim ferociously shot back into the water.

Chapter 368 – Massacre by Drowning

Grenade was only a low-level Spitfire skill. Even though it dealt AoE damage, the damage it dealt was very low. However, it was still very effective for clearing the area because it had an extremely short cooldown. The explosion created by the Grenade could be seen even more clearly in the water.

In the water, the characters were pushed all around, up, down, left, right. The waves on the surface of the water turned over and the characters who were about to reach the surface were then pushed away by the shockwaves from the explosion. Afterwards, they heard the sound of someone entering the water over and over again and then, there was a sudden flash of cold light.

Ye Xiu used Quick Recover once he entered the water. He was in complete control of Lord Grim's movements. As soon as he went under, he immediately drew his sword with a Sword Draw. The sword light slashed through the water, lifting a series of bubbles. The sword's speed in the water couldn't compare with its speed on land, but against these characters underwater, there still wasn't a single one who could dodge it.

Lord Grim flipped his body and shot his palm downwards. Falling Flower Palm's Blow Away effect was reduced in the water, but because it pushed the water, the palm's attack range was increased. Below, five players were pushed down towards the bottom of the lake.

None of the troops that were sent to kill Thousand Creations were weak. They were all elites from the top guilds. Either through personal experience or through spectating others fighting Lord Grim, they suddenly understood one thing: in the water, the difference between Lord Grim and them was even larger.

This was because the water was a special environment. In water, all the numbers and skill effects were different. These elites weren't too experienced in this area because there weren't many quests or dungeons in the game that had to be completed in the water. Even for the ones that did require it, it would only be a small portion. It was only against an NPC, too, so as long as they grasped the strategy for it, they were able to pass it easily. As a result, they didn't really have much experience in an actual underwater battle.

Ye Xiu was different, though. He had a background as a pro player, so he would have gone through specialized training for all sorts of situations. For water battles, pro matches had water maps that they could choose from. Some teams were even good at water battles and chose water maps in order to create an advantage for themselves. As a result, any pro player would have done their research and practiced for water battles. At the very least, they couldn't be like normal players and continue fighting in the water as if they were on land.

As a result, compared to a top-tier pro, they were basically a bunch of noobs.

Everyone immediately felt terrified, when suddenly, another sound resounded out. Countless waves stirred, dealing damage and sweeping them away. They turned around to look and saw that Cleansing Mist was underwater. The cannon shot that she fired had created a swirling whirlpool, sucking in the surrounding water.

Only then did they realize that there wasn't only one person who saw them as noobs, but two.

"What do we do?" Everyone already had their own thoughts on what to do in this situation, but they couldn't help but ask for instructions from their higher-ups.

At this moment, the higher-ups were undoubtedly suffering the most. They were all experts, so they knew better than anyone else that the situation wasn't looking good. They hadn't thought that the opponents would use their advantage of experience in water battles. This.... This was bullying!

The guild leaders wanted to cry, but no tears came out. They had already lost four players. If they continued to fight, there would certainly be more deaths. Even more important was that even if they got an advantage, without any real experience in this area, if their opponents couldn't beat them, they would simply retreat. Could they stop them from running?

No confidence. None of them had any confidence.

The guild leaders quietly discussed this as the struggle in the water continued. The players terrifyingly discovered a fact. Up until now, Lord Grim had taken the initiative to attack them. What did this mean? This meant that the opponent had absolutely no fear of them. Or perhaps their slight number advantage didn't mean anything to this God when they were in the water.

The several players who attempted to fight with the God only made everyone feel embarrassed for them. Their attacks and skills were sent out as if they were blind and it didn't appear as if Lord Grim had any trouble dodging them. His attacks, on the other hand, connected wherever he wanted them to connect.

"Run away first. Run away first!" One of the players didn't wait for their guild leader's orders and began making his own suggestion. Quite a few immediately followed it and began to retreat.

It couldn't be said that they weren't trying. They had tried really hard. However, fighting in the water was way too different from fighting on the ground. On the ground, they could only move around in a circle that was around them. At most, they had the option to make some jumps. But in the water, there were just too many options that they could make. Surrounding someone required more troops and more planning. They weren't experts at this, so they didn't have any methods to deal with Lord Grim. The other guy was swimming towards them while he was attacking. Every one of them that was in the water had taken damage.

"AH!!" Someone suddenly cried out. Everyone then saw his "AH!!" word bubble on top of his head go towards the surface of the water, ignoring everything else. But very soon, an artillery shell exploded above his head as the waves surged. Not only did they stop him from moving up, they also pushed him down.

This guy completely ignored the attack and, after stabilizing himself, he continued to charge towards the surface of the water. At this moment, the others stopped paying attention to him. But out of the corner of their eyes, just as he was about to hit the surface of the water, he suddenly stopped and began twitching mechanically. Startled, they suddenly understood what was going on!

Drowning! This guy had used up all of his air and had ran out of health. This sort of twitching meant that it was already too late to save him. It was an animation that the character made right before dying to let you know what had happened.

Sure enough, the twitching soon stopped. The character stopped moving and floated to the surface of the water. Not long after, a white light flashed and the player chose to revive at the city. The team had lost another member.

This drowned victim could be considered as a warning to them. The complexion on half of them had turned pale white.

They had been worrying about this and that and had forgotten about paying attention to their air. Those who had paid attention to it thought that this was an extremely basic task and that there was no way they'd forget about it, which was why they hadn't thought of reminding the others. The amount of air they had depended on the character's Stamina, so everyone had a different amount and they couldn't use their own when comparing with other players. Only when one of their players drowned did half of them suddenly realize that they had made an extremely low-level mistake.

These players immediately rushed towards the surface of the water as if it were a competition. However, at this moment, their opponents knew that they had forgotten about this and had a plan. Lord Grim quickly appeared near them. He blew up grenades, sent out palms, and captured them. In short, he used everything at his disposal in order to keep them underwater.

If it was only the damage from these skills, the players wouldn't be concerned. However, Ye Xiu was only using displacement skills. Since they were in the water, a knockback could be used in a downward direction, pushing them down further in the water.

The players made threatening gestures, struggling, while crying out for help in the team channel. It wasn't that the others didn't want to save them, it was just they truly had no way to. They had no way of capturing Lord Grim with his artful maneuvering.

The shouts in the team channel grew more and more anxious. The guild leaders were also extremely worried. They personally went into the water to try and save them, but they weren't able to do much. In the water, their orders seemed to have hundreds of mistakes in them; so much so that they were starting to feel embarrassed about giving out orders.

Not long after, another character began to twitch. He ran out of air and had no health left, so he drowned to death.

Soon, characters began to react one after the other. It was Lord Grim though that began to hurry towards the surface. Seeing this, they immediately understood that Lord Grim wasn't able to hold on any longer, either. They immediately went to chase after him in order to drag him down with them. But at a crucial moment, Cleansing Mist fired an artillery shell at them.

For Launcher skills, as long as there was an explosion, the effects would be even more terrifying in the water than they were on land. The shell exploded behind Lord Grim, sending the waves rolling. Lord Grim was in the same party as her, so he wouldn't be affected by it. This was all a part of the game's rules. The others were different, though. They had no way of counteracting the pushing force of the waves.

Because Lord Grim had to go up for air, a few of the guild elites finally escaped. However, there were at least ten corpses floating underwater. This low-level mistake had already created huge losses for the team.

"Scatter!" Changing Spring typed into the team channel.

Who knew how long these players had been waiting for this command. They didn't care if the order didn't come from their guild's leader. They immediately rushed towards the shore.

As they turned their heads to scatter, they discovered that Lord Grim was still chasing after them. All of the players felt a cold chill. Sure enough! They had originally thought that they had taken the initiative, wondering whether there would be a battle. But from the looks of it now, could this even be called a battle?

The players felt depressed in their hearts. But because of their numbers, Lord Grim's group didn't have enough players to catch them all. Just as they were about to reach the shore, several players suddenly jumped out from their ambush spots in the forest. In the lead was a Brawler. Seeing his Level 30 equipment, they could tell that he was under-leveled and shouldn't be in this leveling area. However, after seeing his ID, their spirits immediately burned to ashes.

Steamed Bun Invasion! This was one of Guild Happy's core experts!

"Ah! Over here! Hurry, hurry! There's so many of them!!!" Everyone heard Steamed Bun Invasion yell.

So many? Is he talking about them?

Chapter 369 – Trapped

As soon as they saw Steamed Bun Invasion, the group of players swimming for their lives towards the shore immediately turned cold. It wasn’t that Steamed Bun Invasion himself was scary, but rather that he had come at a crucial moment, indicating that their opponent had made preparations long beforehand. First, he had lured them into the water and then used the fact that these players weren’t experienced in water battles to teach them a good lesson.

They had finally struggled back to shore, when their opponents appeared onshore to set up an ambush. There weren’t many of them, though; only three. However, the problem was that they had enemies both on land and in the water. Everyone couldn’t help but think of the phrase: to beat a drowning dog.

“CHARGE!!!” Even though there was an unforeseen obstacle in front of them, if they stayed in the water, they would only be killed off by Lord Grim. At this moment, who knew how many of them yelled this out at the same time. The several players, who had already reached the shore, jumped ferociously in order to directly exit the water.

While in the air, they suddenly heard three gunshots, which had come from the nearby grove . Obscured by the trees, the flash from an explosion could be seen and three artillery shells were sent flying over. Still in the air, they had nowhere to run to. They could only brandish their weapons and pray that they could chop down the artillery shells.

In theory, this was possible, but apart from the pros, very few could actually accomplish it. Right now, they were controlling their movements in the air, but they also wanted to hit a high speed artillery shell. These players simply didn’t have the skill to do that.

The three artillery shells connected with the several players that had shot out of the water, instantly exploding. The shockwaves from the blast sent the players flying. Several splashes could be heard. Of the five players who had jumped out, four had been sent directly back into the water.

The fifth person jumped over the explosion. Just as he was feeling proud of himself, he hadn’t yet landed when a Brick hit him from the side. Following Steamed Bun Invasion, Soft Mist rushed forward and thrust forward with a Double Stab. A streak of blood flew through the air and this brother was also sent back into the water with a “Splash!” The difference, though, was that after entering the water, a cloud of red could be seen floating on top of the water. Blood was pouring out. Tang Rou’s Double Stab had hit in the same place twice, causing a Bleed status.

Steamed Bun Invasion. Soft Mist. These two were the brave generals in Lord Grim’s dungeon team. No one dared to look down on them.

Who was that person shooting from the grove? They hadn’t seen him clearly. However, Misty Castle’s players were even more quiet than any other guild. This was because this person made them think of the player who had recently left their guild, Horse Shooter.

There was still one more standing on the shoreside. No one recognized him, but in their eyes, the threat from this person was even greater than the other three. That was because this person was a Summoner. He had already summoned a mob of creatures and had arranged them in a line along the shore, blocking their path from the shore.

Were they not confident in beating the Summoner? These experts wouldn’t go that far, but the main point was that it would waste time! With the summoned creatures in the way, Steamed Bun Invasion and Soft Mist would have time to arrive and throw them back into the water, no?

Another name from their team list faded away. Another had unexpectedly died in the water. The attentive ones immediately discovered that this player was one of the players that had been tossed back into the water. Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist had caught him and he died very quickly.

Behind them were pursuers, and in front of them was a blockade. These guild leaders had experienced many battles before. It wasn’t as if they had never seen this scene before and instantly figured out what advantages would help them escape.

“Scatter!” Changing Spring shouted.

Everyone else immediately followed.

No matter the case, they had the advantage in numbers. Happy’s players were using few to surround many. Even though they had been successful, they couldn’t cover the entire field. If they split up, some might die, but the majority of them would be able to escape.

As a result, the players in the water acted instantly and began swimming either to the left or to the right.

With enemies behind them and enemies in front of them, what other direction could they run in other than left or right?

There was nothing Ye Xiu could do about them splitting up, so he could only split his forces as well. Those in the water would chase after one side, while those on shore would block the other side, but his opponents split up again. No one pulled along any partners with them. It was every man for themselves and their forces became even more scattered.

Tang Rou’s group didn’t go down into the water. They stayed on shore, chasing them. Even these experienced players from the top guilds were like noobs in the water. For players like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, no matter how good their mechanics were, they would need practice before they could do anything in the water. They’d be even more nooby than the guild players.

As for Concealed Light, he didn’t need to be said. The line of summoned creatures on shore, now that was a bluff! In fact, the palms of his hands were drenched in sweat. They had been too cautious. If they had courageously charged at the Summoner, they would have immediately known that these summoned creatures were basically the same as paper. Their controller’s skill level was too poor.

In the end, the blockades onshore wasn’t able to block anything. The players in the water swam along the shore for a bit and then went on their own way. Some turned around to keep swimming. Some continued to swim along the shore. Others even swam into deeper waters. Tang Rou’s group didn’t know who to chase, when Tang Rou suddenly received a message from Ye Xiu: “Chase after the ones who turned around.”

“Okay!”

Tang Rou received the message and called out to everyone to immediately go back and chase after the ones who had turned around to run. As a result, those who hadn’t turned around, waited for a chance to get back onto land.

Tang Rou looked and wanted to turn around to kill them, but Ye Xiu seemed to have guessed what was on her mind and messaged: “Ignore them, keep chasing.”

“Why?” Tang Rou was only controlling her Soft Mist to run along the shore, so she had the time to reply.

“Many players. Hard to fight.” Ye Xiu seemed to be busy, so he didn’t say much.

Tang Rou turned to look. There were already almost ten players that had climbed onto the shore. Tang Rou knew that these were all experts. One on one wouldn’t be a problem, but if there were so many of them, if they had a strategy as well, she didn’t think that she could fight them.

Understanding Ye Xiu’s intent, Tang Rou continued to chase after those who had turned back, along with Steamed Bun Invasion and Concealed Light.

But these players’ minds were quite clear. Seeing that there were players over there that had gotten onto land, they immediately turned around again, heading in the direction where others were getting out of the water, clearly to look for help.

“What do we do?” Tang Rou was at a loss. She had the mechanics, but her ability to think was very far off.

“Keep chasing.” Ye Xiu replied.

Tang Rou immediately told everyone else and then turned around, too.

It hadn’t been easy for those ten or so players to get onto dry land. Seeing Soft Mist’s group running towards them, they immediately began arranging their team. Even though they weren’t at Ye Qiu’s or Su Mucheng’s level, they didn’t dare to look down on them. Last time, when they chased after Lord Grim and the others, Soft Mist had slaughtered her way out of Congee City by herself. They had heard of her might. Even though there hadn’t been any elite experts there at that time, to be able to slaughter her away out of such a large mob, no one dared to say that they had the same level of mechanics and courage as her.

“Hurry, hurry. Heal! Heal!!”

The ten or so players busily ran about in disorder. Some of them had taken damage in the water and were hurriedly urging the Clerics to heal them. The aquatic battle had been so chaotic that, let alone coordination, the Clerics had even forgotten to do even the most basic support.

The Clerics in the team were bustling around and white light swept down. Those who were still in the water gradually grew braver as they saw that they were getting closer to the shore. The ten or so players finished arranging themselves. As a result, they moved forward instead of retreating, rushing towards Tang Rou’s group.

“What now?” Tang Rou asked Ye Xiu.

“Kill!” Ye Xiu replied.

“What? Then why didn’t you let me do that earlier?” Tang Rou asked.

“Then, were you going to let those in the water run away?” Ye Xiu asked back.

“How evil!” Tang Rou said.

“You don’t like it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It’s exactly what I like.” Tang Rou replied with a smiley face.

“Is it going to be a problem?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Perhaps. Maybe a little…..” In the All-Star Weekend, Tang Rou had thoroughly witnessed the phrase: no matter how good you think you are, there is always someone out there that is better. The pros’ mechanics, as well as the coordination in the All-Star Team Competition, had made her a lot more modest. She was slowly discovering the difference between herself and a true expert.

“You can send some back into the water.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ah? You’re in the water?” Tang Rou asked.

“Of course.”

“Where?”

“Not too far from you. Don’t worry about me and just send them my way. Anyone that falls into the water will be mine.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Got it!” Tang Rou closed the message. The ten or so enemies had arrived and several players in the water were preparing to jump out. Tang Rou hadn’t said anything yet, when Steamed Bun Invasion took the initiative and shouted: “Kill! Concealed Light, follow your bro forward!!”

Steamed Bun Invasion’s loud voice had made the ten or so players turn sluggish. They could bear with Soft Mist’s yelling, but this Steamed Bun Invasion was a mere Level 33 and that Summoner Concealed Light was only Level 34. Where did these two brothers get such confidence?

The ten or so players looked around them, puzzled. They knew that the grove had a Launcher hidden somewhere inside. Could there be more players hiding in the grove?

“Uh oh! Could there be more waiting in ambush?” someone directly said.

“There’s no retreat! Let’s go forward first!” another yelled.

The group of three charged forward bravely. The ten or so players continued to cautiously pay attention to the grove and any other place where players could hide in, afraid of an ambush.

“Pu…….”

Because they hadn’t been focused on what was in front of them, one of the ten players was smashed in the face by a Brick from Steamed Bun Invasion.

“F*ck, I thought they were experts.” Steamed Bun Invasion smacked a Brick in one of their faces and then even looked down on them.

“F*cker!” The Berserker that was hit by the Brick immediately turned furious. He lifted his Greatsword and crashed towards them with a Collapsing Mountain.

Chapter 370 – A Bit Too Few

“Dodge!”

Tang Rou called as her Soft Mist rolled to the right. Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t slow, either. He rolled to the left and dodged it beautifully.

“F*ck!” Comrade Concealed Light gave out a firm shout and was knocked to the ground by the Collapsing Mountain. The ground onshore was soft and immediately caved in to form the figure of a person. Concealed Light had been pressed into the ground by the Greatsword. His arms and legs were still struggling! It wasn’t as if he didn’t want to dodge, but his fingers were too slow. He had probably only started moving when the attack hit him, so even though he was on the ground already, his hands and arms were still twitching!

“Ha ha ha ha, you suck!” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed out loud. He didn’t move slowly, though, and immediately went up to rescue him, clawing towards the Berserker’s throat with a Strangle.

The Berserker wasn’t slow, either. He immediately jumped backwards in order to try and dodge, but just happened to leap into Soft Mist’s attack range. Tang Rou had been prepared to attack. As soon as she saw that her enemy had delivered himself to her, she didn’t even bother stepping forward to welcome him. She shot out a palm towards his back and Falling Flower Palm blew him away. The Berserker had just escaped from the lake, but he was now heading back.

“Ah! Why’d you hit him into the water? What do we do, now?” Steamed Bun Invasion saw the Berserker get sent flying and asked in regret.

These words were like a gust of cold wind towards the ten or so players. His voice didn’t sound like he was bluffing! It sounded as if he was very confident in cleaning them up.

“Could it be…… that this Steamed Bun Invasion is another pro God?” someone suddenly raised a terrifying notion. This notion seemed rational and logical. If there was a Ye Qiu and a Su Mucheng, why wouldn’t there be another God?

Everyone there had seen Steamed Bun Invasion’s name on the standings before. Even though a few of them had fought with him before, because of how eye catching Lord Grim was, his teammates would have been outshined to a certain extent. The guilds hadn’t done too much research on Steamed Bun yet. They only knew that he definitely wasn’t weak. And now with Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist’s true identities exposed, Steamed Bun Invasion……. They were thinking about this from this perspective.

“I don’t think so……” someone said.

“Your reason?” “The name is…… too stupid, isn’t it? What type of Brawler expert has such a stupid sounding name?” These experienced players were familiar with the majority of Brawlers in the pro scene. They didn’t remember any weird names similar to “Steamed Bun Invasion”.

This group of players had been shaken by Steamed Bun Invasion. During their moment of hesitation, Concealed Light had climbed back out and was mercilessly made fun of by Steamed Bun Invasion. His words left Concealed Light speechless.

“You should just stay behind me and watch the show!” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted, making the ten or so experts go blank…… Just how strong was this guy?

“Let’s try first. At worst, one of us dies!” There was still one brave hero amidst the ten or so players. He didn’t think that they needed to be so scared. He shouted and then rushed forward. But he hadn’t even closed in yet, when the team received a notification. Another person had left the team.

“What’s going on!” This brave hero froze in fear. He turned his head to look back. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven……. Everyone was still there!

He then turned back to look at Steamed Bun Invasion……

“Pu!”

A Brick smashed into his face.

“F*CK!” The Brick couldn’t stop him from cursing out loud. The Brick covering his mouth was only a visual effect.

Steamed Bun Invasion moved nimbly and quickly circled behind him.

“Kick him into the lake!” Tang Rou shouted.

“Why?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked, but Steamed Bun Invasion’s biggest strength was that he would ask why, but he didn’t need to finish hearing the explanation to perform the task. He asked, while comboing an Uppercut into a Knee Attack to the back,sending the brave hero back into the water.

“There’s a BOSS inside the water.” Tang Rou replied calmly.

“BOSS, then we should go and kill it!” Steamed Bun Invasion said excitedly.

“We can’t. The BOSS is on the same team as us.” Tang Rou said.

Steamed Bun Invasion was still confused, but their enemies already understood. They realized that Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng were still hiding in the water beside them.

“There really is an ambush waiting!!” one of them yelled. They suddenly lost all will to fight, but how could Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion let them go? They rushed forward and attacked.

A few of the players in the water had originally been hoping to wait for a good opportunity to go up onto land, but now they knew that danger had been all around them the entire time. They tried to hurry onto land as fast as they could, but then they heard something come out of the water. They turned their heads to see two hand grenades, one on their left and one on their right, arcing above their heads. The grenades landed in front of them and exploded……

The waves pushed them into the BOSS’s embrace. They tried to resist, but it was useless. Dozens of players had been helpless against Ye Qiu in the water. What could the few of them do?

The players onshore may have lost two players, but against Tang Rou’s group, their numbers advantage was still obvious. However, once they knew that Ye Qiu was nearby and seeing that the other side’s plan was to send them into the water, these ten or so players lost all hope. They no longer had any thoughts of fighting them. Their only thought was to run away. Once they started running, Tang Rou’s group couldn’t do anything because they had too few members. They could only do their best to chase. In order to save precious time, they didn’t try and kill them and instead tried to toss them into the water.

In terms of raw mechanics, these players couldn’t compare to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. However, in terms of their familiarity with Glory, they were far superior. Right now, they were completely defenseless, fearful of the God’s presence.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion tried their hardest, but had only been able to toss five of the players back into the water. Concealed Light had initially been extremely nervous facing all of these high-level players, but who would have thought that these guys wouldn’t even fight back? It let even him show off his might.

Concealed Light wanted to give out a good performance, but his skill level was truly too low. These experienced players simply reacted out of instinct and Concealed Light was helpless against them. The players were already in complete disorder, though. They didn’t even notice how bad this Summoner was.

“We can’t catch them!” After tossing five into the water, the other four had already ran far away. Tang Rou could only regretfully report.

“It’s not over until the very last moment! We shouldn’t give up!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Then you go chase them!” Concealed Light mocked. His skills in battle were terrible, but his judgement was very good.

“It’s the very last moment now! I declare: give up!” Steamed Bun Invasion solemnly said.

“Idiot!” Concealed Light turned around to watch the water battle.

“F*ck, how can you talk to your senior like that? I don’t want to talk to you anymore. I’ll throw you into the waters to feed the BOSS, you hear!” Steamed Bun Invasion chased after him.

The three stood together on the shoreside, but they could only see the rolling waves. The characters were underwater, so they couldn’t see what was going on very clearly.

From time to time, a player’s head would come up, but from their observations, anyone whose head came up was dead.

Up until now, three players had shown their heads. Everything under them was a cloud of white light.

“What type of BOSS is this? It’s so strange…….” Steamed Bun Invasion thought.

Tang Rou was speechless. This brother still didn’t understand what she had meant. He was still thinking it was an actual wild BOSS.

Concealed Light, on the other hand, was enjoying Steamed Bun Invasion’s stupidity and didn’t tell him that he was wrong.

“Careful!” A huge wave suddenly rose up from the water. Inside the wave was a figure. Steamed Bun Invasion shouted while jumping forward to protect the two of them.

Against an unknown danger, Steamed Bun Invasion stood firm. Tang Rou saw that the figure in the wave wasn’t their ally, but by the time she realized this, Steamed Bun Invasion had already moved.

This was completely instinct. Tang Rou reckoned that Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t seen clearly what had come out. If Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had jumped out, then that would be hilarious.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s fingers were as precise as ever. He sent out a kick with an Eagle Stamp.

With the double stamp, Steamed Bun Invasion somersaulted back to shore. That brother had naturally been smashed back into the water by Steamed Bun Invasion. As he fell, the three heard a “F*CK YOUR SISTER!”

The brother that fell back in was really bitter!

They weren’t their opponents in the water and Ye Qiu’s and Su Mucheng’s golden duo were extremely terrifying. The dozens of players couldn’t contain them, but the duo had a very easy time containing them. They had already lost their will to fight long ago. They only wanted to run. They tried their hardest. Three of them had died to give this player a chance to escape onto shore, but as soon as he got out of the water, the tips of his toes hadn’t even touched the ground, when a little punk onshore had kicked him back in.

“Beautiful!!” In the water, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim showed his head, praising Steamed Bun Invasion.

However, amidst the roaring waves, although they could hear him, they couldn’t see him.

“Huh? Did I hear senior’s voice!” Steamed Bun Invasion stared stupidly!

“Yeah! They’re in the water!”

“Ah? Senior is fighting the BOSS?” Steamed Bun Invasion cried out in astonishment.

Tang Rou thought for a bit, but didn’t say anything. She was afraid that she wouldn’t be able to explain her analogy to Steamed Bun Invasion to make him understand.

“I want to watch!” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted and jumped into the water, but not longer after, he came back and said to Tang Rou and Concealed Light: “The BOSS is already dead. Senior is fighting with the ones who stole the BOSS. The water feels so weird. It was just like senior said before. We can’t really help him, so we’ll just stand guard here! If anyone comes up, we’ll send them back in.”

Steamed Bun Invasion said and used an Eagle Stamp to demonstrate, wasting his cooldown.

“Me too!” Tang Rou said and jumped into the water. She wanted to see what was so different about fighting in the water than on ground like Ye Xiu had said.

But she didn’t even get the chance to sink deeper! The surface of the water split apart and Lord Grim’s and Su Mucheng’s heads came out.

“Done?” Tang Rou’s Soft Mist asked with half of her body in the water.

“Done.” Ye Xiu said. “A bit too few, though!”

Chapter 371 – No Results

“There was nothing we could have done.” Tang Rou was helpless, “Those were all that we could chase down.”

“Chase?” Ye Xiu was concentrated on his battle in the water, so he wasn’t too clear on the situation that was happening above the water. He still had a general idea on the number of players, though. Their opponents were the guild elites. They had dozens of players and they were up against Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion as well as Concealed Light, who could pretty much be ignored. They actually ran?

“Ha ha ha, how smart of them.” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed.

Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s characters walked out of the lake. Thousand Creations followed behind them. After making their landing on the shore, they looked around and realized that they could still see the silhouettes of players who hadn’t completely escaped yet. As for Thousand Waves Lake, besides them, there was no one else. Steamed Bun Invasion and Concealed Light were underleveled over here. If they aggroed any monsters, it would be troublesome for them. It could be said that Concealed Light had been very nervous the entire time.

“What about Horse Shooter?’ Steamed Bun Invasion headed to the grove to look.

“I told him to leave first.” Ye Xiu said.

In the grove were players from the top guilds. After escaping from the lake, they didn’t actually run very far. Instead, they went into any hiding places they could find. There was a bit of distance between here and the lake, so they wanted to continue observing Happy’s plans. If there were any actual dangers, there would still be enough time for them to run away.

At the same time, they took note of the hidden Launcher in the groves. Misty Castle’s players had already confessed, saying that this person was most likely the player who had recently left their guild, Horse Shooter. As a result, after rushing into the grove, the players searched for this player, but there were no signs of him.

A great battle had taken place. There were those who were tossed into the water and those who ran away. Notifications soon popped up repeatedly in their team channel. Not a single player who had been tossed into the water had survived.

None of the guild leaders had died, but their moods were even worse than those who had died.

Their operation at Thousand Waves Like had officially come to an end. Not only did they not obtain any results, but 29 players had died in the water, which was almost half of their troops.

The remaining half were currently hiding in the grove brushes near the lake. The reflections from the computer screens revealed expressions of constipation from these players. They quietly watched as Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, and their target for this operation, Thousand Creations, walk out of the water unharmed. The six players on the shore were chatting with each other happily.

They then looked at themselves and saw the ones who hadn’t been chased down by Steamed Bun Invasion’s group of three join them in their miserable states.

“Too mean!” The players that came gave a detailed account of what had happened to them.

“Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng were hiding in the water and told the guys onshore to push us in!” one player said.

“You guys have so many people. There’s only three of them. How could they just push you around as they pleased?” someone asked.

“Uh….. that…….” The players who had just escaped were at a loss. Right? What was up with that? They couldn’t think of an answer for it.

“What now?” another asked.

No one said anything. The guild leaders were all here. There was no need for them to discuss with one another.

What now?

The guild leaders were nervously discussing this issue.

“With only these few players, if we fight with them head to head, we might not be worthy of being their opponents.” Jiang You said. He had some experience fighting against them and each one had ended in a complete and utter failure. Even with their entire squad dying, they hadn’t been able to take a single one of their lives.

“Even if we can, we can’t. If they go into the water, what can we do?” Arisaema said.

“This is the perfect leveling place for them, too. If they stay here and level, five days later, they can just swim over to the dungeon……..” Changing Spring had predicted what everyone didn’t want to hear.

“F*CK!” All the guild leaders cursed.

“Let’s leave for now. From a long-term perspective, there’s no point in sitting here, waiting like idiots.” Arisaema said and turned around to leave the grove.

Once he moved, the other Herb Garden players naturally followed. The others didn’t have any other suggestions, so they left, too.

“It seems like killing them here will be difficult. We can only have our players in other leveling areas be aware and see if we can catch them somewhere else.” The guild leaders continued to discuss as they retreated.

“The problem is if they stay here to level and refuse to leave. What do we do then?” Changing Spring said.

Everyone was silent.

Issues, such as their supplies and repairing their equipment, weren’t brought up. If they were lone heroes, they might be forced to return to the city because of these difficulties. However, since they were all in the same guild and the same team, these wouldn’t be an issue for them. They could just ask someone else to do it. Although they wanted to completely cut off their supply, no guild had that type of control, no matter how big they were.

The players left the Thousand Waves Lake leveling area. They had walked for awhile, but they still hadn’t come up with any ideas. Someone suddenly asked: “Where are we going now?”

The guild leaders at the front heard this and all stared blankly. After pondering for a bit, they said in a not so confident voice: “The city?”

“Why the city? Is there something we need to do?” someone asked.

The guild leaders’ faces were almost about to fall off. The operation resulted them in returning to the city in tatters. They had nothing to show for it. It was truly quite embarrassing.

“SHUT UP! SHUT UP!” The guild leader of the curious player immediately shouted at him in private.

“Nothing for now.” Changing Spring said quite calmly. They hadn’t come up with any plans after discussing this entire way. He believed that even if they continued discussing all the way back to the city, they still wouldn’t be able to come up with anything.

“If there’s nothing to do , then why don’t we go level?” someone suggested.

When the guild players leveled up, they usually did so in teams. If they went to go and level, they would obviously leave from their current team. But if they left now, it would reveal which players were from which guilds.

“Go ahead. We’ll disperse first.” Changing Spring was too lazy to argue. He was this team’s leader, so he immediately dispersed the team. As a result, the parties began to separate with each unit being from a different guild.

With this dispersion, each team had two or three players. They then scattered and the place turned empty.

“That can’t just be it, can it?” The team had dispersed and everyone had scattered. But the group chat outside of the game was still there. Arisaema went over there to talk.

“If you have any methods, say it.” Jiang You was clearly agitated.

Arisaema was silent. If he had any methods, he would have said them earlier.

“Tell us if anything happens.” Changing Spring concluded. He was saying that they should discuss again after something happens. If not, then there was no point in wasting their time.

As a result, the group chat went silent. After the team dispersed, the players that had scattered were quiet, as well.

Time went by quickly. Nighttime was the game’s peak with players everywhere. This was also the time when the guild had the most players online. As the guild’s elites, although they had been gathered together previously to be soldiers, in the guild, they were all of high status and had their own responsibilities. They quickly got busy.

In the blink of an eye, the early morning came and the number of players online decreased.

After the guild developed, the guild leaders and elites couldn’t only level. There would always be a few guild tasks that they had to take care of. For example, killing Thousand Creations. Even though they had completely failed, it was still a task from the guild that they had to take care of.

During these early morning hours, these players could finally have time to concentrate on leveling. The dungeon counts refreshed. They formed parties and began to head to the dungeons to begin.

Changing Spring and others like him had run over the new server to handle the issues here. They obviously wouldn’t do any leveling. They weren’t online in the tenth server right now and were on their main accounts in the Heavenly Domain.

“How depressing!” Jiang You suddenly yelled in the group chat.

This group chat had even more people online than before. Jiang You and the other Three Great Guild leaders weren’t the only ones there. Guilds like Misty Castle had also joined in after hearing the news.

“Even if you’re depressed, you still have to work!” Howling Height’s guild leader, West Riding Wind, replied. Right now, the Heavenly Domain’s guild leaders were heading to the dungeons.

“Which dungeon are you planning on tackling today?” Misty Castle’s guild leader, Misty Lock asked.

“Floor within a Floor……. We’ve only advanced to 37%.” West Riding Wind said. The Floor within a Floor he was talking about was the largest scale dungeon in the game and would refresh every week. A team, which was a hundred players, could enter each time. The dungeon was extremely difficult. In addition, the battle line was extremely long. Whenever a team tackled the dungeon, they would usually advance to a certain percent each day and save it before continuing on the next day. This was one of the features that was provided by the system for these types of large-scale dungeons.

“37%……. That’s not too good. You’re probably going to be playing the entire night then, no?” Misty Lock said.

“Sigh, even with that, it’ll be difficult. This time, most of our players are from the reserve unit. 22 players have already died at only 37% progress. It would be already be good if we can get to 75%.” West Riding Wind said.

These two guild leaders didn’t care at all about Jiang You’s sigh about the tenth server and went on to discuss about the dungeon in the Heavenly Domain. Even though they were competitors, aside from their arch rival guilds, none of them would turn in disgust when they saw each other. This was more and more like the style in the pro scene. On the field, it was either you die or I die. But outside of the competition, they all looked like friends.

“You two. This group chat isn’t for you to discuss this.” Jiang You clearly wasn’t happy.

“Ha ha, the Three Great Guilds’ leaders are all here! As long as we give you guys our support, it’ll be fine. What can we do!” Misty Lock said.

“Hmph……” Jiang You wasn’t able to say anything and could only type out his emotions.

There wasn’t anything to say. Suddenly, someone gave out a curse. It was only a tenth server guild leader, though, Blossom Valley’s Backlight Bomb. He had typed out an angry face and then followed: “Our dungeon team has been killed!”

Chapter 372 – Another Team Wiped Out

“What’s going on?” The person who replied to Backlight Bomb was Blossom Valley’s main guild leader, Blooming Blossom. With so many guild leaders in the group chat, he didn’t want to appear like he had lost his temper. As a result, even though the bad news was about his guild, he replied calmly, as if he were used to these sorts of gales.

“It’s Lord Grim’s group! They hadn’t left Thousand Waves Lake and when they saw our team, they went up to kill us.” Backlight Bomb said.

“What!?”

Hearing this news, Blooming Blossom hadn’t spoken yet, when Jiang You leaped up.

“This is troublesome!” Arisaema said.

How could the others not understand what he meant by this? The others immediately became worried.

Thousand Waves Lake. After wiping out Blossom Valley’s team, Ye Xiu and his other friends popped up out of the water.

“What do you think? This is more fun than stealing monsters, right?” Ye Xiu said to Thousand Creations.

Thousand Creations didn’t know how to reply, so he sent out a sweating face emoticon. When he stole monsters, it couldn’t be said that he did it because he liked bullying others. As long as he was interested, he wasn’t afraid of stealing from anyone. It was just that stealing monsters from these types of guild elites wasn’t easy. For one, these players wouldn’t be any worse than Thousand Creations and two, these players didn’t usually level alone; they usually leveled together in a group.

In Thousand Creations vast amounts of experience, there had been times where he hadn’t been able to steal a monster and there had also been times when he had been killed after stealing. Of course, he had successfully escaped, too, but that was relatively rare. As for killing all of the players after stealing from them, that was something that he had never done before.

And now, with the God behind him, they didn’t steal monsters. Instead, they directly went to kill the players. Even though it wasn’t without reason, the quality of the players being killed wasn’t normal! The elites from the top guilds could be considered as the top experts of the tenth server. Yet their team of five might not have even been able to tell which direction they were in or when they were killed and turned into corpses.

Thousand Creations, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion had wanted to help. But they hadn’t been able to find a chance to. They simply couldn’t get used to the water yet.

There were two main differences between the battles in the water and the ones on land. First, there were more choices to move. And second, the movement speed in the water was affected.

Getting used to this type of environment was mainly done through experience. As a result, even players with strong mechanics like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion weren’t much different than Concealed Light in the water.

Tang Rou was currently fighting with a monster in the water. They were basically hitting each other back and forth because, after all, monsters weren’t players. The majority of them only used simple attacks. Tang Rou wanted to dodge as if she were on ground, but because of the water resistance, she wasn’t able to grasp the timing correctly. Tang Rou didn’t give up though. She continued to try, while still sending attacks at the monster.

Her attacks could still hit, though. After all, monsters didn’t have very good awareness for dodging. As for the monster’s attacks on her, Tang Rou was very aware of them, but she just couldn’t dodge them.

And with this back and forth, she did finish. Her appearance afterwards wasn’t pretty though.

“I can never dodge it!” Tang Rou said to Ye Xiu.

“Your movements in the water are much slower, so your judgement and timing will be different than they are on land. Telling you the numbers won’t help you. You just have to slowly get used to it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay!” Tang Rou replied and continued to look for monsters.

“Use the limited practice method.” Ye Xiu said, “Most monsters won’t dodge. Use limited practice and see whether you can predict correctly where your attack will hit.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Tang Rou nodded her head and continued to practice.

Ye Xiu didn’t call them into the water with any hopes that they could help him, but rather to use this chance to have them practice battles in the water. If their goals were to be pro players, they couldn’t have such a large weakness. If not, the opposing team would simply choose a water map and win with ease.

Steamed Bun Invasion and Concealed Light were too low leveled. Hitting back and forth with the monster wouldn’t be very good. As a result, these two players attacked a monster 2v1. For now, Ye Xiu couldn’t say anything to Concealed Light. However, from the looks of it, Steamed Bun Invasion’s ability to adapt was much better than Tang Rou’s. After a short while, clear progress could already be seen.

“Fight while walking with me!” Ye Xiu said.

“Senior, it should be swimming.” Steamed Bun Invasion corrected.

“Okay, swimming. Fight while swimming with me.” Ye Xiu had his Lord Grim aggro monsters. Their team leveled in Thousand Waves Lake while they were wandering around.

After hunting down Blossom Valley’s team, Thousand Creations already knew what Ye Xiu’s goal was. The top guilds wanted to chase and kill him. But now, they were guarding Thousand Waves Lake and killing any guild dungeon team they saw.

The hunted had become the hunters and the hunters had become the hunted. Thousand Creations thought about this and felt quite happy. This really was more fun than stealing monsters. The others swam while fighting monsters, while he was focused on searching for any signs of other players.

“Over here!” He suddenly heard Ye Xiu call out. Thousand Creations turned around to look. He had gotten a bit far from the team. As he swam over, he felt that it was a bit strange. Weren’t they just blindly searching? Why did it matter what route they took?

But not long after, several silhouettes appeared in front of them. After taking a closer look, it was a team of five players.

“Players!” Thousand Creations exclaimed excitedly.

“Yup. Everyone, be careful. Keep the same pace as me.” Ye Xiu said. His Lord Grim had already plunged into the water. When players dove underwater, they would have to come up for air eventually, so when they needed to hurry, they would usually swim above the water. When they saw their targets, they immediately dove into the water, so that they wouldn’t be discovered.

“Is it really necessary, God? It’s just five players…….” Thousand Creations also dove into the water, while carefully sending Ye Xiu a message, expressing his doubts. In his eyes, with this God’s skill, wiping out these five players would be too easy. There was no need for them to hide.

“The other side is definitely on guard against us. Only by hiding can we make sure they won’t run away.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Oh……” Thousand Creations understood. The God was saying that if they were going to kill them, they had to kill them all.

They followed Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, changing their pace or going up for water from time to time. As expected, those five players didn’t show any signs that there was something amiss.

Changing pace wasn’t new to Thousand Creations. At that time in Line Canyon, he had learned from it and knew that it was a way to efficiently use stamina and improve their average speed. Now that he knew the person in front of him was God Ye Qiu, Thousand Creations wouldn’t doubt him and immediately followed behind to learn it well.

After playing with him that time, Thousand Creations had tried studying this technique. After all, for someone who was often running away because of his kill stealing, such a technique was very useful.

His studying hadn’t gotten much results, but he could tell that their current pace was somewhat fast. With their current pace, their stamina wouldn’t last for very long. It seemed a bit different than what God had done at that time.

Thousand Creations was about to ask, when suddenly he recalled that they were in the water. Perhaps this had something to do with the difference in movement speed between in the water and on land? He pondered over this and didn’t ask for now. He continued to observe the distance between them and the five players, while making his own assessment.

As the distance between the two sides shrunk, Thousand Creations was beginning to understand their stamina usage. He discovered that their pace might not be the most efficient usage of stamina, but it was enough to chase down those five players.

And since this still allowed them to chase down those five players, it meant that this was the fastest way to chase down those five players.

Thousand Creations finally realized this after thinking about it for awhile. He immediately had even more respect for this God. Just how much experience and calculating ability did he have?

Reality turned out to be just like Thousand Creations had predicted. The distance between them grew closer and closer. When Thousand Creations could see the splashes from those five players, Cleansing Mist lifted up her handcannon.

“Crash!!”

A burst of bubbles blasted out from the cannon. Cleansing Mist was also pushed back by the recoil. In the water, even normal attacks would cause the character to be pushed back from the recoil.

Three Anti-Tank Missiles shot out. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim also flew through the water like a torpedo.

The missiles exploded and violent waves rolled out. The three Anti-Tank Missiles were in a triangle formation. Not a single one of the five players fell as the waves pushed them into the air. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim quickly swam a bit. He suddenly lifted his weapon and a burst of bubbles blasted outwards. Just as the five players fell back into the water, another wave lifted them up into the air.

Thousand Creations looked on with wide eyes. They truly deserved to be called the golden duo!

After two rounds of Anti-Tank Missiles, the five players dropped down as Lord Grim went up to kill them. These five knew what was happening. But they didn’t have any thoughts of resisting and only thought of running away. But as soon as they hit the water, they were attacked on all sides. Lord Grim was already in front of him. How could they even have any thoughts of attending to the others?

Even though the others were complete noobs in the water, they were still useful as blockades, especially Concealed Light. His summoned creatures were running around all over the place. The five players looked around wildly, but they couldn’t find any escape routes. With Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng attacking, the five players didn’t have any chance of escaping.

After a short moment, in the group chat, Misty Castle’s tenth server guild leader Misty Haze said with a sullen expression: “One of our teams has died, too.”

Chapter 373 – Blue River’s Analysis

With Blooming Blossom as a model, Misty Castle’s guild leader, Misty Lock, felt too embarrassed to go into a rage because of his team’s wipe out, so he calmly replied: “What’s the situation?”

Hazy Mist felt quite puzzled over this question. After a long while, he still couldn’t think of any other way of saying it, so he repeated what he felt that everyone should already know: “They were killed by Happy’s players at Thousand Waves Lake.”

“Of course we know that.” Misty Lock continued, “But didn’t we already warn everyone? Why weren’t you being careful?”

“We were careful……. But they somehow got close to us.” Hazy Mist had also asked the five who had been wiped out about this issue, so he simply passed on what those five had said.

“With God Ye Qiu there, the things they can do will definitely surpass our expectations.” Arisaema said. Many others agreed. They had all experienced the water battle previously. At the time, none of them had seen how Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng had gotten into the water without them noticing. Other than their opponents’ ability surpassing their expectations, how else could they explain it?

And now, even while being careful, they had still been closed in on and killed without them knowing. The guild leaders appeared very calm in the group chat, but they were actually very worried when they were speaking to their own guilds. They hastily confirmed that their teams were, in fact, being careful.

Apart from this, what else could they do?

After understanding the circumstances, the group was once again at their wits’ end. None of them could think of a solution. The guild leaders hated how this was happening in the new server. If this had happened in an old server, they could immediately transfer players over from the Heavenly Domain there. No matter how great Ye Qiu was, there was no way he could fight off a sea of people. But in the new server, there were only 100 players that could reach this leveling area. All of the others were too underleveled. Plus, the majority of them were new players, so many of them would have their doubts and couldn’t be used for much yet.

The group chat was in complete silence. West Riding Wind and Misty Lock, who had been talking about their situations in the Heavenly Domain, felt that it was too inappropriate to chat. None of them could come up with any countermeasures. All they could do was warn their teams repeatedly to stay careful.

After several minutes of worrying, the overall guild leaders were finally notified by the tenth server guild leaders that their teams had entered the dungeon. Only then were they able to heave a sigh of relief.

“What about Ye Qiu? Where are they right now?” Everyone was once again discussing this question.

“He’s probably wandering around in the lake……..” someone replied. No one could see how he was gnashing his teeth in anger, though.

“Are they actually planning on wandering around all day?”

“Why does that question sound somewhat familiar?”

It was true. That question had already been asked about before, except it was from a different perspective. Before, they had thought that the other side were staying in Thousand Waves Lake to protect themselves. But now, they knew that staying in Thousand Waves Lake was a form of attack. Not only was the dungeon in the middle of Thousand Waves Lake, but the monsters for leveling and the main quests were all located in this leveling area. If they were forced back to Sin City in order to level because of this threat, their leveling speed would definitely slow down a lot.

But what if they didn’t retreat? Every time they were killed, they would lose 10% of their experience. This loss would be even worse than retreating back to Sin City.

“Should we gather up everyone? If we have 100 players, Ye Qiu’s group might not be brave enough to attack.” Misty Lock suggested.

“Are you sure that he won’t be brave enough?” The main speakers in this group chat were the overall guild leaders, while the tenth server guild leaders were mostly there to convey the orders to the guild, so they rarely made any suggestions. But Blue River, Blue Brook Guild’s tenth server guild leader, suddenly opposed.

“Oh? Brother Blue River, what do you think?” Misty Lock didn’t look down on this guild leader because, after all, Blue River was a famous player in the Heavenly Domain. Apart from not having as many responsibilities as an overall guild leader, he wasn’t any worse in any other area.

“I came to the tenth server early on and I came into contact with Lord Grim or Ye Qiu very early. Our big guild was on the losing side in every interaction ever since we first met. He had always been in control. I think Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night knows this very well, too.”

“…….” Cold Night was gloomy. He had prolonged experience with him, but his was different from Blue River’s. He was from Tyranny, the team whose mortal enemy was Ye Qiu. Against such a rival, even if he was convinced in his heart, he couldn’t say it out loud, especially when there were so many players……

“I do……” After a moment of hesitation, Cold Night decided to reply honestly.

With a human testimony, Blue River continued: “I don’t think I need to talk about how skilled Ye Qiu is. The most important point is his style. At the very least, I’ve never seen him choose to retreat or surrender. We might have the advantage for one moment, but he’ll always have a backup plan and in the end, the ones who lose out are us. Who knows how many times this has happened before. I’m sure Cold Night also knows this, too……”

“Hey, hey!!!” Cold Night privately messaged Blue River: “Don’t keep dragging me along! Don’t you know Tyranny’s position? It’s very shameful like this!”

“You think it won’t be shameful if we continue fighting?” Blue River asked back.

“What exactly do you plan on saying?” Cold Night asked.

“What exactly do you plan on saying, Blue River?” a guild leader asked in the group chat. Many of them were already frowning. This was because Blue River sounded as if he were from Ye Qiu’s group. Even if this guy was a God, how could a guild leader have such a weak will? It was too inappropriate. When talking about an enemy, you should be despising him!

“What I’m trying to say is…….” Blue River typed and then paused for a bit.

“Don’t regard Ye Qiu as simply a top tier pro player. In reality, even within the game, his experience is incomparable. There’s nothing that he isn’t familiar with in the game. In addition, his individual skill is something that none of us can deal with. It’s by relying on all of this that he’s able to create such a huge movement in the tenth server. His overwhelmingness has always been like our current situation: we know that he’s waiting in Thousand Waves Lake. We know what he’s doing, but the problem is, what can we do to stop him?”

“That’s why I’m saying, against such an opponent, retreating is the choice for the greatest victory…….” Blue River concluded.

No one spoke back in the group chat. Blue River had no way of telling what they were thinking from looking at the empty chat. After staring for a long while in silence, Blue River took the initiative to speak once again.

“There’s one more thing that I think we need to pay careful consideration to.” Blue River said.

“I doubt any of you think Ye Qiu is making a guild simply for the fun of it, right? I’m sure you’ve all watched the All-Star Weekend. All of the pros saw Ye Qiu’s Dragon Raises Its Head as a declaration of his return. By observing his movements in the game, I think that his intent is to create his own pro team with Guild Happy as the team’s foundation in the game. That’s why I’m saying that there’s no way we can avoid having Guild Happy competing with us…….”

“This is where I don’t understand what you’re saying Blue River.” Misty Lock typed.

“You said that there’s no way we can avoid competing with Guild Happy. But before that, you said that our only option was to retreat. So what you’re saying is that we should just sit still and watch as Guild Happy takes the throne and then let him eat us up?” Misty Lock said.

“Hold on, I’m not done talking yet.” Blue River replied calmly.

“This isn’t the point I wanted to make. The point I wanted to make stems from what I can deduce from Ye Qiu’s intent, Happy will continue to develop and will definitely enter the Heavenly Domain and Ye Qiu already has a huge advantage. He hadn’t used it in the past, but he’s started to use it quite a bit……”

“This advantage is his identity! In the new server, the usefulness of his advantage is limited because most of the players here are new to Glory. However, in the Heavenly Domain, if he exposed his identity, what do you guys think? How many players would follow after him?” Blue River said.

The hearts of every single guild leader there shook wildly. They immediately realized the severity of this issue. Just awhile ago, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain showed up online just for a bit. However, his brief appearance gathered a huge amount of spectators. If such a God went to create a guild with the intent of developing it, the amount of appeal the guild would have would be world-shaking! They had no way of imagining how many followers he would have.

“You’re right.” Blue River’s senior, Changing Spring, stood out and supported him.

No one could make any objections to this. In the end, Misty Lock said: “Your words make even less sense than before. He’s so terrifying, yet you want us to retreat……. What do you mean by this?”

“My reasoning is very simple. In the new server, we have very limited manpower. I believe that we have no way of winning against him, so retreating will allow us to keep any benefits we’ve already gained in the new server. If we continue fighting, our level advantage will be lost. As for when he gets to the Heavenly Domain, if he makes any big moves like this, I remind everyone to be careful. If we’re going to resist, we all have to do it together.” Blue River said.

“So you’re saying that in the end, we’ll have to resist in the Heavenly Domain?”

“Correct, but there’s one more thing……” Blue River said.

‘Still more…….” Everyone was clearly a bit scared. The issues Blue River brought up made them all feel uneasy.

“Our fight in the Heavenly Domain won’t be as far as away as you guys think. Don’t forget that Ye Qiu’s character is unspecialized. Unspecialized aren’t able to level up in the normal server once they reach Level 50. This means that he’ll probably complete the Heavenly Domain challenge at Level 50. In other words, he won’t be entering the Heavenly Domain at Level 70, but rather at Level 50!”

Chapter 374 – Watching a Fire From the Other Side of the Shore

“Beating the Heavenly Domain Challenge at Level 50……..”

If a normal player did this, all of the guild leaders would flip their tables in shock. But because they knew that Ye Qiu, the top-tier pro player, was going to do it, they weren’t as shocked at the news.

But in any case, this was something that had never been done before.

The Heavenly Domain Challenge consisted of many difficult battles and achievements that required a lot of time to obtain, such as a certain amount of wins in the Arena.

When the Heavenly Domain Challenge had first started, it wasn’t impossible to complete the Challenge at Level 50. The reason that no one did it then was because there were too many tasks to do, so if the player started it at Level 50, they would have leveled up several times from doing it and it still wouldn’t have been finished.

As the level cap continued to increase, the difficulty of the Heavenly Domain Challenge continued to increase as well. Nowadays, the level cap was Level 70. Completing the Heavenly Domain Challenge at Level 50 would naturally be seen as impossible. However, for someone like Ye Qiu, this task would have to be viewed at in a different light. They were all still shocked, but they didn’t feel like it would be impossible for him to do. If they had began planning now what they would do once he rushed to the Heavenly Domain at Level 50, they would have quite a bit of time to prepare.

“This is what I wanted to say.” Blue River closed the curtains. In the end, this was the problem he had analyzed. As for the problem of how to resolve it, he simply proposed to “retreat” in the new server, a suggestion that everyone else disliked. Although, for Blue River, after telling everyone what he had analyzed, he suddenly felt like a heavy burden had been lifted off of his shoulders.

The discussion in the group chat continued.

“Honestly speaking, I think that if Ye Qiu’s might is that great, then our best option is still to deal with him in the tenth server. If we’re able to stop him from reaching the Heavenly Domain, then that would be way too perfect.” Jiang You said.

“It’s easy to say that, but how are we going to deal with him? Right now, he’s the one who is dealing with our elite teams.” Arisaema said.

“Blue River’s words are reasonable. With our current circumstances, there’s really nothing we can do.” Misty Lock expressed.

“For water battles, unless we use pro players, we really can’t do anything since we don’t have enough manpower…….” West Riding Wind said.

“Are we really going to retreat in the new server and wait until he gets to the Heavenly Domain to deal with him?” someone muttered.

“Sweat, if Ye Qiu’s identity was announced publicly, his guild’s influence will instantly skyrocket to the top ten guilds!”

“To tell you guys the truth, I really like Ye Qiu. If I can actually start up a guild together with him, I’d be pretty happy…….”

“F*ck!” everyone disdained.

“If Ye Qiu really does develop his guild, form a team, and then return to the Alliance, that’ll have a big impact on the pro scene, no? Maybe if we report it to the higher-ups, they might send us pro players to interfere.”

“This…… From what I saw during the All-Star Weekend, the majority of the pro players were looking forward to Ye Qiu returning! Even Han Wenqing did.. and he’s Ye Qiu’s mortal enemy!”

“That’s on the program, though. It’s for the public to see, so of course they’re going to show their support. How do you not know this?”

“Piss off. Our Team XXX definitely isn’t like that!!” Many other similar words were said at the same time. The guild leaders jumped out to support their respective team’s pro players. They believed that their pros were definitely honest, while the others were all just posers.

Right at this moment, everyone in the group chat became their team’s number one fan and disputed in order to protect their team’s reputation. After several minutes, because Changing Spring, who didn’t like to chat, fortunately didn’t participate in the dispute, he was able to keep a clear head and quickly typed something to keep the chat in control.

Seeing that Changing Spring had typed out several messages, they respected it and quickly stopped their banter.

“The Clubs’ stances are what’s important.” the clear-headed Changing Spring typed out after waiting for everyone to calm down.

Everyone immediately understood after seeing this. A pro player’s attitude only represented an individual. If they were going to need pro players to come into the game, this would have to depend on what the Clubs wanted.

“The Clubs’ stances……..” Jiang You repeated these words. Everyone else immediately felt like he was going to say something and quieted down.

“I’ve decided. Our Herb Garden will accept Blue River’s proposal. We will choose to retreat in the new server. We’ll….. be leaving first.” No one had thought that Arisaema would be the first to speak up. They hadn’t even finished discussing it yet, so why did he suddenly make the decision already? The others didn’t really understand and wanted to ask, but Arisaema had already left the group chat, along with Herb Garden’s tenth server guild leader, Plantago Seed.

“That was kind of weird?” Misty Lock said after seeing Arisaema leave.

“It was. For him to suddenly make a decision like that, what is he planning?” Others began to ponder.

“Uh, maybe…….” Jiang You, who had been interrupted by Arisaema, finally spoke.

“Right now, it’s the second half of the season. The teams are all busy. Bothering them right now would distract the pro players and would make them lose the focus which is needed to deal with these in-game matters. Let alone the Clubs not being happy, I don’t think you guys want this to happen either, right? After all, all of our efforts in-game are for supporting the team and not to drag the team behind. If we really did rely on them to deal with these matters, that wouldn’t be a victory. I’m sure everyone knows how much effort has to be put into chasing and killing. If the Club take the initiative to interfere, then that’s fine, but if we request it, then it would be our mistake.” Jiang You concluded.

“Right!” Everyone agreed after hearing it.

“Arisaema probably thought about this. What a sneaky guy, though! He didn’t want to do it, but he didn’t say why so he left it to us, hoping we would ask the Clubs for help. That way, he would reap the benefits without doing anything and therefore, his team wouldn’t be distracted!” Jiang You said.

“How evil!” Everyone looked down on Arisaema.

“He really didn’t need to be like that.” Jiang You sent out a sly smiley face.

“Oh, go on, go on.” Everyone supported Jiang You. This was because they were very confident that Jiang You had a good proposal to make. If not, he wouldn’t have revealed what Arisaema had been planning. If he didn’t have anything to say, he wouldn’t have said anything about Arisaema’s leave.

Everyone understood the relationships between guilds however, they just never spoke about it. Previously, they had cursed at Arisaema, but in reality, there was nothing wrong with what he did.

“There are definitely people who don’t want to see Ye Qiu returning to the pro scene.” Jiang You said.

No one said anything and waited for Jiang You to say it.

“Did you guys forget about Ye Qiu’s strange relationship with Excellent Dynasty?” Jiang You finally said the answer.

“Oh……:”

Messages expressing their sudden understanding of everything immediately filled the screen.

The relationship between Ye Qiu and Excellent Dynasty was extremely strange. With Ye Qiu’s identity and ability, if he left the team and was put into the game, he could easily take over the guild as the overall guild leader. Even if he didn’t stay in the Club, he should at least have some friendly feelings for his own Club, right?

But in reality, he didn’t.

Before all this, since they didn’t know of Lord Grim’s identity, it could have been ignored. However, after they knew it, they felt that it was very strange. Some had even directly asked Excellent Dynasty’s guild leader, Chen Yehui, but the other side wouldn’t respond. There was clearly something that was going on inside.

They couldn’t guess what the exact situation was, but it was clear that Ye Qiu had some sort of fight with Excellent Era and it wasn’t just an ordinary one either. His retirement might have been forced. If this was so, then Excellent Era definitely wouldn’t want to see Ye Qiu returning. If it was not, they wouldn’t have forced him to retire.

“That’s why I say that if we take a seat and ignore Ye Qiu and Happy’s development, there will definitely be people who will be even more uneasy than us.” Jiang You said.

“And don’t forget, Excellent Era’s achievements this year are quite terrible! From how they are doing right now, staying in the Alliance won’t be a problem, but their chances at making it into the playoffs are almost zero percent. That’s why they have the capability of putting in more effort to deal with Ye Qiu in the game!” Jiang You said.

“That make sense….. But…….” The others were clearly hesitant.

“It’s not like we can do anything right now. It’d be best to just take a step back and see what Excellent Era is going to do. After that, we can react depending on the situation. If they really don’t do anything, we can think of something when that time comes.” Jiang You had clearly thought about this thoroughly. As Excellent Dynasty’s arch enemy, he was more sensitive to their matters, which was why he had been able to think of this.

“Watching a fire from the other side of the shore.” Changing Spring concluded.

“Correct.” Jiang You was very pleased. With those two guilds fighting each other, it didn’t matter which side won. He’d be happy all the same. Although from a larger point of view, he hoped that Ye Qiu would be suppressed. After all, his skill in the game was too terrifying. He felt that dealing with him was even more difficult than dealing with the entire Excellent Dynasty team combined.

Chapter 375 – Cede Territory or Pay Reparations?

Jiang You’s solution might not be certain, but right now, they still had no way of dealing with Ye Qiu hunting their guilds at Thousand Waves Lake. It might be best to do as Jiang You said and retreat from this obstacle for now. Later, if they had to do something, they could turn hostile. In any case, battles between guilds were common occurrences. Everyone had a tacit mutual understanding.

Blue River had been sitting idly, but who would have thought that he’d be fired at while lying down? The group decided that Blue River would be the one to negotiate with Ye Qiu and settle this matter.

“You’ve come into contact with him the most often, so you understand him the best!” The words that Blue River said himself had been used against him by the guild leaders.

“Go.” Even his own comrade, Changing Spring, had declared his position. He clearly thought that Blue River was also the most suitable for this task.

Blue River was naturally very depressed because this task wasn’t as simple as just talking for a bit.

When you want to kill, you go kill. But when you can’t kill, you ask the other side not to kill……. The world wasn’t so convenient like that. Even though Blue River didn’t see Ye Qiu as a bad person, the problem was that, this time, retreating may only be a temporary measure, but since they were leaving behind helpers, Blue River didn’t think that Ye Qiu wouldn’t be able to see through their future preparations. Even if Ye Qiu couldn’t see through their schemes, he should definitely be able to anticipate them delaying for time. After all, his terrain advantage at Thousand Waves Lake wasn’t something that he would have at every level stage. After getting past this level stage, there would be a new leveling area to go to.

“I can’t guarantee it.” Blue River admitted.

“It doesn’t matter. There’s nothing that’s 100% in this world. Just do your best!” the guild leaders told him sincerely. Blue River wanted to curse at them. The words coming out of their mouths sounded pretty, but if he wasn’t able to succeed, he didn’t believe that these guild leaders would still be so good-natured. In the future, they might take revenge on their Blue Brook Guild because of it. Blue River didn’t think that Changing Spring wouldn’t know of this. He couldn’t understand why Changing Spring would let him do this errand.

“I can’t guarantee it.” Blue River persisted. He gave his opinion and refused to let go.

“Brother Blue River, this isn’t right. We aren’t telling you that you must succeed. We just think that you have a better chance at doing so. You have to at least try. You’re hurting our hearts too much.”

Blue River laughed grimly. In the Heavenly Domain, they were all trying to kill each other and constantly poked holes into one another’s hearts. The deeper the hole, the happier they would be. Now they were telling him that their hearts were hurting. Blue River could only laugh at this.

Seeing that Blue River wasn’t responding, they switched targets and began peddling to the Blue Brook Guild’s leader, Changing Spring. They were clearly trying to get Changing Spring to persuade Blue River to go.

Changing Spring didn’t say much either and simply sent Blue River a question mark.

“I can’t guarantee it.” Blue River didn’t hesitate.

“I can’t guarantee it.” Blue River saw his own words get typed out into the group chat by Changing Spring. He was quite sure that his guild leader had just copy and pasted it.

This guy refused to let up. No matter how angry they were, there was nothing that they could do, except ridicule him in secret. They weren’t from the same party, so how could their remarks do anything? They did this often, so none of their words had any effect. After a bit, they felt like there was no point, so in the end, they had to choose someone else.

“How about we have Brother Cold Night go? In the tenth server, besides Blue River, Tyrannical Ambition has interacted with Lord Grim the most, so you should understand him well, too.” Blossom Valley’s tenth server guild leader Backlight Bomb suggested.

Cold Night’s expression turned dark. His senior, Jiang You, came out to support him, though: “Everyone…… With our guild’s background, our interaction with him will be filled with tension. If you have us go, I doubt we would be able to succeed.”

His words made sense. But in truth, even if Cold Night now knew that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, Ye Qiu had known that they were Tyrannical Ambition from the very beginning. After so many interactions with each other, Cold Night had never felt like the rivalry between their backgrounds had meant anything to Ye Qiu, so even if their reason made sense, it wasn’t actually true.

Of course, Cold Night wouldn’t say anything. In truth, his thoughts were the same as Blue River. He knew that this was difficult to guarantee and didn’t want the guns to be pointed at him.

As a result, he refused to let up as well. There was nothing that they could do. In the end, they directly mentioned Jiang You’s name: “Guild leader Jiang You, you made this plan, so you choose someone. Don’t say Blue River. He’s already expressed that he won’t do it.”

“How about we do a vote?” Jiang You suggested.

“Vote? If someone gets picked, will no one refuse?” someone said.

“Refuse.” Blue River wasn’t being vague. He directly objected. Everyone gave out helpless expressions.

Jiang You saw that his brilliant plan was actually being stopped at this place. He couldn’t point at the other guilds’ members, and Blue River refused to go. If they voted, Cold Night would definitely be chosen. Since things were like this, Jiang You decided to take it up like a man.

“Cold Night, you go! If you don’t succeed, we won’t blame you. We’ll make an agreement. If Cold Night doesn’t succeed, no one will blame him. How about it?” Jiang You said.

“That’s fine. That’s fine.” Quite a few guild leaders agreed.

“I took a screenshot for proof.” Jiang You said.

“The screenshot will be proof.” The others agreed. There was no point dragging this on. No one wanted to delay anymore. The faster they got this done, the better.

As a result, Cold Night was forced to do the negotiations. He was sent online to talk with Ye Qiu and make peace.

“God…….” Cold Night wasn’t as stubborn as Blue River. After being sent by Jiang You, he could only agree.

“What’s up?” Ye Xiu replied quickly. He was clearly taking it easy.

“Cough, cough. Can we discuss something?” Cold Night said.

“Go ahead!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Can we not fight? We surrender this time!” Cold Night thought about it for a bit and decided that he might as well get straight to the point! He probably wasn’t a match in speaking in a roundabout way anyways.

“Oh? Sure!”

“Thanks!!!” Cold Night didn’t think that the other side would be so quick. He was so happy, his eyes were sparkling.

“Cede territory or pay reparations?” Ye Xiu replied.

“What?” Cold Night replied, but after pondering over it, sweat began to drip from his head.

“The territory you have to cede is Thousand Waves Lake, so that we can level up. The reparations are the same. I’ll send you guys a materials list!” Ye Xiu replied. Cold Night had already anticipated this reply. He had already run out of sweat to sweat.

“This, this, this, it shouldn’t go to that extent…….” Cold Night didn’t have any thoughts of negotiating. He was just saying nonsense at this point.

“It’s a surrender, no? Don’t you have to cede your territory and pay reparations? I’m letting you guys choose one of the two. Aren’t I nice!” Ye Xiu said.

Cold Night was depressed. Even though he was in charge, if he had to accept these conditions, the promise that the guild leaders had made might not be enough. Thinking of their promise, though, Cold Night had his own idea. He directly copied down his chat with Lord Grim and sent it over to the group chat.

“Everyone, what are your thoughts?” Cold Night acted tactfully. He wouldn’t be their negotiator. He would simply be passing on their messages.

Lord Grim’s material list……. The tenth server guild leaders knew about this, but the Heavenly Domain guild leaders didn’t know, so they asked: “What is this?”

“It’s very simple! It’s his condition!” Blue River wasn’t busy, so he explained it to everyone.

The others clearly didn’t have very good opinions of Blue River and ignored him. They listened to a different tenth server guild leader explain it.

“Give Thousand Waves Lake to him? F*ck, their guild only has five Level 40s. Two of them can’t even join until five days later!” One guild leader was furious.

“Maybe we should have a look at the materials list.” West Riding Wind said.

“Yeah, let’s take a look at the list!” Misty Lock agreed.

The tenth server guild leaders chose to stay silent. They wouldn’t say to look at the list because they anticipated that the list would also be brutal and inhumane. The main guild leaders would definitely have their eyes opened.

Cold Night didn’t dawdle and immediately asked Lord Grim if they could take a look at the materials list.

Ye Xiu had clearly anticipated that they would talk it over. After fighting with them previously, he knew which guilds had participated. He swiftly sent them a long list. The speed made Cold Night believe that he had prepared for this long beforehand.

“F*ck me! How can he be so heartless!!”

Sure enough, after the list was sent to the group chat, the main guild leaders all went crazy.

“His way of getting materials has always been far more efficient than looting……” Blue River mocked.

“This…… this……” Misty Lock looked at the list and kept saying, “This….”. He couldn’t seem to find any words.

“Though if you guys think about this carefully, if we split this up evenly among everyone, the list is in our acceptable range.” Blue River said.

“Blue River, which side are you on!” Someone began to doubt Blue River’s position.

“I’m just helping you guys understand his style. He’s always been like that. He’ll make your heart hurt, but he won’t go past what your heart can’t take…… I’m not the only one who has experienced this before, right?” Blue River said.

The majority of the tenth server guild leaders were already used to it, but the main guild leaders clearly couldn’t bear it.

“It doesn’t matter!” Misty Lock finally said after saying, “This…..” many times: “I don’t believe it. Thousand Waves Lake is so large. They only have those few people. How can they control the entire field?”

“Brother Misty, you’re right!” West Riding Wind, who was always quite close with Misty Lock, expressed his approval.

Chapter 376 – Too Careless

The guilds had to advance or retreat together because it was just like Blue River said; the materials Lord Grim had requested just happened to be within their limit of acceptance. If everyone equally split the materials, it was still bearable. However, if a single guild backed out, sharing the cost would be difficult. Herb Garden had already left, though, but Ye Xiu didn’t know that, so the list of materials he wanted already made the remaining guilds extremely unwilling. Two guilds immediately refused. Splitting the cost was now impossible.

And from the looks of it, ceding land was also unacceptable. The two guilds didn’t want to talk anymore and planned on continuing to delay matters. The group chat went silent for a while again. Jiang You began: “Have you two already decided?”

“Decided!” The two practically said at the time, making the others wonder if they were discussing with each other in private.

“All together, three guilds have already left. From what I see, there’s already no point in this group chat.” Jiang You’s personality was very direct. He was extremely disappointed in this alliance and he clearly had some anger in him. After throwing these words down, he directly left the group. Cold Night followed soon after.

The remaining guilds saw that there really was no point, so they left as well. In the blink of an eye, the group chat dissolved because there was no one there.

Each guild began to discuss with themselves for their own plan.

Everyone had already seen the conditions and they was still the same as before, so therefore, some of the guilds began to negotiate with Ye Xiu. Misty Lock and West Riding Wind had different ideas, though. They felt that, with Thousand Wave Lake’s size and Happy’s few players, taking complete control over the entire map wasn’t possible. They might as well try delaying to see what would happen.

The group chat dissolved as the guilds went on their own paths. No one knew what the others were planning. However, Ye Xiu had a good understanding of the situation.

There were a total of nine guilds competing in Thousand Waves Lake. All of them had fought together during the Christmas Event. One of them had conflicting interests with the others and immediately cut off any and all connections. Although Ye Xiu felt it was a bit of a pity, he wasn’t too surprised.

The other side clearly hadn’t been able to reach a unanimous decision towards Ye Xiu’s condition, resulting in Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition contacting Ye Xiu. They had hoped to pay materials in order to obtain the right for a peaceful development at Thousand Waves Lake.

Ye Xiu didn’t care which guild was which. If someone agreed, then he would happily welcome them. He had already calculated that the guilds definitely had the materials he wanted, so everything went along smoothly.

Blue Brook Guild, Tyrannical Ambition.

Ye Xiu confirmed that it was these two guilds and then reminded them that when they came to Thousand Waves Lake, they had to make sure their guild tags were turned on in order to avoid any mistakes. It would be best if they could tell him the others’ positions. That way, Ye Xiu could save some time since he wouldn’t need to take as many detours.

The two guilds had sent Blue River and Cold Night to talk with Ye Xiu. The two understood Ye Xiu’s thoughts very well, so they accepted in satisfaction. They were already spending materials, so they wouldn’t hesitate to make the most out of it. Right now, they were hoping that God would kill the players from other guilds quickly.

“What are the other guilds planning?” Ye Xiu asked Blue River.

“……”

“Tell me!”

“Senior, I’m not your spy!” Blue River was filled with grief!

“I wasn’t asking about your Blue Brook Guild. Don’t I already know what your Blue Brook Guild has planned? I’m asking about the other guilds!” Ye Xiu said.

“Don’t know.”

“That’s not possible! As Blue Brook Guild’s backbone and core member, it’s your responsibility and duty to accurately report information on the others guilds to their enemies. I’m sure you know that the enemy of your enemy is your friend. From this perspective, we’re friends, so why are you still protecting your enemies? I’m looking down on you!” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River’s cheeks were streaked with tears. What type of nonsense was this? Why did it seem logical?

“I really don’t know what the other guilds are planning.” Blue River said.

“Then do you have a general idea?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Some of them have decided to continue wandering around Thousand Waves Lake.” Blue River said.

“Hmm……” Ye Xiu expressed that he was thinking.

Blue River didn’t think that it was anything important, when suddenly, he received another message with a sharp question.

“You guys did this as a temporary measure. What are you planning?”

Sure enough, he had guessed that their temporary measure wasn’t without reason. However…….

“This question touches on our Blue Brook Guild’s interests, so I have a good reason not to answer, right?” Blue River replied.

“Oh, so you really do have plans?”

Blue River coughed up blood.

“With Thousand Wave Lake’s terrain, I reckon that you guys have no means of dealing with this situation. Are you guys planning on asking for outside help?” Ye Xiu began to guess.

Blue River remained silent.

“If you ask for outside help, you would have to tell them who I am…….. And if that’s the case, there wouldn’t be many people who would dare help!”

“Hey, hey!” Blue River couldn’t listen anymore.

“If you don’t believe me, go ask your team. In the water, even Huang Shaotian wouldn’t dare come.” Ye Xiu said.

“The team has the numbers advantage!” Blue River said.

“If they all come into the game, then wouldn’t that mean they’d be giving up on their team record?” Ye Xiu asked back.

“If each guild sends one pro, it’ll be enough.” Blue River remained stubborn.

“Disturbing all of these teams is kind of embarrassing……..” Ye Xiu said.

“You scared?” Blue River secretly felt good, especially because the other side didn’t reply back after he sent the message.

Blue River didn’t keep talking though. He hadn’t been on his account for several days so his character’s experience was falling behind. He put on his equipment and prepared to gain some good experience. Not long after he began to travel, a message popped up. He checked and Lord Grim had replied.

“Tch, you were just bluffing! I just went and asked around. None of the teams said they were sending players over!”

“What? Who’d you ask?”

“The players from every team!” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River had run out of tears. How could he forget! This guy had a completely different status than he did! The other side didn’t need to guess. He could just directly go to the pro circle and ask. He had been in the pro scene for so many years. How could he not have known players from the other teams!

“It’s late now. We were planning on notifying them tomorrow.” Blue River continued to quibble.

“Did I hear that right? How come it sounds like you’re the Club’s boss or the team captain? They’re just going to come if you tell them to come? Are you summoning creatures?” Ye Xiu replied.

Blue River stayed silent.

“Liar! Lie after lie!” Ye Xiu didn’t let up.

“……” Blue River could only reply with ellipses.

“Oh! I found a party! Talk to you later!” Ye Xiu suddenly replied.

“Which guild?” Blue River asked excitedly.

“Yours.”

“F*ck your sister! We made an agreement!!” Blue River cried in shock. Had this punk completely joined in on the guild battle and was now going back on his word?

“I lied. They’re from Misty Castle.”

Blue River coughed up blood again. Wasn’t he busy? How could he still joke around like that? But….. Misty Castle was good! Misty Castle hadn’t felt that this was problematic. Letting them get a good taste of retribution would be good. Speaking of Misty Castle, they had already been wiped out once. Did that team really just rush back, only to be killed once again? How unlucky of them.

Blue River’s guess was correct. Misty Castle’s party really was just that unlucky. Before, they had been closed in on, unbeknownst to them and died. They had just rushed back and this time, they were able to save some time though. Right before they were about to enter the water, they saw Lord Grim’s group jump out of the water.

A dungeon team would only have five players. With Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng there, wiping them out was very easy, whether it was on land or on water. In addition, they had Tang Rou, Steamed Bun Invasion, Thousand Creations……. And the cheerleader, Concealed Light.

It could be said that this battle on the shore was even more without suspense than it was in the water. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were as valiant as ever. Plus, Tang Rou was going all out. Tang Rou’s skill was already much better than the usual guild elite.

Even the elite teams from the grandest of guilds were nothing but paper in front of these opponents and were easily cleaned up.

Misty Lock naturally became furious after hearing this news: “You pigs! You clearly knew that there was danger. Why didn’t you scout it out clearly first and choose a better route?”

The players who were being yelled at also had their cheeks streaked with tears. It wasn’t that they weren’t being careless. It was just that they just didn’t think that the other side would hide at the shore side. Weren’t they supposed to be wandering around the dungeon island? This move looked as if the other side was waiting for them to return. It was way too shameless.

“Care a bit more. Be more careful. Is that too much to ask!” Misty Lock personally lectured them. Misty Castle had formed their own group chat with the overall guild leader personally directing the tenth server’s elite teams.

What could the five players who were being yelled at say? They had to run over from the main city again!

“Work’s done. Let’s continue on with what we were saying.” Ye Xiu chatted up with Blue River again.

“I already have nothing to say to you.”

“Has your dungeon team come over yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

“What are you planning on doing?” Blue River was being extremely cautious.

“If you see any other guilds, give me a call!” Ye Xiu said.

“……”

“You’ll be coming over to level here, right? You pay attention, too!” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m not a spy!”

“Didn’t you keep on stressing that you were a spy before?”

“That was that account.”

“It’s all the same to me. Pay attention! If you find anyone, tell me.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay. I’ll talk to you later.” Ye Xiu added.

“Which guild now?” Blue River was surprised. What insane efficiency! It was fortunate that their Blue Brook Guild had made an agreement.

“It’s quite embarrassing to tell you, but it’s Misty Castle again…… Sigh, they’re too careless!” Ye Xiu replied, while looking through reports from his guild. He had the manpower now, too.

Chapter 377 – One After Another

The majority of the guild players were around Level 30 and were relatively inexperienced, which meant they weren’t able to actually go to Thousand Waves Lakes and fight in the leveling area. However, they were good enough to stay on watch on the road from Congee City to Thousand Waves Lake.

Most of the players in the tenth server were around Level 30. If they hid their guild tag, it would be impossible to recognize who they were if they stuck within a crowd. As for those Level 35 and above players who had just joined, Ye Xiu didn’t maneuver them because he knew that there were spies hidden amongst them. He couldn’t be certain that those players who were around Level 30 weren’t spies, but the risk for that was much less. Even more so, Ye Xiu wasn’t ordering every member of the guild to move. Instead, he only picked a handful of them, asking them to take note of certain players.

If a spy got in, then he could only blame his bad luck.

From the looks of it, none of the ones he had chosen were spies. In addition, they had completed their mission very well. After all, they had only just recently joined the guild, so they were still enthusiastic about the guild’s errands.

Misty Castle’s dungeon team had been noticed this way by these inconspicuous low-level players, who then notified Ye Xiu. From the direction they were moving in, Ye Xiu could easily figure out which route they were taking. Misty Castle’s team hadn’t thought about this possibility and had only thought about being careful around the lake. How could they not have been mopped up by Ye Xiu?

Even more tragic was that Misty Castle’s players still hadn’t noticed the problem yet. They simply thought that their luck was just bad. The dungeon team was once again completely defenceless when they came out of Congee City. They rushed out onto the main road and were being watched the entire time by Guild Happy’s players, who excitedly notified their guild leader. Ye Xiu looked at their reports and figured out their route once again.

“This time, let’s be a bit more active!” Ye Xiu didn’t underestimate his opponents.

“How?” the others asked.

“We’ll just ambush them on land and be done with it.” Ye Xiu said as he led them out of Thousand Waves Lake. They found a random hiding spot along the main road from Congee City to Thousand Waves Lake and hid there.

“How are we going to attack this time?” Concealed Light asked. Even though this guy was quite useless in actual battle, he was always the most serious player when it came to preparations before the battle. Concealed Light was the type of person who, if you said one was one, then one was one. There was no changing it. When a plan was carried out, his firmness to stick with it would already be approaching stubbornness.

“Even though wiping them out isn’t that hard, we can’t be too careless either. Concealed Light, when the time comes, summon your creatures and do your best to fill up any gaps in our encirclement.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Concealed Light said solemnly. In reality, Ye Xiu had already said this numerous times today. However, every time, when a new battle started, Concealed Light would always ask again. Hearing the same arrangement over and over again didn’t make him feel tired of it.

“Everyone else do the same as always. Pay attention to coordinating with each other.” Ye Xiu said. With him and Su Mucheng there, wiping out a five-man team wasn’t a problem. It didn’t matter whether or not the others were there. However, since this was on land, Ye Xiu hoped to let Tang Rou and the others practice and gain some experience.

“If we hide here, even though they can’t see us, we can’t see them either!” Steamed Bun Invasion said. The six of them were currently hiding behind a big rock.

“Hm? This way works!” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly started jumping up and down.

“Don’t do that.” Ye Xiu hastily stopped him.

“By taking into account their movement speed and their distance, we can accurately calculate how long it will take for them to arrive.” Concealed Light explained.

“Correct.” Ye Xiu said, “How’s your grasp on the other team’s situation? Can you calculate it?”

“I can try.” Concealed Light was feeling rather confident in himself at this moment.

“The last report had their coordinates at 3654, 2865; time – 0:54.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Concealed Light immediately began calculating it. After a short moment, he gave out his answer: “If nothing unexpected happens, they should arrive in 7 minutes and 21 seconds.”

“Wow! Not bad.” Ye Xiu praised. Concealed Light’s mechanics might be awful, but he was quite keen in this area, and was especially good with the game’s numbers. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, on the other hand, were very lacking in this area.

“If we have so much time, we can go up a bit and kill them earlier!” Tang Rou said.

“After killing them, we have to go back to Thousand Waves Lake! In terms of time, this place is the best location.” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou heard this and appeared to understand, even though, in actuality, she didn’t. Concealed Light, on the other hand, knew that this was another calculation that had to be considered. Even though it was only a small amount of time, if it could be grasped accurately, then it would still save them some time.

Seven minutes of waiting wasn’t that long. They had found some random stuff to do to pass the time and when it was almost time, they immediately switched back to the game.

“Switch to using messages to speak.” After returning to the game, Ye Xiu messaged the team.

“Are they almost here?” Everyone switched to messaging.

“Yeah. Listen carefully. There’ll be footsteps. By listening to how loud or soft they are, it’s possible to figure out how far away they are from us.” Ye Xiu said.

As a result, the six of them crouched behind the stone and began listening intently.

“They’re here!” Ye Xiu suddenly messaged.

“Where?” Steamed Bun Invasion was completely unaware.

“Around…… 20 units away?” Su Mucheng said.

“It’s 20 now. It was 22 before.” Ye Xiu said.

The two pros had the ability to determine distance from the sound of footsteps. Even though the others had no idea whether or not the two were right or wrong, from Ye Xiu’s confident voice, they could tell that Su Mucheng wasn’t as good in this area as Ye Xiu.

“Careful. Focus on one set of footsteps.” Ye Xiu didn’t waste his teaching materials and helped everyone out.

“Crouch and go around!” Ye Xiu suddenly messaged.

Thousand Creations was very experienced in this area. Crouching while walking wouldn’t produce any footsteps. It was a necessary movement for sneak attacks from behind. He immediately crouched down and went around the big rock. He heard the sound of footsteps pass by. When his body circled around the big rock, he just happened to see the figures of five players. Thousand Creations continued to worship.

Tang Rou, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Concealed Light followed closely behind Thousand Creations. Quietly, a line of players had formed behind Misty Castle’s five players. The four looked at one another. They didn’t hear any orders from Ye Xiu, so they didn’t act.

Suddenly, they heard a gunshot. The first one to move wasn’t Ye Xiu, but Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist. They were already accustomed to this situation. In the majority of the battles, Su Mucheng’s Launcher pulled the monsters from far away.

When monsters were pulled, they would rush over. But players were different; this gunshot had been too sudden. The five weren’t noobs and immediately scattered. After seeing Cleansing Mist’s name, they almost started crying on the spot. They already knew who they had run into.

The five didn’t have any intentions of fighting. They immediately wanted to turn and run, when suddenly, they saw four characters crouching behind them stand up! The right side became their only escape route. The five didn’t need to communicate with one another and rushed in that direction. But then a character suddenly appeared in front of them with the terrifying ID floating above his head: Lord Grim.

The five players’ hands trembled and almost crouched down like the four behind them…..

Against top-tier pro players, the five truly didn’t dare to fight them head-on. The four players that were behind them seemed less scary than the pros on their sides. As a result, they turned around and charged at the players behind them. However, when they turned around, there were no longer just four of them. That Summoner had summoned all of his creatures, who now stood by the four players to form a great wall.

The five fell into despair as the other side began to attack.

There’s no need to describe the battle. Their defeat came swiftly. Afterwards was another roar by Misty Lock in the group chat: “WHAT? AGAIN!?”

“They ambushed us on the road. We didn’t think…..”

“You couldn’t even think of that! Did you guys forget to bring your brains with you when you left?” Misty Lock was truly furious and he denounced them savagely.

“This Ye Qiu is too excessive! Why isn’t he looking for Tyrannical Ambition to attack? Why is he set on our Misty Castle?” Misty Lock was unbearably depressed.

Hazy Mist wanted to say that Ye Qiu probably didn’t have any special hate towards them. It was just that their Misty Castle was showing openings and giving the other side the opportunities. Though in the end, he wasn’t able to say it and called Ye Xiu shameless along with his guild leader.

“What now?” After dying three times, the five players’ cheeks were streaked with tears. They hadn’t gone to the dungeon this entire night and their experience had already fell by 30%, and that wasn’t even including the previous massacre. In that massacre, one of them had been among the dead, so he had lost a total of 40% of his experience today. That loss was too great. An entire day wouldn’t even be enough to get it back.

“Hazy, what do you think?” Misty Lock asked.

“I think……. That the other guilds’ teams are already in the dungeon, so Ye Qiu only has our team to attack. Let’s not fight with him and hide for now. When the other dungeon teams come out, there will be new targets for him. At that time, we can take that chance to get to the dungeon!” Hazy Mist suggested.

Chapter 378 – Separate Attacks

“Misty Castle’s players might stop coming for now……”

Ye Xiu received reports from the guild members that were assigned to Congee City. This time, after reviving, Misty Castle’s dungeon team didn’t seem to have any plans for leaving the city. Two of them were taking a stroll in the market, another two had gone to the Arena and one was just standing there, staring blankly into space.

“Hahaha, they’re smart. They at least know what fear is.” Steamed Bun Invasion was delighted.

“Steamed Bun, you and Concealed Light go and train. You can leave Thousand Waves Lake to us.” Ye Xiu said. Steamed Bun Invasion and Concealed Light were more than five levels lower than Thousand Waves Lake’s monsters, so even if the two possessed the ability to beat the monsters here, the experience they would gain would be reduced because it was over the five level range. Leveling here was absolutely no good.

“Senior, will you guys be okay without us?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked in a serious tone.

“We’ll be fine. If not, we’ll call for you.” Ye Xiu said.

“No problem. You can call for us whenever you’d like.” Steamed Bun Invasion gave out a mighty expression. He turned around and looked towards Concealed Light: “Let’s go, little bro. Say bye bye to everyone.”

“F*ck off!” Concealed Light was sad. Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t stop treating him like a little bro; he was treating him like a little kid.

The two went off to their own suitable leveling areas. Ye Xiu and the other three were at the perfect level for Thousand Waves Lake, so they returned there. The guilds were no longer attacking together. If it was just a five-player team, let alone four players, Ye Xiu alone would enough to beat them. The reason they were in a group was for carrying out Ye Xiu’s usual battle spirit: if he was going to kill, then he would kill them all.

Thousand Waves Lake was as calm as it was before. There was no one in sight. Ye Xiu looked at the time; it was 1:17 A.M. Even if the guild dungeon teams started at 12 o’clock sharp, there was no way they’d be finished with their three runs already. The guilds that had participated in the Christmas Event had each sent out eight players. In other words, three of them were left out.

For newer players, it wasn’t possible for them to clear Thousand Waves Lake with just three players. However, these were all veterans from the Heavenly Domain so Ye Xiu reckoned that it would be possible for them. The top guilds were still competing for the dungeon records, so an elite team consisting of a complete five players was necessary. The three that left out would have a harder time or perhaps they might look for other guilds to form parties with?

Ye Xiu guessed, but he couldn’t be certain.

In truth, Misty Lock’s thoughts weren’t wrong. Thousand Waves Lake was too huge and the number of players Ye Xiu could use were way too little. If he had wanted to cover the entire lake and make it so that it was impossible for the other players to enter, it would be impossible with just Ye Xiu’s small group. They could only continue chasing and killing the other guilds in order to threaten the guilds to give in. For example, Misty Castle had been a successful case, where they had to give up because they were too afraid of the dangers.

“What now?” Tang Rou asked after seeing that there was no one left to fight at Thousand Waves Lake.

“Would you be fine with a 1v5?” Ye Xiu asked.

“In the water?”

“On land.”

“I could try. But if they run, there would be nothing I could do.” Tang Rou said.

“Of course, if they split up and run, there’s nothing anyone could do, but you could at least kill one of them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay!” Tang Rou nodded her head.

“What about you, Thousand Creations?” Ye Xiu asked Thousand Creations.

“God, don’t joke with me……..” Thousand Creations wiped away some sweat.

“But getting their attention shouldn’t be any problem, right? I remember you being very good at taunting!” Ye Xiu said.

Thousand Creations was speechless. The past had come back to haunt him! At the time, he had taunted because he was too weak when compared to the God, which was why he had been preyed on because the other side thought he was easier to deal with. However, that was completely different! He hadn’t known of Lord Grim’s identity at that time. Thousand Creations had felt extremely annoyed at that time. But now that he knew of Lord Grim’s true identity, there was nothing he could say. Compared to God Ye Qiu, being a worse player was a given.

“God, what do you want me to do?”

“If you can’t beat them, then lure them to where we are.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, I’ll do my best!” Thousand Creations said.

“That’s good. Next, we’ll be camping at the dungeon entrance. We don’t know which entrance they’ll be coming from, so each person will each take one! The more you can kill the better. Thousand Creations, you can just report your position and then we’ll find a way to meet up.” Ye Xiu planned.

“Understood!” the three affirmed.

“Horse Shooter, you’ll be the same as Thousand Creations.” Ye Xiu suddenly called.

“Okay.” The voice came out from the grove near the shore. The Launcher, Horse Shooter, came out from there. He had been hiding there the entire time and had killed some monsters onshore, while keeping an eye out. Horse Shooter had been the one to discover Misty Castle’s dungeon team the first time. It was too bad that his observation range was limited because he was by himself. He had only found Misty Castle’s tracks. He had continued to wander around after that, but he hadn’t been able to find anyone else.

Soon after, the five players went into the lake and split up. After each of them chose an entrance, they landed and reported to each other. Then, they began to study how to ambush the teams coming from the entrance in front of them.

In the dungeon, teams from twelve guilds were fighting hard. Amongst these, nine of them had made an alliance in order to resist the threat of Guild Happy. However, they had suffered losses in the previous water battle.

Among these nine guilds, Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition had paid materials in order to ensure their safety. Misty Castle was too scared and they didn’t dare show up at Thousand Waves Lake for now. Right now, six guilds were Ye Xiu’s targets. Ye Xiu had obviously told the other four beforehand.

Herb Garden, Howling Heights, Blossom Valley, Royal Heritage, 301, and Void Walk.

Six guilds backed by Clubs. Herb Garden didn’t need to be said. They had the champion team, Team Tiny Herb, behind them. The other five might be a bit weaker on paper, but they were all strong competitors as well. As long as they got into the playoffs, there were endless possibilities. The next champion team was never fixed.

And only these types of competitive teams would even have their guilds bicker over every gain or loss. The other three guilds who had participated in the Christmas event didn’t have that much ambition. They were satisfied with simply having their own place in the Alliance. Their thoughts weren’t to win, but rather it was to not lose. They would still try hard to compete for the dungeon records, but they didn’t have that sort of ambition to go all out like the top guilds.

They hadn’t participated in chasing and killing Lord Grim, so when Ye Xiu counterattacked, they wouldn’t be his targets.

Outside of the game, Ye Xiu created his own group chat on QQ. He called for the others to go on QQ and then sent them a complete list.

The others looked and saw that it was the predicted time for when the six guilds would finish their three runs.

“Where’d you get this from?” Thousand Creations was astonished.

“It’s just a guess!” Ye Xiu said.

“A guess?”

“The dungeon strategy they’re using is from my guide. I can look at the eight characters from each guild on the level standings and I can figure out which team composition is the most optimal. Then, I make a good guess on how long it takes for them to clear the dungeon. That’s not so hard, is it?” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, so it’s like that…….” Thousand Creations wasn’t too amazed. He had already reminded himself that he was currently playing with one of Glory’s top experts. He couldn’t keep on looking at things like he had in the past or he’d die from shock sooner or later. His view on things had to be very wide.

“Everyone, pay attention. Remember these six times.” Ye Xiu said.

The six times were around the same. The elite teams were putting in all of their efforts into the dungeon and so their characters’ strengths were around the same. The only differences were the players and some luck from the dungeons.

Before the time came, the five players killed some monsters around the lake in order to not waste any time. When the time grew near, they immediately went to the spots they had chosen beforehand.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng weren’t afraid of battles in the water, so they could choose any spot. The other three were different, however. They wanted to finish matters on land. Tang Rou was looking for a battle, but Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter were only planning on luring their opponents to where God was. They weren’t fighting a battle on mechanics, but rather, a psychological battle.

“How are things going?” The time had jumped into the range that Ye Xiu had predicted. Ye Xiu was already asking for information in the team channel.

“Nothing here.”

“Nothing here.”

“Nothing here.”

“I have…… Blue Brook Guild here……”

Thousand Creations was hiding to the side of the dungeon entrance, waiting for a character to exit out of the dungeon. But the character he saw jump out had a “Blue Brook Guild” tag on him.

“Don’t worry about Blue Brook Guild.” Ye Xiu replied.

“I know.” Thousand Creations said. He didn’t need to be concerned about Blue Brook Guild, but it was a bit awkward. Thousand Creations didn’t show himself and instead shrunk back as Blue Brook Guild’s five players left the dungeon.

“Ah! What good luck!” Su Mucheng suddenly said.

“What is it?”

“I have two teams!” On Su Mucheng’s side, one dungeon team came out. Before she could make a move, another team came out.

Herb Garden and Royal Heritage.

These two guilds’ teams had appeared in front of Su Mucheng. Su Mucheng was alone so surrounding them was impossible which meant there wasn’t any point in being sneaky. As a result, she chose not to hide and directly stood outside of the dungeon entrance. The first team was still astonished, when suddenly the second team came out and saw Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist fire a shot from her cannon.

“F*CK!!” The curses from the ten players were nearly in perfect sync as they scattered to dodge the artillery shell. The fear in their hearts only magnified Su Mucheng’s attack. It made the attack seem like an atomic bomb rather than an anti-tank missile.

Chapter 379 – Two Types of Intimidation

Thousand Wave Lake’s dungeon entrance was a cave. The echo from the cannon shot was extremely frightening. The ten players had dodged it, but they all felt that they were going to die very soon.

They didn’t think about too much. As soon as they saw Su Mucheng’s character, they immediately thought Ye Qiu would be nearby. As for any others…….. They weren’t that important. Those two were enough to wipe them all out.

None of the players had been hit by the artillery shell, but they had immediately scattered as if the shock wave from the explosion had pushed them away. Aside from the direction directly facing Cleansing Mist, every other direction had a splash sound.

“There’s no way they can kill all ten of us!”

All of them had thoughts like this. They weren’t wrong though. However, they would certainly have to sacrifice a few in order for the majority to get away.

There really was nothing that Su Mucheng could do. No matter how good she was, it wasn’t possible to catch ten players with just one person, so she chose a random one to chase after.

One poor player won the lottery. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist flew over and fired a shell while in midair. Running as fast as he could was the only thought he had in his mind as the shell exploded above his head.

It was only one hit. His character was far from dead, but not his heart because he knew that no matter what he tried, it would be of no use. This player was already similar to that of a corpse, floating on the surface of the water in a daze.

However, this pitiful behavior actually made Su Mucheng make a mistake. Su Mucheng thought that at this moment, no matter what he tried, whether it be hiding, continuing to run, or counter-attacking, the player would definitely dive into the water. Temporarily escaping from the opponent’s field of view was the most optimal choice. As a result, Su Mucheng dove into the water predicting this.

But how could she know that this brother would have given up so decisively and would stop moving? Cleansing Mist dove all the way down into the bottom of the lake and missed the player.

However, Su Mucheng quickly realized this and adapted. In a pro player’s eyes, this mistake was just a mistake. But for a regular player, they wouldn’t even have known what had happened.

In the water, Su Mucheng turned around and didn’t take notice of how poor this player’s reactions were. While she comboed several attacks, she had already begun looking for where the others had run off to and prepared to hurry and try to kill another one.

Since the player wasn’t resisting, he quickly turned into a real corpse and didn’t even revive after a long while. The player probably wasn’t even in front of his computer anymore.

Su Mucheng didn’t think about it too much. While she had been attacking, she had chosen her next target. She fired a shot under water and used the recoil to propel her character. The water swirled as Su Mucheng shot towards her next target.

Aerial Fire could be used in the water, too, and it was faster than swimming. From far away, it looked like Cleansing Mist was bobbing up and down repeatedly, leaving behind ripples after ripples. She had quickly closed in on her target.

This player had discovered that Su Mucheng had been chasing him long ago. He was so nervous that his keyboard’s up button was practically broken by now. He hated how the game wasn’t like a car. No matter how hard he pressed, his speed wouldn’t increase.

Su Mucheng had obviously chosen her target very well. Her target was neither a Gunner nor a Witch since those types of classes with high movement speed skills. She knew that even if his mechanics were ten times better than hers, if she continued to chase, she would eventually catch up. Sometimes in the game, there was nothing you could do.

In the blink of an eye, she had caught up. This target wasn’t as pitiful as the previous target and had already dived into the water long beforehand in order to escape from her line of sight. But in front of a pro, he was simply displaying his slight skill in front of an expert. It was obviously useless. Su Mucheng accurately caught up in the time that she had predicted and fired. The target tried to resist, so it took Su Mucheng ten seconds longer to kill him.

Of the ten players, Su Mucheng had successfully killed off two of them. There was no longer anyone in her line of sight, but Su Mucheng still went towards a direction to search for more.

With the ten players running in this manner, killing three of them was the limit. The third relied on luck, too. Su Mucheng remembered which direction they had initially gone off to, but whether or not the player changed directions midway was something that she had no way of knowing. After all, quite some time had passed since they had scattered.

“How’s it going on your side?” Ye Xiu asked in the team chat.

“It’d be great if pro matches played out like this.” Su Mucheng sighed in lament.

“What is it?”

“As soon as I appeared, they scattered……” Su Mucheng said.

“Ha ha, how many did you kill?”

“Currently, two. There’s still one more that I’m not sure if I’ll be able to get.”

“That’ll depend on your luck.” Ye Xiu had already guessed the situation.

“Yeah. What about you guys?” Su Mucheng asked.

“I’ve got nothing here.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Nothing here either.” Horse Shooter said.

“None.” Tang Rou said.

“None.” Thousand Creations was the same.

Because Glory had so many players, characters couldn’t pass through one another, which was why dungeon entrances were often packed with players. One entrance wasn’t enough for everyone. As a result, no matter which leveling area it was, there would always be several dungeon entrances. In Thousand Waves Lake, one dungeon entrance was an island.

Su Mucheng encountering two teams was already extremely lucky. In comparison, not finding anyone was even more likely.

“It seems like it’s about time……” Thousand Creations looked at the times that Ye Xiu had calculated.

“That’s just in theory though. It’s not that rigid in reality, so we can afford to wait a few more minutes.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Got it.”

“I still remember where a few of them were heading. Do you guys want to try and stop them?” Su Mucheng asked.

“I’ll go then!” Ye Xiu replied. Finding them would require going into the water. Only he could do that. For the others, it was hard to say whether they would win or lose.

“Oh! I have some here!” Tang Rou suddenly said excitedly.

The other three could only hear this, but Ye Xiu could see it. Ye Xiu turned his head and looked at Tang Rou’s screen to get an accurate first-hand report.

It was Guild Void Walk’s team. They were influenced by their team’s style since Void Walk had a lot of players playing as a Ghostblade.

Even though class composition was important to the guild, this sort of characteristic from fans would still be revealed. After all, these types of loyal supporters were the Club’s foundation.

As a result, Void Walk had many Ghostblades, Blue Brook Guild had many Blade Masters, Excellent Dynasty had many Battle Mages, and Tyrannical Ambitions had many Strikers. These were not coincidences.

At this moment, Void Walk’s dungeon team had two Ghostblades, who were naturally imitating Team Void’s classic Ghostblade duo. Of course, an imitation was still an imitation. If they could reach Li Xuan and Wu Yuce’s level, then they wouldn’t be here running dungeons.

Tang Rou wanted to fight though, so she didn’t hide and immediately appeared outside the dungeon entrance. As soon as the five players came out, the two sides faced each other.

The five players were all surprised, but Tang Rou wasn’t as shocking as Su Mucheng. The ten who saw Su Mucheng had immediately scattered, but the five who saw Tang Rou looked for a bit longer, thinking over what their situation was.

Besides Soft Mist, there were no signs of anyone else.

“What type of conspiracy is this!!” The five couldn’t help but feel uneasy.

“There’s something strange!” one said.

“I agree!” another agreed.

“Let me say something……” another interjected and then followed: “The other side has Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng. They wouldn’t need anything strange to deal with us, right?”

The listeners stared blankly. The two who had thought that there was something odd immediately felt embarrassed. That’s right. What was their identity? The strongest duo in all of Glory didn’t need any tricks to beat them. They were overestimating themselves too much.

“Could she be alone?” One person was still unsure.

“Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng definitely aren’t here though. If not, then she’d have attacked long ago.” one player said.

“With those words, it’s still strange!”

The five couldn’t come to a conclusion. Soft Mist raised her spear and rushed forward to attack.

“Don’t go in the water. Stay on land. Let’s see if there really are any tricks.” Knowing that there was no Ye Qiu or Su Mucheng, the five thought about fighting. They immediately got into position. Each player took a direction, guarding against the charging Soft Mist and looking towards their surroundings.

The island with the dungeon entrance was very small. If you stood on top of the rock at the cave entrance, you would get a sweeping view. In truth, there was nowhere to hide. At best, they could only be hiding behind the cave.

Even so, the five were very careful. From time to time, they would raise their heads to look up at the sky to see if there was anyone behind the cave climbing up to ambush them.

In the end, their worries were for nothing. There was only the spear in front of them that was stabbing towards them.

Soft Mist charged directly towards the Cleric on the team. Tang Rou was no longer that noob who didn’t know anything. After playing for some time and learning this and that from Ye Xiu, she at least had this sort of basic knowledge.

In a one against many, if the Cleric wasn’t killed off quickly, the opponents would be able to heal up. Even if they couldn’t kill her directly, they would be able to slowly whittle her down.

Killing the Cleric was the first step for battle.

Chapter 380 – Key

This important strategy was very basic. Anyone with a bit of game knowledge understood this. Whenever there was a team battle, the Clerics would always be protected. Even though this was only a small-scale battle right now, with many against one, the five players didn’t dare be careless, since they knew of Tang Rou’s history and immediately went into a team formation. Four players formed a square with the Cleric being protected in the middle.

Soft Mist was charging head-on. If she wanted to reach the Cleric, she would have to break through the two players in front.

One of these two players was a Ghostblade, while the other was a Knight. The guild’s elite team coordinated well together. The Knight moved forward with his shield raised to meet the attacker. The Ghostblade stayed behind and sent up a Ghost Boundary.

Apart from reducing damage, the shield was also important for reducing effects from attacks.

For example, the Battle Mage’s Falling Flower Palm was a Blow Away attack that would cause the player hit by it to be sent flying and knocked down to the ground. However, if the Palm hit a shield, the Blow Away effect wouldn’t appear, and instead it would be reduced to a Knock Back. The character would be forced back a few steps, but he wouldn’t be knocked down to the ground.

This sort of basic knowledge was something that Tang Rou already knew. But she still sent out a Falling Flower Palm as if she didn’t know this, and it hit the Knight’s shield.

With the shield protecting the body and a Cleric to heal, the Knight ignored the hit. After being hit by the Falling Flower Palm and staggering backwards, the Ghostblade had to dodge. Crashing into each other would at least interrupt his Ghost Boundary’s cast.

This slight dodge forced him away from the Knight’s protection range and caused a slight change in position. A cold light slashed across. The Ghostblade was caught unprepared and was flung into the sky.

The Ghostblade hastily adjusted his camera and saw Soft Mist stand up from a crouching position. Her position was extremely brazen. She was actually right next to the Knight’s shield. After pushing the Knight back with a Falling Flower Palm, she rolled forward to stay close and seized an opening that wouldn’t have been considered one to a normal player.

“Shield Attack!!!” the Ghostblade roared. Because he was a member of the team, he knew that when Knights had a shield, it was true that the larger the surface of the Shield, the better the protection. However, if it was too large, the shield might obstruct his line of sight.

His teammate Knight’s Maple Leaf Shield had an extremely large surface. In a dungeon, Knights loved to use this type of huge shield. However, in a PVP battle with many variations, Knights had to be careful when choosing a shield. The best examples could be seen in the pro scene. The self-made shields in the pro scene were never large because large shields weren’t suitable.

Right now, this Knight had suffered from his large shield. Soft Mist’s roll had been very precise. She didn’t bump into him and used the shield as a cover to stick close to the Knight without him knowing.

The Ghostblade in midair saw this and naturally gave a warning.That Knight hadn’t completely realized the situation, but when he heard his brother shouting, he didn’t hesitate and immediately slammed his shield forward with a Shield Attack.

However, Soft Mist had already rolled to the side. She stabbed forward with her spear and pierced through the Ghostblade. Targets stabbed in the air would be blown away a bit. The Ghostblade was sent flying by the attack to the others, who were still studying whether there was someone waiting to ambush them in the cave.

Under his warning, the brothers were able to dodge this human meat bag. Tang Rou ignored them. With just a few moves, she had circled around one of the two characters in front and sent the other one flying away. The Cleric that had been originally been protected was now completely exposed.

Clerics weren’t so powerless that they had no means of surviving in battle. However, he was still too slow compared to Tang Rou. Tang Rou’s fingers flew across the keyboard. The spear in Soft Mist’s hand danced around, sticking to the Cleric. Ye Xiu also felt very gratified seeing this. There was finally some skill in her moves. She at least understood how to link her normal attacks and skills together. For players with fast hand speed like Tang Rou, these types of combo fighting styles should be better.

Void Walk’s five-player team consisted of two Ghostblades, one Knight, one Cleric, and one Elementalist.

The two Ghostblades were completely imitating Team Void’s Ghostblade duo. One was a Phantom Demon, while the other was a hybrid.

At this moment, the two Ghostblades were on one side and the Knight was behind her. Tang Rou observed her surroundings. She comboed a few strikes on the Cleric and, not waiting for the Knight and the Ghostblade to come rescue the Cleric, she used a Falling Flower Palm to blast the Cleric in the direction of the Elementalist.

The Elementalist wasn’t just sitting there doing nothing. He had been casting magic attacks at Soft Mist the entire time.

But to his dismay, it was as if she wasn’t looking at his magic. All of his magic attacks landed on her.

None of the magic attacks were able to interrupt Soft Mist’s attacks. And it was only now that she seemed to suddenly realize that there was an Elementalist there. The hit flying Cleric shot towards the Elementalist. At this instant, the Elementalist even felt gratified that he was no longer being regarded as air.

Not just the team, but even the pro Ye Xiu was shocked by Tang Rou’s strategy.

This girl was always this bold and fierce. Ye Xiu understood what she was thinking. She wanted to take down the Cleric at all costs. This was because she believed firmly that if she couldn’t take down the Cleric, her efforts would be for nothing.

The Cleric was flying towards the Elementalist, who obviously avoided him. At this moment, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist already had all of her Chasers buffing her and she quickly chased after them.

Elementalists didn’t have much close combat ability. He immediately cast an Ice Wall in order to try and block her. In the end, Soft Mist went directly towards the Ice Wall. She didn’t feel that it was a pity using her hard to come by Chasers on the Ice Wall. The Ice Wall shattered in the blink of an eye, causing the Elementalist to go wide-eyed in shock.

He couldn’t tell if this was being quick, being fierce, or both.

Soft Mist dashed through the shattered Ice Wall. It was already too late for the Elementalist to widen the distance. He was launched into the air by a Sky Strike and then sent flying towards the two Ghostblades with a Falling Flower Palm.

Ye Xiu was still watching on the side. Tang Rou’s play style was copying his.

In the battle at Line Canyon, where Ye Xiu was fighting several opponents, he had the opponents flying around like pinballs. Tang Rou’s intent was the same.

Ye Xiu could only sigh, seeing this. It was pretty impressive that Tang Rou could think of using this, and with her mechanics, it was certainly possible to do it. However, she was still a new player, so there were still areas where she didn’t know what to do.

This type of strategy was something that Ye Xiu could use, but she couldn’t.

It wasn’t an issue of mechanics, nor an issue of experience, but rather her class.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was an unspecialized. At level 20, he had access to 120 skills. Because of all of these skills, Ye Xiu had incredible controlling ability. However, Tang Rou was using a Battle Mage. Even at Level 70, she wouldn’t have that many skills.

In other words, that type of control over the field by Ye Xiu couldn’t be done in any normal circumstance. In order to copy his strategy, besides unspecialized players, it could only be done with several players. Only several players could have enough skills to create such a pinball scenario.

Tang Rou wanted to do it with just her alone. She would soon discover the problem: she didn’t have enough skills to use.

“That’s no good.” Ye Xiu had seen the problem and he wouldn’t not point it out, so he went up to tell Tang Rou.

“What?” Tang Rou was too busy to turn her head.

“You can’t control the field like this. You don’t have enough skills to use. Plus, if you keep on spamming your skills, you’ll run out of mana.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then I’ll just kill however many I can kill!” Tang Rou said.

“Huh?” Ye Xiu stared blankly. This sort of compromise didn’t seem like this sister’s style! When did such a sudden change happen?

“I’ll just do my best.” Tang Rou said.

Ye Xiu began to sweat. Sure enough, this sister continued to fight with everything she had.

The Elementalist transformed into a missile as Tang Rou pounced towards the Cleric again.

Void Walk’s team completely saw through Tang Rou’s intent. Their team’s leader was the Knight. Seeing this, he suddenly shouted: “Into the water.”

“Water?”

This word had left a deep mark in the elites’ hearts. They hadn’t thought that they were that bad in the water, or at least so much so that two players were enough to wipe out dozens of them.

“She can’t water!” The Knight couldn’t find the right words to use.

For a successful team, listening to the shot caller was very important. Even though the Cleric’s mind was still in a mess, he still heard his captain’s orders. He hastily sprinted towards the water, as Soft Mist chased after him.

Tang Rou didn’t think that her opponents would have realized what her big weakness was. The water……. She really couldn’t do anything in the water. She was fast enough to catch up and stop the Cleric from entering the water. But if she did that, the others would be able to catch up to the Cleric and the distance that she had taken great efforts to widen would be gone.

“Rotate.” At this moment, a calm voice suddenly sounded out. Tang Rou was startled for a bit, but she quickly understood. She sprinted to the Cleric and pushed the Cleric out to the side.

Everyone had already understood the key to this battle. With the Cleric sent flying to the side, they went to chase after him. However, the Battle Mage had the speed advantage with the Chasers and was faster than them. When the Cleric climbed back up, he was still thinking of going into the water, but Soft Mist had already arrived. Her Falling Flower Palm was still on cooldown, so she used a Sky Strike into a Dragon Tooth instead, to send the Cleric flying.

“If you calculate the direction and distance well enough, you can do it so that the others won’t be able to catch up.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 381 – Remote Control

“They have the numbers advantage though. What do I do if they split up and continue to move forward?” Tang Rou asked.

“This is just a way of getting more time. Once you get rid of the Cleric, you’ll be good to go, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“Got it.” Tang Rou suddenly understood. During this time, her hands never stopped. The Cleric was practically tumbling nonstop. Even if he succeeded in using a Quick Recover, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist could still catch up in time to send him flying again. All of the attacks she used were able to push him a quite a bit of distance away in a circle around the small island. It looked as if he were only a few steps away from jumping into the lake, but he could never find the opportunity to do so.

The Cleric hoped for his allies to help him, but none of them were able to do so. They were always just a bit too far. Battle Mages had a faster movement speed than the other four classes after being buffed by Neutral Chasers. She was running while attacking him, but her movement speed didn’t slow down. The Cleric immediately understood that her playing style was quite quick, being able to complete all of these attacks while still moving.

“You two, cut her off from that side!” The Knight also realized that if they continued chasing like this, they wouldn’t be able to catch her. It was fortunate enough that this was a small island though. If not for that, the other side would have simply be able to continue pushing the Cleric forward. The others knew of their Cleric’s skill level and they knew that he wasn’t weak. But right now, he was being kicked around like a football and was unable to do anything to resist. The others already had a good idea about Soft Mist’s skill level. If they didn’t have their numbers advantage, they would have turned tail and ran by now.

“Persist for a bit more,” the Knight shouted.

“Hurry up!” How could the Cleric not be worried?

Tang Rou was constantly turning her camera to observe the field. She saw that the other side had split up into two groups of two players each. The two groups were running in opposite directions and were obviously planning on cutting her off. Tang Rou was currently thinking of what to do, when Ye Xiu said: “Don’t be in a hurry. Wait for my command.”

“Okay……” Tang Rou replied. She honestly didn’t know what to do in order to break out of this predicament.

After pushing the Cleric around another three times, Ye Xiu suddenly said: “Turn left for the next attack.”

Before he finished speaking, Soft Mist had already rushed in front of the Cleric. When Tang Rou heard Ye Xiu’s words, she hastily changed her push forward to a push to the left. The Cleric immediately tumbled to the left and Soft Mist continued to chase after him.

“Falling Flower Palm him once.” Ye Xiu followed. Tang Rou heard the order and used a Falling Flower Palm. The direction that she had chosen had been accurately grasped. Too far, and the Cleric would have enough time to get up by the time she closed in on him. Too close, and her cooldowns might not be up in time. As a result, every one of her palms had been done with just enough power, just so that the Cleric had no way of getting up. Her grasp on this technique might not be very good yet, but she at least wasn’t blindly letting loose. Her moves were starting to become more and more flexible.

“Sky Strike, jump, Circle Swing!”

Tang Rou didn’t bother thinking too much about Ye Xiu’s orders. She simply did as she was told.

The Cleric was hit by the Circle Swing and was smashed onto the top of the cave.

“Jump, Dragon Tooth, go around!”

Tang Rou was having a very comfortable time with Ye Xiu’s commands. The four players, who had just barely been about to pincer her, were now heading in the same direction.

“Stop for a bit and give him a good beating!”

This time, the Cleric didn’t get pushed away immediately. Instead, he received a violent beating.

“Good. Continue pushing now and head towards the water.” Ye Xiu called.

The battle spear thrust forward and the Cleric was driven to the edge of the water. He had healing skills, but he didn’t have the chance to use them. As a Cleric, being forced to use potions to heal was the same as if he had lost his identity! In addition, his health potion was currently on cooldown. From the damage he had taken, the Cleric knew that he didn’t have enough time to wait to down another potion. He would either die or be saved by his friends.

In any case, anything he did was for nothing, so the Cleric could only message: “Hurry! I’m going to die soon.”

“She’s so cunning! We were so close to trapping her just before.” The other four were trying their hardest to catch up.

“Hurry, hurry, hurry! I’m about to die!” The Cleric was extremely agitated.

In the time it took for these few messages to be exchanged, the Cleric had already been pushed into the edge of the water.

“Hurry up and kill him. If your hands are fast enough, it’ll be no problem for you.” Ye Xiu said.

These sorts of words were very effective for Tang Rou. No matter what, she didn’t want Ye Xiu to say that her “hand speed wasn’t fast enough”. She knew very well that her greatest strength right now was her hand speed. If she was looked down upon even in this area, then she’d truly feel too ashamed.

“Pa pa pa pa pa pa…….”

The sounds of repeated keyboard taps and mouse clicks mixed together. Basic attacks and skills chained together onto the Cleric. The Cleric hadn’t thought that his opponent could attack even faster. He had originally held great confidence that he would be rescued in time. But as his health quickly dropped, his hopes gradually died out as well. He saw his four friends getting closer and closer, but it seemed like he wouldn’t be able to hold on until they arrived.

“Hang on!” The Elementalist was a long-range attacker. As soon as he was in attack range, he immediately cast a spell.

Tang Rou’s camera quickly glanced at the Elementalist and saw that he was chanting. Ye Xiu’s voice could already be heard: “He’s using Ice Wall. Go forward two units!”

Tang Rou hastily attacked and moved forward. Right as she completed Ye Xiu’s orders, she heard a crack as three ice walls stood erect in a triangle formation. If she hadn’t gone forward two units, she would have been trapped by the Ice Wall. For the Elementalist to instantly put up an Ice Wall accurately was quite impressive.

“D*mn it! Just barely!” The Elementalist shouted in a depressed tone.

“Stop talking!!” The other three were just as depressed.

In truth, if the Elementalist hadn’t yelled out a “Hang on”, Tang Rou wouldn’t have turned her camera to look at them. And if she hadn’t seen them, Ye Xiu wouldn’t have known that the Elementalist was going to cast an Ice Wall.

Tang Rou was feeling quite guilty, too. She knew that if it weren’t for Ye Xiu, there would have been no way that she would have been able to make that sort of split second decision. She would have most likely been trapped by the Ice Wall. With her fast hand speed, she would have been able to get out of the Ice Wall very quickly, but she needed all the time she could get to kill off the Cleric. That small amount of delay could have been enough to turn the whole situation around.

“So dangerous…….” Tang Rou celebrated, but her hands didn’t stop moving. The sounds of repeated tapping and clicking continued to sound out. The Cleric saw that even his friends could not do anything to stop the opponent. In the end, his last shred of hope disappeared. While the Elementalist was chanting another spell, he saw Soft Mist suddenly leave. She took her spear and made one last strike on the Cleric. The Cleric’s body finally fell over.

The Cleric’s name on the team list had faded away. He was now dead. However, because he hadn’t chosen to revive back at the city yet, he was still with the team.

“Into the water!” Ye Xiu gave Tang Rou a new command.

“Ah?” Tang Rou was startled. Wouldn’t going into the water expose her weakness? Could he be wanting her to practice fighting in the water?

Tang Rou was unsure, but had her Soft Mist go into the water. The four players chased closely after her as she was already in their attack range.

“Go down, turn around, swim back, flip over!” Ye Xiu continued to give orders. Tang Rou finally realized that with this prompting, there was nothing she needed to worry about. It was kind of boring to play though!

“Don’t play so mechanically! Be more attentive and find your tempo.” Ye Xiu saw Tang Rou controlling her Soft Mist as she was commanded to do.

“Hm?”

“Dragon Tooth!”

“Dragon Tooth? Right now?” Tang Rou questioned, but still did as she was told.

She had originally thought that using the Dragon Tooth was completely wrong, but it turned out that it accurately hit one of the Ghostblades.

Tang Rou followed up with an attack. But when she used Sky Strike, she missed because of the water.

“Whether you hit or miss, pay attention to them!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, I understand.” Tang Rou understood what Ye Xiu was saying. Afterwards, she didn’t stop following Ye Xiu’s orders. Her line of sight was no longer on the enemies. That capability had been completely given to Ye Xiu. With Ye Xiu observing the opponents and giving her directions, she focused on observing the timing for her strikes and their effectiveness.

“F*ck me! This…… what’s going on…..”

The four players weren’t stupid. After exchanging a few blows, they felt that something was off. This sister didn’t seem like she was clueless about water battles. It could be said that she was an expert! If they kept on fighting her, the four players wouldn’t stand a chance. None of them had much skill in water battles. They just had the numbers advantage and wanted to go down to bully someone. How could they know that their opponent was actually extremely good in the water?

“F*ck! Too crafty.” The four felt like they had fallen into a trap. They didn’t dare fight in the water anymore. They only wanted to get back up onto shore now.

Tang Rou was listening to Ye Xiu’s orders, so she was slower. Completely trapping the four of them wasn’t very likely. However, she had still been able to successfully catch two of them. Under water, these four players were pretty much dead weight.

Chapter 382 – One Battle After Another

Ye Xiu’s orders continued to be carried out. Even though there were lots of problems with this method, it was more than enough when facing against these two opponents. The two players who were caught by Tang Rou were the Knight and Elementalist. Right now, they had no means of resisting. Their only thoughts were to get onto land. However, it seemed as if the water was doing damage to them. Every time they swam a stroke, their health went down a chunk.

The two obviously knew that all this was due to Soft Mist’s attacks. But what could they do? In the water, they already had a deep scar in their hearts. Seeing Soft Mist move so agilely in the water, their hearts wanted to sink into the depths. How could they have any thoughts about fighting back? The only thing the Knight could do was swing his shield around randomly, hoping that he could block a few of the attacks. However, under Ye Xiu’s experienced eyes, trying to win through sheer luck was just a dream. Soft Mist’s attacks avoided his random shield swings and continued to directly strike him.

“It’s no good……”

The two had already drunk their best potions. There was nothing they could do about their potion cooldowns and their Cleric had died. What hope could they have?

“What about those two?” The Knight’s health finally dropped down to zero and his character floated in suspension. He knew that the Elementalist would definitely die with him, but it seemed like the two Ghostblades had successfully escaped.

His dead spirit’s viewpoint slowly floated higher. The Knight saw that the two Ghostblades had climbed back up onto the island and were currently standing on the shoreside, looking helplessly towards the water.

“What are you doing? RUN!” The Knight quickly revived and messaged the two of them.

The Elementalist was going to die. With only the two of them remaining, whether it was on land or in the water, they still weren’t going to be Soft Mist’s opponents. They should be using this time to run, not stalling around, waiting to die.

The Knight only regretted that they didn’t immediately run. Otherwise, they might have had to sacrifice one player, but two fewer players still would have died.

“I underestimated the opponent too much……” the Knight cried. After reviving in the city and telling the two to hurry up and run, he left the game and went into the QQ group chat to give a report.

When he went into the group chat, his comrade Cleric was already wailing remorsefully inside! Their guild leader hadn’t said a word the entire time. The Knight wasn’t sure about the current situation was, so he sent an emoticon of a crying face.

“You also died?” The Cleric asked after seeing it.

The Knight typed out a “Yeah” and then saw the Elementalist’s name pop up, too. He didn’t cry. Instead, he sent an angry face: “I died, too.” The group chat suddenly fell into silence. No one said anything.

And at the same time, Su Mucheng was going along a route based off of her initial observations. She didn’t find her original target, but she happened to bump into someone else.

The guys from the guilds knew that they all had to flee. Every one of them had hidden their guild names. But what did that do? All of these characters were on the tenth server’s level standings. Even if they died another ten times, their names would still be there. Su Mucheng saw him and wanted to confirm. She opened up the level standings and checked the player’s name. After five seconds, she confirmed who it was and saw that he was from Royal Style.

Su Mucheng had encountered a combined total of two guilds. The previous two players that she had killed were both from Herb Garden. After fleeing far away, this Royal Style player was praising himself for his outstanding luck. However, if he had just gone straight instead of going on this random path, he wouldn’t have bumped into Su Mucheng. His luck really was outstanding!

Su Mucheng Aerial Fired her way over. The waves split apart, causing this lucky talent to turn his viewpoint to look over to see Cleansing Mist behind him. He had originally thought that he had escaped from danger but his mood immediately turned from heaven to hell. Smashing his face to the ground wasn’t enough to vent all his emotions.

Fight back? He didn’t have any thoughts of doing that. This player also thought about playing dive deep down to see if he could hide. But as soon as his head entered the water, a cannon shot lifted up the waves, carrying him into the sky. The scene appeared that much more eye-catching on the calm surface of the lake.

He never went under the water ever again. He became like a skipping stone, bouncing around on top of the water. When everything turned still again, his health had dropped to zero.

“I caught one. It doesn’t look like there will be anyone else.” Su Mucheng messaged, while looking around to see if luck would give her another one.

“If I had known this would happen, I would have gone with you.”

Ye Xiu hadn’t found anyone at his dungeon entrance. He had already given up and was now wandering around randomly to see if he could bump into someone.

“I killed four of them. I’m currently heading towards where the fifth one is going. I might be able to catch up.” Tang Rou also said. Ye Xiu obviously knew about her situation. Her report was just for the others on the team to know.

“Which direction? Do you need me to help block him?” Su Mucheng asked.

“No need. I might bump into him.” Ye Xiu was now heading towards that Ghostblade’s direction.

The two Ghostblades had split apart. Tang Rou could only catch one of them. She had chased one, the same one as Su Mucheng. As for the other one, she had remembered which direction he had gone off to. After finishing off her target, she could try and chase towards that direction.

Ye Xiu saw this and, since he wasn’t doing anything, naturally went over to intercept him.

At this moment, three of them were busy. Only Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter were sitting on their island, silently going around in circles.

Ye Xiu hadn’t forgotten about these two. He messaged: “I don’t think anyone is dungeoning anymore. Thousand Creations, Horse Shooter, you two can leave. Go to Sin City. If you meet any other guilds, do what you want.”

“Sin City?” The two questioned, but immediately understood.

“Of course, Sin City.” Ye Xiu chuckled.

Sin City might be of a lower level than Thousand Waves Lake, but the experience from Sin City’s dungeon was still much better than killing wild monsters at Thousand Waves Lake. This was why, no matter the level, players always ran two dungeons. One was suitable for their level, while the other was a grade lower. Some even ran three dungeons. After all, aside from the experience in dungeons, better items would be dropping, too.

“If you’re going to Sin City, then hurry! You might be able to directly intercept them.” Su Mucheng said.

“Yeah, everyone head towards the shore! But if you run into someone on the way, don’t miss an opportunity to kill him. It’s just these players anyways.” Ye Xiu said.

The five players were all in different locations, so they all headed towards the shore in different directions.

Thousand Waves Lake was so vast. With less than a hundred players there, finding someone by chance was very difficult. The five continued to scout as they swam, but didn’t find anyone else when they reached the shore. On the shore, they scouted around once again, but didn’t find anything. As a result, they headed straight for Sin City.

Sin City wasn’t as empty as Thousand Waves Lake. In normal circumstances, this was where the highest leveled players would be at. There were numerous players in a server, so there would naturally be many at the same level stage. Right now, Sin City was packed with players.

“There are so many players here. How troublesome!” The five were outside of the entrance to a prison, Sin City’s dungeon. When they looked, there were quite a few dungeon teams and quite a few of them were from enemy guilds. Seeing them, Thousand Creations immediately called: “Ah! So many guild players. We’re going to be found out!”

Thousand Creations, who loved to kill steal monsters, was the most sensitive to being found.

“Stay calm.” Ye Xiu said, “Even if we’re found, don’t worry.”

“Can we still kill them?” Thousand Creations said.

“Even if we can’t, we can at least let them know.” Ye Xiu said.

At this moment, there really were quite a few players who noticed Lord Grim’s group and they immediately reported it to their guilds. These players had only received orders to pay attention to Lord Grim’s movements. The higher ups didn’t say what to do if they found them. After all, getting pressured by Ye Xiu’s group wasn’t anything glamorous. The guilds backed by Clubs cared about their appearances, so they hid some things from their members. The players from the new servers weren’t as loyal though.

The top guilds pretty much received notifications that Lord Grim’s group was at Sin City’s dungeon entrance. None of their reactions were alike.

“F*ck me! What do these guys plan on doing? What are they planning?” Misty Lock was quite sad and angry. They had suffered greatly at Thousand Waves Lake and chose to retreat. Retreating didn’t mean that they were just going to stand there and do nothing. They went to the lower grade leveling area and ran over to run Sin City’s dungeon. It had only been peaceful for a short while, when suddenly the other side unexpectedly started chasing after them. It was too unlucky.

“Did you guys offend Ye Qiu somehow?” Misty Lock talked to Hazy Mist. He was already at this step.

“No….. we didn’t……” Hazy Mist said. When they had come into contact with each other, he hadn’t known that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. He was a bit angry when they were haggling over dungeon guides, but Hazy Mist didn’t think that he went as far as to offend Ye Qiu.

“Then why does he keep on focusing on us?” Misty Lock said.

“Maybe it’s just a coincidence?” Hazy Mist said.

“How could it be so coincidental!” Misty Lock didn’t believe it. He felt like he was right.

“What now?” Hazy Mist asked. After this information came, the five brothers in the dungeon were notified as well. Reports said that they had narrowly missed getting wiped out in the dungeon because of nervousness. After clearing away a mob, the five stopped their advancement and went into the group chat to talk about what to do. Hazy Mist didn’t want to say that they had no ideas in front of everyone, so he opened up a private window with his guild leader.

“Tell the dungeon teams in Sin City to not go into the dungeon. I’m going to contact the other guilds.” As the manager of a guild backed by a Club, he wasn’t an idiot. Misty Lock was finally going to make a move!

Chapter 383 – Take Advantage of the Opportunity

Outside of the Sin City dungeon, more and more players began to gather together. There were always lots of players outside the dungeon, so no one noticed the change.

The extra characters just stood there in front of an entrance. Their viewpoints were pointed towards the dungeon entrance, as if they were going to go in at any time. However, those who paid attention to them would discover that these characters had already been standing there for at least twenty minutes without going in.

Time continued to pass. Players without a team, who were busy organizing wild parties, began noticing these strange fellows.

They seemed to be in a party and no one was sure if they had enough players. Others sent them requests, but they didn’t seem to even look at them and just left them. All of their energy seemed to be focused on that dungeon entrance.

Among this crowd, players gradually began to notice a few characters. These characters were on the tenth server level standings, so quite a few players recognized them. Quite a few of them were here.

High-level characters still needed to train. Sin City was a suitable dungeon for them, so that wasn’t the strange part. The strange part was that these players were all pushed into this one dungeon entrance. In addition, they were the same as those extras. They just stood there, staring without any response.

A few curious players had already begun paying attention to these characters.

They moved!

The curious players suddenly discovered that these characters suddenly moved.

Their feet shuffled forward a tiny bit as if they were ready to rush forward at any minute. Their hands were raised up a bit as if they were going to attack at any time. Their viewpoints all focused towards a certain direction.

The curious players also moved their viewpoints in that direction and saw an even more famous Lord Grim.

Even though Lord Grim wasn’t the player with the highest level in the tenth server, he was most definitely the most famous player there, and was undoubtedly the strongest as well.

Were these players waiting for Lord Grim?

The curious players were wondering this. Then, they saw that Lord Grim had a few characters beside him. They weren’t able to see their names, when their characters disappeared.

If a character disappeared in front of a dungeon entrance, then they obviously went into the dungeon.

Outside of the dungeon entrance, the strange fellows turned into statues again.

The faces of the leaders of these strange fellows, the overall guild leaders of the seven top guilds, turned ugly.

“He’s clearly playing with us.” Herb Garden’s Arisaema gave his opinion.

Misty Castle’s guild leader, Misty Lock, had the ugliest expression on his face. Their guild had suffered the most losses tonight. He had been the one to look for the other guilds and set up this operation. He had thought that they would be able to cause a ruckus. But all that ended up happening was them being forced to stand outside of the dungeon entrance.

His train of thought was very simple. This was because their Clubs cared very much about their image. After Lord Grim created his guild, they had the clear advantage in overall strength. On the surface, they had to follow the rules, and could only resort to backhanded methods.

And now, Lord Grim’s group was attacking back and killing them. They had chased them all the way from Thousand Waves Lake to Sin City.

Thousand Waves Lake didn’t have any other players; the top guilds could ally together and fight. But in Sin City, they couldn’t hide from the public eye.

However, if Lord Grim was the one to take the initiative and attack their players in Sin City, then fighting back was completely reasonable. No one could say that they were in the wrong.

Once they knew that Lord Grim’s group had chased them all the way to Sin City, Misty Lock was first filled with grief and anger and then quickly came up with this plan. He had the ability to gather up the other guilds backed by Clubs. Crying wasn’t his only skill.

Misty Castle wasn’t the only guild to notice Lord Grim’s appearance at Sin City. After knowing this, they had also begun discussing a countermeasure. This was especially so for the other three guilds that had been attacked at Thousand Waves Lake: Herb Garden, Royal Heritage and Void Walk. Even though their losses hadn’t been as great, they were still very sad and angry.

At this moment, Misty Lock contacted them and told them his plan.

The other guild leaders heard him and immediately felt that this was a good opportunity as well. If they took advantage of this opportunity well, they might even be able to use this as an excuse to attack Guild Happy and utilize their advantage in overall strength.

As a result, the top guilds deployed their troops and sent everyone who was at Sin City’s level stage to gather there. Even if they couldn’t use this as an excuse to attack Guild Happy, they were determined to use their advantage in numbers to wipe out Lord Grim’s group.

But first they needed Lord Grim to initiate.

The guilds backed by Clubs also had their own annoyances. It was like those large sects from Wuxia stories. All of their actions had to be proper and reasonable. They couldn’t be like those bandits who did whatever they wanted to do.

Before this, everyone had been working their hearts out to avoid Lord Grim killing them. Now, at a different place, they were impatiently waiting for Lord Grim to hurry up and attack them.

But it seemed like Lord Grim was completely uninterested in these not even Level 40 extras. The guild leaders knew that their opponent’s goal wasn’t here, so they also sent Level 40 and up characters to attract his enmity.

But then they watched as Lord Grim’s group just enter the Sin City dungeon.

The guild leaders, who had been filled with hope, immediately turned cold.

“Maybe he didn’t see us?” someone guessed.

“No way. How could he not have seen us?” Their plan had been executed very on point. The guild leaders had no idea why. They had personally seen the plan through. Their high-level characters stood out in the crowd, showing off their might. How could they have not been seen?

“Should we wait?” someone suggested.

“Let’s wait. Get ready and wait for them to come out.”

As a result, the scene in the beginning appeared again. Everyone just stood there staring stupidly out into space. They were all waiting for Lord Grim’s group to come out of the dungeon, and were hoping that Lord Grim would attack them, so they could use this as an excuse to fight back.

The heavens didn’t disappoint those who tried. The time had finally come. Some were ready to attack. Some stood in a position that was easy to be attacked.

But Lord Grim didn’t even turn his head to look at them and entered the dungeon again.

Herb Garden’s guild leader, Arisaema, had previously been doubtful about whether Lord Grim had seen them or had chosen to ignore them. This time, he was sure that they had been played.

“In this half hour…… Not only have our elites not leveled, our second-string teams haven’t done anything either.” Arisaema said.

“This…… This guy’s too crafty!” Misty Lock said helplessly.

“He also understood our thoughts and wasn’t tricked by us. He also used this opportunity to waste our time.” West Riding Wind said gloomily.

Everyone went silent. It was true that normal players may not understand some of the choices that guilds backed by Clubs had to make. But how could a pro player like God Ye Qiu not know? He already knew that there was no way that they could attack him at this place. If they did, it would have to be some open accounts. However, at this point, most of their open accounts had been sent to infiltrate the other guilds. The remaining few could deal with a normal player, but they were against two All-Star-level pros, who also had the level advantage. Sending their open accounts to attack was just asking to die. It wasn’t as if the top guilds hadn’t thought of using their open accounts. It was just that their strength wasn’t enough.

All of this might have been completely seen through by their opponent, which was why he wasn’t afraid. Every step he made, whether he fought or not, caused their top guilds to suffer losses. And him? At Thousand Waves Lake, they were clearing monsters. In Sin City, they were running the dungeon. Even though they weren’t completely focused on leveling, it didn’t delay them too much.

The guild leaders couldn’t come to a conclusion. They could only quietly make their own orders. The players outside the dungeon entrance gradually went away.

The curious players had thought that there would be something fun to watch and were now stunned. During this time, those players just standing there seemed to have moved for a single instant when Lord Grim appeared. And now they just left. Had they been waiting there the entire time for Lord Grim to look at them? Was this some sort of deep love?

When Ye Xiu’s group came out of their second dungeon run at Sin City, they saw that those bunch of characters had left.

“They all left…….” Tang Rou’s voice carried a bit of lament. She felt that it was a pity that they hadn’t fought.

“Too bad……” Ye Xiu also had the same tone as her. He obviously didn’t feel that it was a pity that they didn’t fight, but rather that he had wasted only a bit of their time. If the other side had stood there stupidly all night, Ye Xiu would have been much more satisfied.

“Do we continue?” Tang Rou asked.

“We still have one more. We’re all here, too, so let’s go. We have to use this time well.” Ye Xiu said.

As a result, the five once again ran the dungeon again. After coming out, it was very late. It wasn’t convenient for Su Mucheng to play all night, so she logged off. Horse Shooter had come because of Su Mucheng, so he followed after his idol. When he saw that Su Mucheng had left, his enthusiasm died and he also logged off after saying bye.

“It’s just us three now. There’s nothing to do here, so let’s go to Thousand Waves Lake!” Ye Xiu said.

“Are we going to keep on causing them trouble?” Tang Rou asked.

“Leveling is our main priority. Causing trouble will only be when it’s convenient.” Ye Xiu said.

“Understood!” Tang Rou replied.

“How is it? It’s fun, no?” Ye Xiu asked Thousand Creations, “You probably feel very happy stirring up trouble everywhere, right?”

Thousand Creations was speechless. Was he really the type of person that liked to cause trouble? But after thinking for a bit, Thousand Creations discovered that he really was that type of person……

Chapter 384 – Even Sitting Idle is Scary

This night had not gone well for Herb Garden, Howling Heights, Misty Castle, Blossom Valley, Royal Heritage, 301, and Void Walk. Normally, they were the mighty top-tier experts in the game, but tonight it was as if they were in a nightmare.

With their levels, after running their dungeons, Thousand Waves Lake was the most suitable place for leveling. These seven guilds didn’t want to agree to Lord Grim’s conditions. They hoped for good luck and played hide and seek.

Their plan wasn’t that risky either. Thousand Waves Lake was such a large leveling area. There was a very low chance of coincidentally bumping into someone else. After Ye Xiu’s group returned to Thousand Waves Lake, they also completed quests and cleared monsters to level. However, they weren’t like others, who only went around in a small area. They were wandering around the entire leveling area with the purpose of coincidentally bumping into someone.

It was quite unfortunate for the characters that they came across. Ye Xiu always had a method to close in on his opponents unaware. Even when they discovered each other at the same time, with Ye Xiu’s skill, he was able to catch up to his target.

It didn’t happen often. All the way up until the day lit up, this had only happened three times. Three times might not be a lot, but it proved that it was possible that it could happen. They had originally thought that completing quests and killing monsters would be a very relaxed task, but because of this, they had to take precautions. That night, they circled around and around until their minds went dizzy and their hands became sore. There was nothing else that they could do! They had to keep a lookout around them at all times in order to prevent being bumped into.

As for Ye Xiu’s group, their night passed by like any other. It might have even turned out better. Besides clearing monsters and completing quests, they also held hopes of finding someone else. It was a small plus in the course of their leveling. Being filled with hope was a wonderful feeling.

“The sun’s up.” When these words came out, most all-nighters would look exhausted. But today, Thousand Creations didn’t seem tired at all. His tone even carried a hint of lament. Tonight, he had actually played with his idol, God Ye Qiu, all night. Thousand Creations could only feel that this was a dream. He nearly pinched his leg to check.

“Yup, the sun’s up. Go rest!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay……” Thousand Creations was reluctant to part: “God, when are you going to be on again?”

“Uh, I don’t have an exact time. Whenever I wake up!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, I do that, too!” Thousand Creations felt excited, knowing that he shared a common habit with his God.

“Nice. Have a good rest.” Ye Xiu said bye to Thousand Creations.

Thousand Creations logged out from the game. Tang Rou was still fighting a monster. Apart from killing monsters, completing quests, and hoping, Tang Rou naturally consulted Ye Xiu for help on water battles. Ye Xiu didn’t hold back, teaching what he could and helping to devise a training regimen for Tang Rou to use in the water. It couldn’t be said that she had made a huge amount of progress, but she was, at least, taking another step towards her goal to be pro. Besides pro players, normal players wouldn’t specially study how to fight in the water, unless they were really interested.

“How’d it go? How’d it go? How’d yesterday night go?”

Chen Guo had already woken up and appeared in the Internet Cafe. The first thing she did was run over and ask about this. These days, even if she wasn’t there, her heart was pretty much set in the tenth server. She wasn’t a part of the development of Guild Happy, but she felt happy or sad for it as if she were. Last night, if it wasn’t because she didn’t have an account to use, she would have pulled an all-nighter, too.

“Nothing much. We killed a few dozen players. Yeah.” Ye Xiu said.

“A few dozen!” In Chen Guo’s eyes, such a number was frightening.

“A few dozen and you’re not worried? Do you have a red name?” Chen Guo said.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu looked at his screen. Lord Grim’s name was bright red. This was very common after PKing. It was quite troublesome to have a red name. Most NPCs would not trade with a red-named character. When a red-named character died, the experience and gold loss would be greater, and the chance for an equipment to drop would be much higher.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had PKed the most. Tang Rou had also killed four players. But after nothing had happened for a long time, her red name was pretty much gone. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was different though. He didn’t even know how many he had killed and had no idea when his red name would go away.

“You’ve got to be careful!” Chen Guo said. Ignoring all else, Ye Xiu’s account had a Silver weapon on him. If he died and his Silver weapon dropped, that would be extremely bad.

“Yeah, you be careful. Don’t get killed by the monsters.” Ye Xiu stood up and said.

“What are you talking about?”

“I’m going to rest. I’m going to leave my account here. Help me watch it.” Ye Xiu said.

“What! If you’re going to sleep, then log off!” Chen Guo said.

“I can’t do that. The other guilds’ players are still leveling. I have to leave my account there to give them some pressure.” Ye Xiu said.

“Too evil.” Tang Rou had killed off her monster and understood what Ye Xiu meant. As long as Lord Grim’s account was online, it meant that Thousand Waves Lake was unsafe and the guild players had to be careful. Even though it wasn’t actually a threat because Ye Xiu wasn’t controlling it, they would still be looking around them nervously. The pressure from an expert standing there was difficult to bear.

“Don’t. What if they attack?” Chen Guo was too afraid to take up such a task.

“What a joke. Who do you think I am…… They wouldn’t dare to take the initiative to attack me.” Ye Xiu said.

“How could they not dare? They have the numbers advantage!”

“Even if they had dared to before, after last night, they wouldn’t anymore.” Ye Xiu laughed and then added: “Just don’t go out of the water.”

Chen Guo sat nervously at Ye Xiu’s spot and controlled Lord Grim a bit clumsily.

“You don’t need to play on him. You can do your own thing. Just don’t let the monsters scratch me to death. At other times, you can just have him floating.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s too fake! I’ll control him!” Chen Guo took Lord Grim and began fighting monsters in the water. She was very unfamiliar with this character, but unspecialized characters had Launcher skills, too. At the Christmas event, Chen Guo had learned how to change the forms on the Thousand Chance Umbrella. After switching to the Gun form, it felt pretty much the same. The Thousand Chance Umbrella was extremely powerful, so clearing monsters was easy. Chen Guo wasn’t a beginner either. Her water-fighting skill wasn’t good, but the monsters were stupid, so even if she couldn’t move or dodge, it wasn’t a problem.

Chen Guo killed a few monsters and discovered that it was an easy task, so she relaxed and waved her hands to Ye Xiu: “Okay. You can go ahead!”

“Should I also have her stay and float?” Tang Rou asked.

“Sure. If you die, you die. It doesn’t matter.” Chen Guo didn’t turn her head. She was focused on controlling Lord Grim.

“Ha ha ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed as he left. Tang Rou obviously knew that Chen Guo was joking and wouldn’t be angry at her. She messed up Chen Guo’s hair and then left as well. After a few steps, she looked back and saw that Chen Guo was still focused on controlling Lord Grim. Her hair was all messed up, but she didn’t seem to care.

The guild players didn’t know about Ye Xiu’s little trick. Their characters were leveled on shifts. After playing all night, someone else took their place. Of course, they were told the current situation. The most important order was that if they encountered Lord Grim, they were to run as far away from him as possible.

After hearing about the nightmare that night, the people who took the next shift didn’t dare be negligent. The people who went off their shift had looks filled with envy. They felt that Ye Qiu had to rest, so while Lord Grim was offline, everything would be peaceful. How beautiful was that?

All of those experts understood what it meant to be lucky at this moment.

The people who took up the next shift continued to play and stay alert. They also thought that it was about time for Lord Grim to go offline, so they asked about it from time to time.

One hour, still there;

Two hours, still there;

Three hours, still there;

The new players were also constantly rotating their cameras in circles to be on the lookout. Their heads were going dizzy and their hands had turned sore, but Lord Grim was still there.

“Has anyone seen where he is?” They continued to ask each other.

“I haven’t!”

“If you see him, you’re probably already dead!” another said.

“Yeah, not seeing him is a good thing……. If you see him, how could he not see you?”

“That’s not necessarily true, no?”

“You can go check then. Go look around and maybe you’ll find him.”

“Uh, nevermind!”

That morning, even though they didn’t bump into Lord Grim, Lord Grim was still the main topic of every guild.

The players who had taken up the shift were all waiting impatiently. Even when they changed shifts again, Lord Grim was still online. After resting, the guild leaders began working again and also froze when they heard this news.

After exchanging information, they knew that no one had been attacked, but they couldn’t tell if it was because of luck or because of something else.

“Maybe he’s already gone to sleep and his character is just floating there.”

“Could it be a bluff to give us pressure?”

“How despicable!!!”

“And it’s about time that he’ll be getting up, too……”

Everyone fell silent.

“F*ck ….. He really is up …….” Guild 301 sent a sad face, “One of our players just got killed by him.”

“There’s nothing that we can do…… We can’t know whether he’s actually playing or just sitting there.”

“Not moving might just be a trap to lure us in.”

“Oh great Gods, help us subdue these devils!!” The guilds all cried.

Chapter 385 – Taking Advantage of the Situation

They might not have suffered any losses, but they had been in a high-pressure situation.

Each of the top guilds held a meeting with their tenth server elites, telling them not to be afraid of the dangers. They were to “level stubbornly”, bearing the heavy pressure, and resist Lord Grim’s terrorist attacks. They were to struggle until the very end.

The reaction from the meeting was average. These guild leaders ignored exhaustion and nervousness from this type of pressure. They were more focused on the results. They could only say “persist, persist and persist” towards the difficulties met during the process.

If this wasn’t a guild backed by a Club, no one would be listening. Gaming was for relaxing and having fun. Who would struggle so hard for a game? But once it involved the Clubs, the game was no longer just a game. It was a job and a reason to struggle for. Even though the encouragement from the guild leaders didn’t do much, it made clear their attitude towards this. The elites could only follow the orders and brace themselves.

At Cafe Happy, Ye Xiu switched with Chen Guo after getting up. That morning, Chen Guo hadn’t killed anyone, but she had gained quite a bit of experience for him. As soon as Ye Xiu switched places with her, he immediately began his operation. He killed monsters while looking around, and then quickly found a Guild 301 player, who was naturally eliminated.

Tang Rou had also gotten up around the same time as Ye Xiu. She didn’t go directly to the game though. Instead, she went to change shifts at the front desk. Ye Xiu saw this and was startled. These past few days, he had been too invested in the development of the guild. He kept on feeling that something wasn’t right. When he saw Tang Rou take a shift, he suddenly remembered: he hadn’t taken up a shift ever since the All-Star Weekend!

Ye Xiu began to sweat madly. He glanced at Chen Guo. There was no way that Chen Guo didn’t know that he hadn’t worked these past few days, yet she hadn’t said anything about it.

“I say……” Ye Xiu opened his mouth to speak.

“Hm?” Chen Guo turned her head.

“Who took up the night shift these past few days?” Ye Xiu tried to speak vaguely about the topic, without getting to the point.

“You don’t need to worry.” Chen Guo was much more direct.

“Then I……. this……”

“Developing the guild and creating the team is your work!” Chen Guo made a fist.

“……”

“What? How come you don’t seem happy about it?” Chen Guo narrowed her eyes at Ye Xiu, who looked like he wanted to say something.

“Nothing. I just thought that you’ve made quite the profit.” Ye Xiu said.

“Me? What profit?” Chen Guo was puzzled.

“The pay for being a cafe manager during the night shift is very reasonable. But now you want me to do this for that pay. That’s not how much I’m worth!” Ye Xiu said.

“Bullsh*t. You’re taking advantage of me!!!” After knowing Ye Xiu’s identity, Chen Guo’s tolerance for Ye Xiu had clearly gone up. A lot of things had become nicer to look at. She hadn’t gotten angry for quite a while.

“I couldn’t help but mention it.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo stared blankly for a bit. Her mind churned and she realized that Ye Xiu wasn’t wrong. He was an expert at his speciality. As a top-tier God in Glory, he only had a normal status as a cafe manager. But if you wanted him to play Glory, he was much more valuable and his worth would naturally be very different.

“Then what do you want?” Chen Guo was a bit uneasy. If she had to pay Ye Xiu according to his pro status, then she would have some trouble taking the loss.

“Nothing. I was just saying.” Ye Xiu said.

“Do you want a pay raise?” Chen Guo asked unconfidently. Ye Xiu currently had the pay for a cafe manager. Even if his pay was ten times that amount, it wouldn’t be enough for his status as a pro God!

“No need, no need. Just food and shelter is enough.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Chen Guo saw Ye Xiu go back to his game. She didn’t know what to say. She turned her head and played the game for a bit, when she suddenly realized something. He had been the one to start the conversation. From his tone of voice, it seemed like he had felt bad about not working these past few days. Why did she feel like she had been in the wrong and that she was taking advantage of him?

“Ah, another one!”

Just when Chen Guo was about to say something, Ye Xiu interrupted her. She hastily went up to look at Ye Xiu’s screen. Lord Grim was bravely charging towards a figure out in the distance. But as the distance shrunk and he saw the tag on top of the character’s head, Ye Xiu was disappointed: “He’s not one…..”

There were 12 guilds in Thousand Waves Lake. Apart from Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter, there were 94 others. Not all of these were Ye Xiu’s targets, because some of them hadn’t participated in the conflict. There was also Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition, who had paid for protection, so Ye Xiu wouldn’t touch them. The player in front of him wasn’t a target.

“You won’t find many if you search like this!” Chen Guo said.

“That’s just the way it is.” Ye Xiu said as he clicked on Blue River’s name on his friends list: “What’s the situation!!”

“What situation!!!” Blue River added three exclamation marks to express his emotions.

“Did you find the whereabouts of any targets?” Ye Xiu said.

“What targets!!!”

‘You know.”

“……”

“This is to your benefit, too. What are you hesitating for?” Ye Xiu messaged.

Blue River was gloomy. He was right! Telling him their whereabouts would definitely benefit their guild. But why did he always have the feeling that he had to resist?

“Just look at Tyrannical Ambition! They’re so communicative!”

Ye Xiu said, while controlling Lord Grim.

He hadn’t asked just Blue River. He had also asked Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night. Cold Night was much more cooperative than Blue River and called out to all of the elites in Thousand Waves Lake. When he received Ye Xiu’s message, he first asked something that he was curious about: “God, were you not on in the morning? We had at least three reports in the morning! What a pity.”

“Oh, then what about now?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Only one.”

“Tell me. I’ll go.” Ye Xiu replied.

Cold Night happily sent Ye Xiu a name and his coordinates. Ye Xiu headed towards there, while encouraging Blue River. Apart from these two guilds, there were three other guilds. However, these three guilds were in a neutral position. They couldn’t gain anything from this sort of conflict, so they didn’t join in. Just like how they wouldn’t help the guilds pressure Lord Grim, they wouldn’t help Lord Grim mess with the other guilds, so Ye Xiu didn’t look for them.

Taking Cold Night’s report, he quickly found and eliminated the target. Ye Xiu took out a notepad and wrote something down. Chen Guo looked and saw a list of characters from seven guilds. Every time a character was killed, Ye Xiu would add an “X” symbol to it. How tragic for Misty Castle! Their characters had a bunch of marks next to them.

“Are Misty Castle’s player still here?” Chen Guo couldn’t help but ask. They had been killed to such an extent.

“I haven’t encountered any.” Ye Xiu said and opened up his friends list again: “Let me ask around.”

“Are you still leveling at Thousand Waves Lake?” Ye Xiu messaged Hazy Mist.

Hazy Mist’s cheeks were streaked with tears. That had to be a type of arrogance! He implied that they were helpless and that they could only hide.

“What do you plan on doing!” Hazy Mist’s heart was weeping, but his reply sounded tough.

“Nothing, really. My friend just wants to know.” Ye Xiu said and turned to look at Chen Guo. Chen Guo was already completely speechless, looking at this exchange.

“We won’t agree to your terms.” Hazy Mist carried out his overall guild leader’s wishes.

“What a coincidence. I won’t either.” Ye Xiu replied.

Hazy Mist wept even harder. What do you mean, ‘you won’t either’! Our players are suffering and you’re probably just thinking how fun it is!

“Be careful; don’t let me bump into you!” Ye Xiu sent another message to threaten Hazy Mist. Hazy Mist jumped up in fright and closed his messages to check his surroundings. He spun in a circle three times before confirming that he wasn’t nearby.

“When will this end…….” Hazy Mist looked at his experience and continued to kill monsters. Even in normal circumstances, where there was no one terrorizing them while they were leveling, it would still be a few more days before they would leave Thousand Waves Lake!

On Tyrannical Ambition’s side, even though they were very enthusiastic in giving reports to Ye Xiu, they didn’t consider Ye Xiu as an ally. Ignoring everything else, their identity as a branch of Tyranny made them eternal enemies.

“Has there been any reaction from Excellent Dynasty?” Jiang You hadn’t forgotten his original thoughts.

“It doesn’t seem like it.” Cold Night said.

“Could those idiots not have understood that no one can deal with Ye Qiu?” Jiang You mumbled.

In the blink of an eye, the daytime went by and day gradually turned into night. More and more players began coming online, but Thousand Waves Lake was the same. The scenic lake was as beautiful as before. But to the majority of the players there, the lake was full of danger.

That afternoon, the players leveling at Thousand Waves Lake had died eleven times. The seven guilds repeatedly confirmed the reports in order to understand the situation.

If this record had been done entirely by chance, then either their opponent’s luck was too amazing or there was something else going on.

“Could there be someone selling us out?” They weren’t idiots. The guilds were only working for their mutual interest, so it was easy for them to think of something like this. This was why, even though they were opponents, they still made an alliance. Making an alliance at least guaranteed that no one would make things worse.

But some of the guilds were outside of their Alliance and those guilds were the first ones to be suspicious about. They could suspect them, but they had no proof. And even if they had proof, so what? They couldn’t start a guild war because of this, could they? There hadn’t been any large guild wars between the top guilds for a long time. This was because of the other guilds. When two guilds fought, the ones to benefit from the war wouldn’t be them. This reasoning was something every guild leader understood after so many years of competing with each other.

“We can bear such a loss. But those conniving guilds are too terrible.” Herb Garden’s Arisaema said hatefully.

Chapter 386 – Exploit

Which guild was giving away information behind their backs? The amount of suspicion towards other guilds could be divided into different levels. For example, the relatively weaker guilds who wanted to avoid having any part in the conflict were less suspicious. Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition had been involved with everyone else from the start, but then cut off communications with them. They were, without a doubt, the most suspicious.

“We can’t let them go!” a guild leader expressed.

“Yeah! If they want to give into the terms, then that’s fine. But if they’re going to be like the legs of a dog after giving into the terms, we can’t allow that!”

“We can’t allow that +1”

“We can’t allow that +2!”

“We can’t allow that +10086!”

The overall guild leaders from seven of the top guilds were furious. The tenth server guild leaders looked calmer though. As they quietly watched the discussion between these top guilds on how to deal with Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition, they suddenly felt that they needed to vent their anger. There was nothing they could against Ye Qiu, but Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition could become their punching bags!

“What? You died?” Blue River turned indignant when he received Thundering Light’s report. After creating a guild, he was beginning to scheme and play dirty tricks! Thinking of this, Blue River clicked on Lord Grim’s name and sent an angry face at him. Afterwards, he inquired: “What’s going on?”

“Hm?”

“Why’d you kill my player!” Blue River said righteously.

“Did you make a mistake?”

“Shameless!!” Blue River didn’t think that the other side would pretend that nothing had happened. At this moment, he received a new message. It was from Thundering Light: he hadn’t been killed by Lord Grim, but one of Herb Garden’s players.

“Herb Garden…..” Blue River was in a daze.

“Did another guild do it?” Ye Xiu’s message floated in at just the right time.

“How did you know?”

“You guys sold them out. How could they not take revenge?” Ye Xiu asked in return.

Blue River nearly choked. He had been the one urging him to sell the others out! Right now he was talking as if he had nothing to do with it. After being angry for a bit, Blue River suddenly realized: “Did you know that this would happen?”

“Who wouldn’t have known?” Ye Xiu replied.

“You purposefully asked us to give you reports in order to get us to fight like this!” Blue River reasoned.

“You’re thinking too much. The reports benefited both parties, so it was something that should be done.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’ve gotten a lot of benefits, but we’ve run into trouble!” Blue River said.

“It’s troublesome for me, too!” Ye Xiu said.

“What trouble?”

“My……. my red name still hasn’t gone away……” Ye Xiu’s reply looked as if he were having trouble saying it, making Blue River certain that this “trouble” was something that the other side had tried very hard in order to come up with something..

“Too evil!” Blue River mumbled.

“How many of your guild members have died?” Ye Xiu began to discuss matters properly.

“One isn’t enough?”

“Whether that’s enough doesn’t depend on me to decide!”

Blue River coughed up blood.

“After taking your materials, I should help you guys do some stuff. If you get attacked again, you can bring them over to me.” Ye Xiu continued.

Only at this moment did Blue River understand. He had been too shallow in his thinking. After creating a conflict, this could still be done! Blue Brook Guild’s players became his fish bait. What could Blue Brook Guild do about it though? If they did nothing, they wouldn’t be able to handle the guild alliance’s venting. If they did as they were told, they would establish much hate from the other guilds. That would be bad, too!

Moreover, the overall guild leaders were currently the ones managing the guild on the tenth server now. It was possible that the fight here could carry over to the Heavenly Domain. Although the top guilds had always been fighting nonstop, fighting as the few against the many had never been done before. Everyone was always careful and never attracted the enmity of two guilds simultaneously. But now, they would be provoking seven guilds at the same time! That sort of strength was something no guild could defend against by themselves.

“What do we do?” This was a matter of great concern. Blue River didn’t want to make a hasty decision either, so he went to look for his guild leader, Changing Spring. In addition, he felt like this matter was complicated as well. He didn’t think that he would be able to explain the situation clearly enough through brief messages like how Changing Spring talked in chat, so he went to speak to Changing Spring through voice.

The same situation had fallen onto Tyrannical Ambition. After knowing that one of their elite players had died, but wasn’t killed by Lord Grim, Cold Night quickly realized the gravity of the situation as well.

Of course, he wouldn’t be like Blue River and ask Lord Grim. Instead, he directly went to contact Jiang You.

“Asking us to give him reports was a trap……” Cold Night grieved, “It was my bad. I was too hasty to gain an advantage and hadn’t expected such an obvious development to happen.”

“No……” After hearing Cold Night’s report and self-criticism, Jiang You paused for a long while, before saying this single word.

Cold Night didn’t understand what he meant by “No”, so he waited for Jiang You to continue.

“As soon as we accepted the terms, while others didn’t, we fell into his trap.” Jiang You said.

“He really does deserve to be called Glory’s most experienced God….. and encyclopedia? Not only is he skilled in the pro scene, even for guild battles in game, he also taught us a good lesson.”

“He exploited the biggest weakness between our guilds. In the end, we’re all competitors. The only reason we work together is for our mutual interests. We don’t have any friends……”

“Ever since we made different choices, we were destined to suspect each other. Asking us to give him reports is only one way. Even if he didn’t use this, he would have other ways to sow doubt between the guilds. This.. is something we can’t do anything about. The way we work determined our nature. This can’t be changed.” Jiang You sent. No one interrupted. They all saw how helpless they were in this situation.

“Then what do we do now?” Cold Night asked.

“Things are already like this. Those other guilds won’t stop either. We can’t explain ourselves either, unless we work together with them to fight Lord Grim.” Jiang You said.

“This…….” Cold Night held back a choke. They had already paid the materials in order to ensure that they could safely level. Lord Grim didn’t make trouble for them, but the other guilds did. If they turned around to fight Lord Grim, Lord Grim obviously wouldn’t not fight back because they had given him materials. Everything would be back to how it was originally. The guilds who accepted the terms would have wasted their materials. The guilds who hadn’t accepted the terms had suffered losses from deaths and pressure.

Tyrannical Ambition had the same style as their team Tyranny. Backing down wasn’t their nature. When they chose to agree to Lord Grim’s terms, that decision had already been difficult to bear. Plus, they had plans on what to do next. But now, their Tyrannical Ambition was being forced to reach terms with the guild alliance. It was hard to say if they had any plans afterwards either. This made Cold Night feel uncomfortable as if he had swallowed a house fly. He believed that his guild leader Jiang You was feeling the same way.

“Since things are like this, it might be better to be more thorough.” Jiang You suddenly said.

“Oh?”

“We’ll ally with Ye Qiu!” Jiang You said.

“That….. That’s not good, right?” Cold Night hastily said, “What about the Heavenly Domain and the other servers?”

If it was just the tenth server, allying with Ye Qiu to bully the other guilds would be a very easy decision. But the problem was, the tenth server was only a part of the top guilds’ influence. Ye Qiu was currently a huge problem here, but he wouldn’t affect any other servers. A move here could affect everywhere else and the consequences would be serious. In the Heavenly Domain and the other servers, if these guilds allied together and attacked, Tyrannical Ambition’s days would become very difficult.

“We’ll just have to try and see what happens.” Jiang You said.

“Don’t be hasty, guild leader!” Cold Night advised. He thought that Jiang You was unable to hold back his anger and was ready to let it out.

In the end, Jiang You sent a smiley face: “It seems like you still don’t understand.”

“What?” Cold Night was surprised.

“These chain of events were probably within Ye Qiu’s calculations.” Jiang You said.

Cold Night stared blankly. His mind was rapidly turning.

“The balance between the guilds has continued for many years. And with everyone’s foundations, pulling up a guild from their roots isn’t possible. This is why guilds avoid getting into any large-scale conflicts. Kill one thousand enemies, lose eight hundred soldiers. If such a conflict happens, it might even be hard to say what advantages one gets from winning. Instead of a trade-off, it would be better if everyone developed happily together. It really would be difficult to deal with if the seven guilds allied together, but they wouldn’t gain much either. The sandpiper and clam war together, while the fisher catches them both. Only an idiot would make such a move. Do you think the guild leaders are idiots?” Jiang You said.

‘This….. But if there’s a chance…..” Cold Night was still worried.

“There’s no chance. Any guild who would make such a move would have already died.” Jiang You was extremely confident.

“Then you’re saying?”

“Work together with Ye Qiu. If you find a target, report it to him. If they chase after you, look for him! Have our players stay together. Whether they dare to gather together in one area depends on how brave they are.” Jiang You said.

“Okay…… I understand.” Now that he understood the general direction, Cold Night could figure out the details.

“First, borrow Ye QIu’s help to beat down these guys. Let them get a taste of hell. At the same time, this will help Ye Qiu’s momentum. I don’t believe that Excellent Era would kick out Ye Qiu and then quietly watch as he charges back into the pro scene. You want to be the fisher, while the sandpiper and clams fight? We’ll use this chance to kill two golden eagles with one arrow. Ye Qiu, you’re a good card to play, too!”

Chapter 387 – Still Running!

Jiang You made a clear analysis on the situation. With a definite plan in mind, he decided to make a temporary alliance with Ye Qiu and start a fight with their previous allies. As for Blue Brook Guild? Changing Spring had many years of experience as well. It wasn’t hard to predict the direction events would play out towards. His line of thinking was the same as Jiang You’s and he made a similar decision.

The other server guild leaders from these two guilds were all worried about the impact the decision would have overall. The two overall guild leaders both saw that a violent conflict nowadays wouldn’t be a good idea, especially with a God like Ye Qiu attempting to make his comeback. How big such a conflict would turn out to be could be seen by the sorry figures of these tenth server guilds.

Even though the top guilds had a much stronger foundation in the Heavenly Domain than the tenth server, Ye Qiu would also have a popularity that he didn’t have in the tenth server. They had to take precautions in every area against this opponent. How could they give him any chances to take advantage of them?

Only after weighing the pros and cons were the two overall guild leaders able to be at ease and bravely order their tenth server elites to ally with Ye Qiu.

“Understood.” After everyone heard the order, they immediately began to carry them out. They stopped leveling in one specific area like before and began to wander around the entire leveling area. The difference between the two guilds was that Tyrannical Ambition moved in one large group, while Blue Brook Guild didn’t require this, so they were free to do as they pleased. Those who wanted to form parties could form a party and level together. Those who wanted to level on their own like Blue River continued to guard a single area.

Blue River didn’t wander around.

He had been deeply in admiration towards Changing Spring’s analysis, but he didn’t express it. Just listening to these calculations and plans made him feel tired, let alone thinking carefully about them. When he had played around in Guild Happy for a few days and became like a babysitter taking care of the new players, he didn’t have to think so much about deceiving each other. It was much more fun.

“Sigh……” Blue River didn’t know why he sighed and continued to mechanically clear away monsters.

He didn’t know how the others were doing. He had been killing monsters for a while, but he hadn’t received any news. There probably wasn’t anything going on. If not, whether if someone had been killed or found a target, he would be the one to speak with Lord Grim about it.

How were things going to turn out? Blue River strolled around for a bit and once again thought of this. He was beginning to get distracted and was slowing down in his killing. Suddenly, he heard sounds of water being stirred violently. Even though he didn’t have much experience in water battles, he could still tell that this sound wasn’t normal. The experienced Blue River instantly took up his guard. He had his character turn his body over in the water and then watched as a bullet shot by him. Only one of the bullets had been dodged, the numerous other ones following connected with him. In the water, very few players were able to nimbly move around the water and dodge attacks.

The blood that sprayed out from the bullets quickly faded away. Blue River had already turned his character around to see a Sharpshooter standing there, pointing his gun at him.

“Herb Garden’s player.” Blue River could tell just from the player’s name and couldn’t help but laugh bitterly. He didn’t want to find anyone, but they went to look for him and it didn’t seem like he’d be let go.

However, if they were intending to kill him, they wouldn’t send only one player. These elites, whether they were on land or in the water, their skill levels were very even. In addition, Blue River was considered to be one of the Five Great Experts of Blue Brook Guild. His skill level was top notch amongst normal players.The opponent wouldn’t be so confident as to think that a single player could bring him down with certainty, just because he had made the first move. This was even more so for a old rival like Herb Garden.

Blue River calmly thought and didn’t hurry to attack the Sharpshooter. While moving, he turned his character’s camera and looked all around himself. Sure enough, the other side had four players. One of them was even their tenth server’s guild leader, Plantago Seed. The four had taken advantage of the fact that Blue River was distracted and had already closed in. The reason the Sharpshooter had fired at him was because they believed that Blue River had nowhere to run.

A message popped up. Blue River looked and saw that Plantago Seed had sent him a smiley face. Blue River was too lazy to talk with him. He turned his character and immediately charged towards Plantago Seed.

Plantago Seed didn’t panic. He didn’t go forward to welcome the fight. Instead, he slowly retreated and watched as the other three players closed in.

Blue River also paid attention to his left and right. He didn’t have the confidence in defeating Plantago Seed in just a few hits. The other three weren’t far either. The Sharpshooter had been attacking the entire time. If Plantago Seed stalled him for just a bit, they would be able to surround him and his death would be certain. Plantago Seed understood this, too. Retreating was just a way to stall for time. He wasn’t planning on staying away from Blue River the entire time. Seeing that his three allies were close, he stopped his retreat and waved the broom in his hands, whipping up a spray of water.

Blue River had been charging bravely for awhile. But when he got close enough to attack, he suddenly changed directions and his character dove down into the water.

Plantago Seed saw this and immediately threw down a Lava Flask. When the Lava Flask was used on land, it would create a sea of fire wherever the flask broke. In the water, it had a different effect. The lava flowing out from the flask couldn’t ignite the water, but it could make the water bubble. The waves spread the lava out, making it float all over the place, making the waters look like a polluted garbage dump. If a character touched the flameless lava, they would still take damage.

Blue River understood this. But with his skill, not touching the lava wasn’t easy for him. Blue River didn’t want this to waste his time though, so he took the damage and directly rushed out from the lava.

Plantago Seed had already swam over after throwing the Lava Flask. His own skill wouldn’t harm him. Seeing Blue River take the damage and rush out from the lava, he waved his arms and tossed out a Shadow Cloak, in order to try and bind Blue River.

But Blue River wasn’t blindly running. He noticed Plantago Seed’s movements and as he came out of the lava, he used a skill.

Plantago Seed had only just thrown out his mantle, when he saw a blade light hit the mantle. It was already too late to dodge and the Sword Draw connected with his body, sending him tumbling into the water.

Plantago Seed was sad. He hadn’t seen the attack at all…… Why? Because the bubbling from his lava had blocked his line of sight.

With just this short delay, Blue River was able to get out of the lava area. He had a few lava bits on him, but it didn’t affect his movement speed.

“Chase!” Plantago Seed called out to his team and the four chased after him.

“There’s no escape.” Plantago Seed messaged Blue River as his character lifted his head and rose from the water. He was a Witch, so he could use his broom to move even faster than a Launcher using Aerial Fire. He was confident that he could stop Blue River.

Blue River ignored Plantago Seed. Seeing him rush over on the surface of the water, he understood his intent and immediately changed directions again.

Plantago Seed was on top of the water, so he couldn’t see far underwater. He could only chase according to the direction of the other three players. When Blue River changed directions, the three notified Plantago Seed. But their message had been a bit too slow and Plantago Seed didn’t know how far away he had been thrown off by. He could only wait for Blue River to come back up to the surface in order to know.

“It’s about time. You’re still not going to go up to breathe?” Plantago Seed casually messaged Blue River. In his eyes, Blue River’s demise was just a matter of time.

“I’m coming.” This time, Blue River unexpectedly replied. Just as the message came out, half a body had come out from the water. If that wasn’t Blue River, who else could it be?

Plantago Seed saw this and immediately rushed forward on his broom. As soon as Blue River came up, he went to see where Plantago Seed was. He swam madly, while paying attention to where Plantago Seed was.

“Still running!” Plantago Seed shouted. As he flew on his broom, he threw a Magic Missile to try and stop him.

Blue River ignored the damage though and continued to swim madly. Herb Garden’s three players had already came up to the surface of the water as well. They didn’t have a movement speed advantage over Blue River though. After chasing underwater for so long, the distance between them was the same. When the Sharpshooter came up, he also used an Aerial Gun technique. It couldn’t compare to an Aerial Cannon, but it was enough to move faster than a swimming player.

“Still running!”

“Still running!”

“Still running!”

Plantago Seed yelled every time he threw a Magic MIssile. He was having quite some fun chasing. Tiny Herb and Blue Rain were archrivals, just like Excellent Era and Tyranny. The guilds in-game naturally held the same view. Blue River was one of Plantago Seed’s rivals, too. At this moment, chasing him around felt extremely good.

Magic Missile might only be a low-level skill, but several strikes of it still whittled down quite a chunk of Blue River’s health. Plantago Seed quickly caught up with his movement speed advantage. He was even feeling a bit reluctant. He felt like slowly killing Blue River with Magic Missile was very fun. Was there any need to stop Blue River?

He didn’t hesitate because of this. It was only an afterthought when he caught up to Blue River. At the same time, he tossed a Shadow Cloak, ready to bind Blue River. But Blue River flipped his body and headed into the water, just barely dodging the Shadow Cloak.

“What a time-waster.” Plantago Seed helplessly said, “You guys continue watching him.”

“Yes,” the three replied, and then they dove into the water.

“I say, this is pretty interesting. Where can you run to?” Plantago Seed messaged Blue River.

“It’s about time.” Blue River replied.

“What?” Plantago Seed stared blankly for a bit.

A message flashed. Plantago Seed opened it and saw the three type simultaneously: “LORD GRIM!!!!”

Chapter 388 – To Move a Stone and Stub One’s Foot

“Blue River, how despicable!!” Plantago Seed suddenly came to a realization. Blue River had been blindly wandering around, waiting for help. And the help he got was way too excessive. It was so excessive that Plantago Seed was so powerless to do anything that all he could do was roar angrily on top of the lake. Soon afterwards, his character could no longer be controlled. A spout of water lifted his body up as Plantago Seed was launched into the air. He turned his camera to look and the same situation that had befallen his three allies as well.

How had Lord Grim blasted all of four of them into the sky at the same time? Plantago Seed couldn’t imagine how. The instant he looked down, the fifth player shot out of the water. On top of his head was the hateful ID “Lord Grim”.

Plantago Seed only had two thoughts on his mind.

One, how much he despised Blue River.

And two, how he was going to escape.

There’s got to be a chance…… Plantago Seed shuddered. Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, that much was true… But they had four players. If they all scattered and ran, at least three of them should be able to escape, right? Who was going to be the first target though?

Plantago Seed was trying to guess, when suddenly he saw that Lord Grim had decided to swim towards his direction. He immediately wanted to cry, but then again, there really wasn’t any need to guess. As the guild leader, who wouldn’t go after him? Was there any need to think about who else the opponent would attack?

Seeing that it had already been decided, Plantago Seed could only take responsibility as the guild leader and shout: “Hurry up and run!”

“Run where?” someone responded to him. This voice was different, but the tone was very familiar. Plantago Seed heard it and wanted to rip his hair out in anger. The voice was Blue River’s, but the tone was the same as when he had previously been chasing after Blue River and throwing Magic Missiles.

“Blue River, you have no future! I despise you! If you’ve got the guts, 1v1 me!” Plantago Seed shouted.

Blue River wasn’t having an easy time either. Originally, he hadn’t wanted to help God and gather intelligence for him, but the enemies had started to come look for him. First, the opponents were from Herb Garden, and Blue River didn’t like them. Second, God had come asking him for intelligence at that time, so Blue River gave him a report because it was convenient for him. As a result, God provided him a direction to go towards. Blue River had swum madly in that direction and received his welcoming. In an instant, the situation turned around, but Plantago Seed’s denouncement made Blue River speechless.

In the end, Ye Xiu replied: “1v1? You think this is a competitive match? In this game, it’s the many who bully the few. And you call yourself a guild leader. Your comprehension skills are too poor.”

After saying this, Lord Grim received the falling Plantago Seed with an attack. The scene afterwards would make those who saw it terrified.

“F*ck your mother! You can keep me in the air endlessly from the water?” Plantago Seed cried. He didn’t even get the chance to fall into the water.

“Don’t be too fascinated by me! Pay attention to the player that is in your hands! I’m talking to you, Thousand Creations!” Ye Xiu shouted.

“Ah? Oh!” someone replied from a different direction. Thousand Creations had been distracted and the opponent that he had been fighting all along had slipped away. He hastily chased after him.

Plantago Seed suddenly realized that Lord Grim wasn’t the only opponent there. Soft Mist, Thousand Creations, and Blue River were there, too. Those three each took care of one of his three brothers.

Plantago Seed was completely speechless. Even a God like Ye Qiu was playing with others. What could he say?

Finally, Plantago Seed dropped into the water. He had run out of health and with a heart unwilling to accept it, he revived back at the city.

“How’s it going? Can you guys hold on?” Ye Xiu turned to ask the other three.

“It’s no good. Hurry and help me.” The person to speak was a female voice, which naturally meant that it was from Soft Mist. Those who were familiar with her would be very surprised, because how could Tang Rou say something like that? In truth, it was because the person controlling Soft Mist wasn’t Tang Rou, but Chen Guo. Tang Rou was currently working at the cash register at the front desk. It was currently during peak hours, so she didn’t have time to play the game. As a result, Chen Guo took the chance to play on her account.

Chen Guo respected Ye Qiu very much, so she liked the Battle Mage class. She had even leveled up a low-level account. But in truth, she had never played it seriously, so she wasn’t familiar with the class. Plus, the opponent in front of her was an elite from the top guilds. They were more skilled than her, so fighting against one was extremely difficult for her. If she continued to fight, she would be the one to die.

Luckily, Ye Xiu was lightning fast. It had taken him less than a minute to take down Plantago Seed, and this Herb Garden elite wasn’t good enough to beat the experienced Chen Guo in less than a minute. Ye Xiu rushed over to help and the situation immediately became as simple as one plus one equals two. Chen Guo also took the chance to take revenge. However, because she was in the water and because she was unfamiliar with the class, many of her skills hit Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Fortunately, attacks from players in the same party didn’t do damage. Otherwise, Lord Grim would probably have taken the same amount of damage as their opponent.

With a second one dead, next were the other two sides. Blue River was fighting steadily and was revolving around his opponent. For now, the battle was even. On the other side, Thousand Creations was currently chasing his opponent because he had been distracted previously. He was relying on his Battle Mage’s movement speed buff from the Chasers in order to gradually close the distance.

Ye Xiu saw this and immediately controlled his Lord Grim to rush over to Thousand Creations’ side, while telling Chen Guo: “You go help Blue River.”

“Okay.” Chen Guo listened and swam over. She raised her arms and used a Dragon Tooth. But the waves crashed against her and her character moved over to the side. The Dragon Tooth, which was supposed to be towards the Herb Garden player, slipped and stabbed towards Blue River. Luckily, Blue River had moved a bit, too. The Dragon Tooth didn’t connect and swiped past him.

“Sister, which side are you on!!” Blue River cried out in surprise.

“Sorry. It was an accident.” Chen Guo apologized in shame.

“Hurry up and add me to the party. Add me!” Blue River shouted. Lord Grim and the others were in the same party, but Blue River wasn’t. He would still take damage from them. If the Dragon Tooth had connected, it’d be the same as if an enemy had injured him.

“Add him to the party.” Chen Guo was afraid that Ye Xiu wouldn’t hear her, so she turned her head to give Ye Xiu a shout. Ye Xiu was currently chasing after his target and trying to cut him off. He sent a party invite to Blue River, which Blue River immediately accepted.

Chen Guo controlled Soft Mist and kept a distance away from Blue River. She was familiar with Ye Xiu, so it didn’t matter. But in front of a stranger, Chen Guo couldn’t lose too much face. Her following attacks were much more careful.

Blue River’s skill had originally been above his opponent’s. Now, with a bit of help, his superiority was clear and he quickly seized the advantage. The opponent didn’t want to fight either. He knew that no matter hard he fought, once Lord Grim came around, he was a dead man, which was why he had been trying to escape the entire time. However, Blue River was an experienced player and didn’t let him get a chance to run. Finally, after getting Chen Guo’s help, the elite wasn’t even able to last until Lord Grim got there and died under Blue River’s sword.

“Blue River, you’re shameless!” This brother didn’t forget to pass on their guild leader’s spirit when he died.

Being told like that in front of a lady was quite embarrassing for Blue River. Chen Guo didn’t care though. Seeing that the opponent had been taken care of, she immediately looked towards Ye Xiu’s and Thousand Creation’s direction: “How’s it going over there?”

“You think there’s any suspense?” Blue River wasn’t worried at all.

“Stupid! Why am I watching like this.” Chen Guo’s words made Blue River somewhat confused. Chen Guo turned her head to look at Ye Xiu’s screen.

Ye Xiu had just caught up. And just like what Blue River had said, there wasn’t any suspense. A bunch of attacks came out. In Chen Guo’s eyes, Thousand Creations’ help only ruined the beauty.

“You guys are done over there?” Ye Xiu easily cleaned up the remaining player and asked Chen Guo.

“Done.” Chen Guo put her thumbs up.

Ye Xiu nodded his head and messaged Blue River: “Not bad, not bad. Pulling four players at once. You’re quite a good taunter!”

“……” Blue River had no words to say.

“Keep up the good work!” Ye Xiu said.

“……” Still no words.

“Don’t be too scared. There are a lot of options in the water. Most players aren’t good in the water either, so as long as you can stay alive for awhile, I’ll be able to rush over.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m going to level……” Blue River didn’t want to say anything.

“Go ahead, go ahead. If anything comes up, call me!” Ye Xiu replied.

Blue River’s misdeeds had naturally been exposed by Plantago Seed. The seven top guilds condemned Blue River, but as time went on, they discovered that Blue River wasn’t the only one to do this. Every player from Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition did this.

These two guilds had entered the struggle again. However, this time, they were standing on Lord Grim’s side and were bullying the other guilds. This made these seven top guilds even angrier, but there was nothing they could do. Killing a player in the water wasn’t easy for them. Now, the players from these two guilds could call on Lord Grim for help if they ever got targeted.

For such a God like Ye Qiu, he wasn’t acting proper in any way. He was like a summoned creature and would arrive whenever he was called upon. The players from those two guilds were no longer his targets, but his bait.

The most shameless ones were the bait, who were acting extremely arrogant. They went around Thousand Waves Lake showing off. Any fish they discovered would be chased after. And then, Lord Grim would quickly be summoned over and the fish would be caught.

The players from the seven top guilds cried.

They had originally wanted to carefully hide from Guild Happy’s few players. But the number of players they had to hide from now were too many. Attacking the players from those two guilds were like moving a rock to stub their own toe!

“Did it make a difference?” A guild leader was still comforting himself: “Those two guilds had already chosen to stand on that side. Even if we didn’t chase after them, they would have helped Lord Grim look for us. Whether or not we went to kill them didn’t matter, no?”

“It didn’t make a difference, but the problem is that we can’t compare to Ye Qiu in the water. Not only did we not make a comeback, we suffered even more losses. How many of our players have been killed today?”

Everyone went silent. They didn’t have the heart to count how many of their players had died. On the other hand, Ye Xiu had taken note of every kill in his notebook.

Chapter 389 – Three Choices

The top seven guilds persisted under the increased pressure. They felt that Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition had been telling Lord Grim about their whereabouts since long ago, so the general situation hadn’t changed much from how it was before. It had been a mistake on their part to have their players take the initiative to look for trouble though. In the end, the problem laid in their weakness in the water. They had no way of killing their targets fast enough, thus giving their targets enough time to stall till Lord Grim arrived.

The guild leaders of these top seven guilds were all very flexible people. Once they saw that their actions weren’t working, they despised Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition, then they decisively changed their plans. They would then continue with their previous hiding plan and would not take the initiative to attack.

Going back and forth had only caused more trouble for them. Ye Xiu’s side was completely unconcerned. They continued to level while still wandering around and reporting their situations. Any single enemy that they met would be killed. A bit later into the night, Su Mucheng came online. With another overwhelmingly powerful killer, the pressure only increased for these top seven guilds.

Time passed. Ye Xiu’s group was as happy as ever. Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition were also in high spirits. Against other guilds backed by Clubs, this type of pressure they exerted, which made their opponents run away on sight of them without any intentions of fighting, was truly something that they hadn’t felt in a long long time. They deeply felt, through experience, how comfortable it was to cool in the shade under a large tree.

Midnight arrived and finally, it came time for the dungeons to refresh. The players from those top seven guilds had been tense the entire day. Dungeon running was usually the time where they had to concentrate and focus, but now it felt like a resting time for them. In the dungeon, they wouldn’t have to worry about someone suddenly popping up out of nowhere and attacking them.

“Dungeon! Dungeon!” The elites from the guilds eagerly cheered.

“We can finally rest……” The branch guild leaders from those top seven guilds muttered in their hearts. They were a part of the elite teams and had been tense like the others for the entire day.

“Form two parties of four!” The higher up guild members passed on the order. PvE wasn’t a problem for players of their skill level. A party of four would clear a dungeon with ease. However, there was no chance for them to beat the dungeon record. Though with their current conditions, entering the dungeon was the same as taking a vacation. They didn’t have the energy to go all out for a dungeon record.

The branch guild leaders from these seven top guilds hadn’t thought that their orders to do this would strike a huge blow to their guilds. After finishing their first runs, they were then ambushed. Against top-tier experts like Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu, they didn’t even have a chance of entering the dungeon again. Two teams had been wiped out by these two players. At the other dungeon entrances, Tang Rou, Thousand Creations, Blue Brook Guild’s players and Tyrannical Ambition’s players had been waiting to ambush them. Through their numbers advantage, they were able to wipe out another two teams.

One dungeon run resulted in four teams being wiped out. The four teams had belong to four different guilds, immediately causing those four guilds to go mad. Soon after, they realized that just before midnight came, their opponents had already begun to monitor their movements at the dungeon entrances. When they saw a team enter, they didn’t reveal themselves. Instead, they dispatched troops to wait for them to finish the dungeons and then ambush them.

The players from these top seven guilds had been on high alert the entire day and were exhausted. When midnight came, their only desire was to enter the dungeons and relax. They had been too impatient and too careless. Not a single player had thought about taking precautions against such a simple move.

It was too late to regret it now though. The four guilds who had their teams wiped out immediately thought that if their opponents were only able to guard those four entrances, then it meant that they didn’t have enough manpower to cover every single entrance. In terms of numbers, their opponents had around 20 players. In theory, it was possible for them to know the whereabouts of every one of their teams.

Thinking about this, those four guilds immediately notified the other guilds to take advantage of the fact that their opponents weren’t there waiting and to hurry up and find a different dungeon entrance to enter.

The teams of the three guilds that weren’t affected were too late after hearing this news. Their players had already entered the dungeons a second time. It was already too late to change dungeon entrances. If they exited the dungeon forcefully, they would waste one of their runs. In addition, it wasn’t worth it for them to enter an endangered status. But if they cleared the dungeon, came out, and met an ambush, they would also suffer many losses. If they wanted to run away safely, they could log off in the middle of the dungeon.However, if they did that, they wouldn’t be leveling, and would suffer even greater losses.

Helpless, the guilds could only face the dangers. First, they would clear the dungeon and then hope that their team’s whereabouts hadn’t been discovered.

As a result, after coming out of the dungeon for the second time, the teams who hadn’t encountered anyone cried out at their good luck. The teams who had encountered players though could only accept their deaths. This time around, two teams had been caught and killed.

The seven guilds saw this and knew that their opponents really had known where they were beforehand and came again to clean them up. They immediately had their teams change positions.

They did what they could. But after suffering heavy losses two times, the teams all felt uneasy. Dungeoning had originally been their time to relax, but they became so nervous that some of them made serious mistakes, causing their team to wipe out. Unfortunately, Ye Xiu didn’t know about of this. If he had, he would have drawn a few more “XX”s on his notepad.

After the last run, another round of both happiness and sadness came about. Some of the teams had been noticed and the result was still the same. Midnight was supposed to be their time to relax, but it turned out to be the time for the peak of deaths. The players from the seven guilds spat out blood with ashen-colored faces.

The experience loss from one death would take several hours of leveling in order to make up for it. The leveling speed of these seven guilds had clearly slowed down. The top 100 characters on the level standing had a huge change. Even though there was a lot of luck involved in who was killed, in general, the elites from these seven guilds were steadily dropping.

During the peak of deaths, their three runs at Thousand Waves Lake finished. Everything was in chaos for these guilds. They had no idea what to do next. After taking a hit in the experience area, everyone’s morale was extremely low. Even those who hadn’t been killed during the peak didn’t feel happy at all.

The elites were split into two sections. One section had just died and revived back at the city. They had no spirit left in them and didn’t want to come out. The second section’s players were safe, floating around on Thousand Waves Lake like lonely ghosts. They were just happy to be getting by.

At this moment, the guild leaders of these seven guilds didn’t feel good saying stuff like “Don’t give up”. Because what was the point in persisting? Everyone had been very careful and on high alert, but they were all killed anyways. For the dungeon ambushes, even if they had predicted that it would happen, there wasn’t much that they could have done about it.

Just when everyone was pacing back and forth, the tenth server guild leaders from these seven guilds all received a message from Lord Grim: “You’re still not going to give in? Is there any point?”

Yeah! What was the point?

The seven guild leaders received this message, but none of them became angry. After thinking about it for some time, the seven all felt the same. There really wasn’t any point in persisting.

Their original motive was to kill Thousand Creations, so that Guild Happy wouldn’t be able to create a dungeon team. But the result? Not only were they not able to kill Thousand Creations, bur Guild Happy’s God attacked back terrifyingly all day long. Right now, their goal had turned into reducing their losses at Thousand Waves Lake by as much as possible. As for Guild Happy? They were attacking them nonstop, while their dungeon team was formed because of Thousand Creation’s and Horse Shooter’s addition.

What was the point in acting like this? If they had done nothing, they might have been able to level up peacefully. But they had to bring trouble on themselves and turn a nice, peaceful leveling area into a bloody danger zone.

Their leveling speed had slowed down and they didn’t have the ability to snipe at Happy’s dungeon team. Their efforts were no longer towards gaining any benefits, but rather reducing losses. There was nothing that they could do to avoid these losses either. The guilds all shared the losses. Some were lucky and some were not. Some had died miserably, while some had laughed sneakily. However, this wouldn’t be the only day. It might not even end on the fifth day. These sorts of days would only end once they leveled out of the Thousand Waves Lake leveling area.

They could retreat and level at Sin City or go to the leveling area higher than Thousand Waves Lake. However, the veterans chose to stay at Thousand Waves Lake; naturally because it was the most efficient place for them to level. Retreating would be taking a loss.

Now, they had three choices in front of them.

One, they could retreat and go to a lower or higher leveling area than Thousand Waves Lake, which would make their characters level slower.

Two, they could negotiate with Lord Grim and pay him materials for their safety. They would lose materials, but would guarantee just about everything else.

Three, they could continue to bear the pressure and the dangers, hiding from Lord Grim’s company and level. They had no idea what would happen if they chose this option. This option depended on luck. For example, Misty Castle had suffered the most, but Royal Heritage hadn’t suffered very much. Compared to the first and second choices, this third choice might be the best for them.

The seniors of these seven guilds once again started discussing.

Chapter 390 – Accept Surrender

The same problem with the same result. After carefully pondering about the issue, the seven guild leaders chose to eliminate the third option.

This risk for it was too high to take. Apart from the pressure they had previously, there was still a harsh reality right in front of them. If any of the seven guilds switched sides, they would be like Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition and immediately switch sides to take advantage of their misfortune.

Don’t look at how they were all despising and indignant at Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition. If they had been in the same situation, any guild would switch sides faster than flipping a page in a book, especially in an online virtual environment. None of them would even feel bad about it at all.

There was no such thing as an eternal friendship, only an eternal interest. They thought about how if they continued to push forward with their current situation and other guilds switched sides, they would be under even more pressure. No guild would dare continue wasting their resources at Thousand Waves Lake like that.

Next was the issue of retreating or agreeing to the terms.

Retreating meant leaving the Thousand Waves Lake leveling area and agreeing to the terms meant paying Lord Grim materials. The former would result in a loss of experience while the latter would result in a loss of materials. There was only one option that could be chosen. From an emotional standpoint, agreeing to the terms felt more oppressive. Even though the guild leaders put their interests first, they couldn’t ignore their guild members’ feelings.

At this moment, Lord Grim’s identity as God Ye Qiu provided them with comfort. After eliminating the third choice, whether or not they would retreat or agree to the terms was no longer an issue of weighing the advantages and disadvantages, but rather the feelings of their guilds. The seven guilds also knew that they wouldn’t gain anything from delaying, so they quickly came to their decision. Ye Xiu received messages from five of the seven guilds, probing him out, asking what they should do, as they didn’t want to continue on like this.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything and simply sent them a list of materials.

The five guild leaders who received the list were already prepared. But when they saw it, they couldn’t help but grind their teeth. Compared to the previous price, there were clearly more materials on this new list. There was nothing that they could do. Times had changed. A price increase wasn’t something that the five guilds hadn’t expected.

The five guilds could only curse angrily in their hearts, but no one made any objections. They replied, giving their approval.

Soon after, the two sides agreed on a trade location. The location would be in a safe area in the city; naturally, this was to prevent any traps. When they arrived, five players from the five guilds were all gathered together. All of them were in the top 100 places on the level standings. Even though these guilds had a frustrating day, mixing up the level standings, the list of names hadn’t changed. However, if they had continued resisting, it would be hard to say that new faces wouldn’t appear on the level standings.

“It’s been a long day, everyone.” Ye Xiu had come alone. Even though the other side had more players, they had already accepted their full defeat. No one said anything so in the end, Ye Xiu began. His words made everyone choke.

“Who wants to come trade first?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’ll go…….” One of the characters walked towards Lord Grim. It was only an in-game character, but he gave a sort of dejected feeling. They discovered that it really was as if they had accepted surrender and were currently paying reparations.

“Oh, oh, it’s you.” Ye Xiu looked at the first player’s name. He flipped open his notebook: “You died four times! It must have been very difficult.”

The Misty Castle player who died four times hastily finished the trade and hurried away in tears.

“You died three times! It couldn’t have been easy.” The second player, who was from Herb Garden, was commented on by Ye Xiu, too. He too quickly completed the trade and left.

“Four times.”

“Two times.”

“Wow, not bad. You never died once? What do you think? Want to join our Guild Happy? Our guild is in need of lucky people like you.” The last player to come up didn’t have any “X”s next to him. Ye Xiu was amazed and even tried to rope him in, but the other side left angrily after the trade.

“You’re too evil.” Chen Guo watched as Ye Xiu received the materials. She knew that Ye Xiu wasn’t sincerely trying to rope him over, but rather mocking him. In game speak, this was a type of trash talk. She laughed, while looking down at how shameless Ye Xiu was.

“Five guilds…… There are still two guilds left. It seems like they’re not willing.” Ye Xiu looked at his notebook. In the end, only 301 and Howling Heights hadn’t contacted him.

“I’ll confirm.” Ye Xiu had both guild leaders on his friends list and immediately messaged them. The replies from the two were practically the same. They were going to hide.

“A shame.” Ye Xiu sighed. He obviously preferred that they give him materials. By retreating to a different leveling area, their leveling speed might slow down, but Guild Happy wouldn’t be able to gain much from it. They were on a different level than Guild Happy! Their retreat probably made the other guilds that were backed by Clubs happier. As for Ye Xiu, he would rather have these types of material goods.

“Our rewards were quite good!” Ye Xiu was very satisfied with his bag filled with materials. Even though the materials he had obtained weren’t all necessary for his Thousand Chance Umbrella, with this capital, he could buy or trade the materials he needed. Next, apart from a few extremely rare materials, the remaining ones had been obtained. He could completely upgrade his Thousand Chance Umbrella to Level 50 without a problem.

But the more important part was how he would upgrade it later. This was because Ye Xiu would no longer have a clear list of materials that was needed to upgrade the umbrella. The path would require thinking, researching, and testing. During this process, it was possible that he might choose the wrong materials and ruin his Thousand Chance Umbrella. If that happened, his only choice would be to start over, which was why he couldn’t stop accumulating materials. Ye Xiu wasn’t confident that he could succeed in the Level 50-70 stage on his first try. Even if he did succeed, he might not be completely happy with the result.

For upgrading the Thousand Chance Umbrella, Level 50 and below only required that he get the materials. After Level 50 was the true beginning.

After thinking through this, Ye Xiu put his newly acquired materials into the storage room. In the beginning, he had earned materials by substituting in. Later on, he had bet with Wang Jiexi. Then, he moved on to selling dungeon guides. Finally, he received reparations from this time’s surrender. His storage room was filled with materials from bottom to top. Moreover, these were all uncommon materials. The glittering treasures made Chen Guo’s eyes fall off. She was only a normal Glory player so all of the uncommon materials she had gained over her many years of playing wouldn’t even come close to that amount.

“How do you play this game!” Chen Guo felt like she was going to cry.

Ye Xiu left the storage room and received a message. Cold Night was still happily reporting his findings.

“Oh, there’s no need anymore!” Ye Xiu replied.

“What?” Cold Night asked.

“They won’t be looking for trouble anymore.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ah……” Cold Night immediately understood. He couldn’t help but think of something though: weren’t you the one who was looking for trouble?

Everything had been dealt with. On Thousand Waves Lake, 301 and Howling Heights had already left the leveling area. Pretending to leave and then sneakily coming back to level was an option, but no guild was in the mood to do that. The guilds were done with leveling while being on high alert at all times.

After telling Cold Night, Ye Xiu messaged Blue River: “There’s no need to report anymore.”

“What?” Blue River also asked.

“They won’t be looking for trouble anymore.” Ye Xiu replied in the same way.

“Weren’t you the one who was looking for trouble?” Blue River wasn’t like Cold Night and directly said his thoughts.

“You guys started it!” Ye Xiu said.

“You dug out our players first!” Blue River reminded.

“I didn’t. I only said that I was Ye Qiu. They left themselves. Can’t you ever say the truth?”

Blue River wanted to cry. He had lost again.

“We’re going to dungeon. There’s a spot. Want to come?” Ye Xiu asked Blue River. The guilds had finished their three runs. It was almost two already. Su Mucheng had a match tomorrow, so she had to go to sleep early and had already logged off.

“……” Blue River.

“If you guys put five players on a team, there are still three players left who aren’t in one, right? Want me to carry one of them?” Ye Xiu continued to ask.

“If you carry one, what about the other two!” Blue River exclaimed angrily.

“Oh……” Ye Xiu replied and quickly followed: “Both of us messed up. After five players form a team, there will only be two left.”

Blue River stared blankly. Then, he realized that there was Thousand Creations, who had left the guild, so there were only two players left.

“Two players can’t run the dungeon, no? We can carry one.” Ye Xiu said.

“What about the other one!” Blue River asked.

“Find another guild to party with?” Ye Xiu suggested.

In truth, the first string troops often formed a mismatched team. This was because each guild had eight first string players. In order to beat a record, they would need five players. The remaining three could clear a dungeon, but it would be difficult. And since they were the only ones there, they didn’t want to waste time, and many just formed parties with members from other guilds. Ye Xiu’s suggestion was a common measure that the guilds took. It was just that Blue River felt that forming a team with Happy’s players would be setting a bad example for the others.

Chapter 391 – The Breeze is Still, the Waves are Calm

The guilds felt a bit dispirited towards the dungeon records. There was no way to stop Lord Grim from forming a dungeon team. They felt like no matter how hard they tried, second place would be the highest that they could ever achieve. There was no fun in that. As a result, some of the teams didn’t care about having five players in a team before dungeoning. Eight players could be split into two teams of four. A team of four was enough to beat a dungeon.

However, Blue Brook Guild had one less player because Thousand Creations had left. Seven players split into two teams meant one team of three and one team of four. Unless there was no other choice, they didn’t want the team of three to struggle on their way through the dungeon.

“You guys form one first. Bound Boat and I will look for players from other guilds to party with.” Blue River was a kind guild leader. He made arrangements for the subordinates first before thinking about himself.

“I say that there won’t be any other guilds to party with.” Bound Boat said.

Blue River stared blankly before remembering. In Thousand Waves Lake, besides God Ye Qiu’s group, only Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition hadn’t finished their three runs for the day.

“Aren’t there players from Tyrannical Ambition? They just happen to have three extra. We can form a party with them.” Blue River said as he messaged Cold Night. But it turned out that the other side had split their eight players into two teams of four and the two teams had already entered the dungeon.

“It seems like our only option is to struggle our way through the dungeon with just three players.” Bound Boat said helplessly after learning about the situation. Blue River also sighed. The seven of them could only split into one team of four and one team of three. The two teams entered the dungeon. In the end, Blue River ignored Ye Xiu’s invite.

Chen Guo saw Ye Xiu’s invite get rejected. Why did Ye Xiu want to invite him? It was because their team had Su Mucheng, whose free time was limited. There were three reasons for why Su Mucheng had a high level. One reason was because when she first started, Ye Xiu had spent time to carry her through. Another reason was because she was good at the game. Her leveling speed was a bit faster than normal players. The third reason was because of the Christmas event. However, even though Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng and Tang Rou had gained by far the most in the Christmas event, it could still be seen from the level standings that no matter how skilled they were, they couldn’t compare to the top guilds’ 24/7 leveling.

Ye Xiu saw that in the end, only four players would enter the dungeon. Su Mucheng’s character wouldn’t be able to do this run, so she would definitely fall behind in experience. If she kept on doing this, she would naturally fall further and further behind. Chen Guo couldn’t help but be concerned: “If you guys go dungeon now, what about Su Mucheng? When she comes back tomorrow, she won’t have anyone to dungeon with.”

“There’s nothing we can do about it. We can’t wait for her. She doesn’t have time tomorrow either. She has a match to play.” Ye Xiu said.

“She’s so busy. It must be tough.” Chen Guo felt her heart ache for her idol.

“It’s not too bad. She doesn’t spend too much time online. She can make it up with her skill.” Ye Xiu said.

“No matter how good she is, she can’t compare to the top guilds’ 24/7 leveling, no?” Chen Guo used to be a part of a top guild, so she knew of this, too.

“That’s true.” Ye Xiu acknowledged.

“Actually, my Chasing Haze is at the maximum level and I’ve also just left the guild, so I don’t have a set team to dungeon with. I can let her sit there for now.” Chen Guo was speaking as if her tongue were in a knot. It wasn’t at all like her usual unrestrained self.

“Hm? So you’re saying, you can help her level?” Ye Xiu understood what she was trying to get at.

“Yes, yes, yes.” Chen Guo nodded her head furiously. She was a bit excited. Playing on the same account as her idol, how fun would that be?

“You would have to keep on moving the card around. You won’t find that annoying?” Ye Xiu said.

“Not at all. Not at all.” Chen Guo shook her head furiously and became even more excited. This was another reason to be happy about! In Glory, the account was tied to the card. To get someone else to level it required handing over the account card. This would mean that she would be able to see her idol every day. Thinking of this, Chen Guo couldn’t help but smile.

“Boss, how old are you?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked.

“What?” Chen Guo couldn’t understand why he asked this question. Her age? Didn’t Ye Xiu already know it?

“Boss, you’re so old already, yet you’re still acting like a little girl chasing stars?” Ye Xiu said.

“Are you looking to die!!” Chen Guo jumped up in anger. She looked around, but couldn’t find anything she could grab to hit someone with. The mouse and keyboard in her hands were newly bought for her to use and she liked them very much. The monitor, too expensive. The chair, too big. Too much commotion wouldn’t be good.

“Cough, cough. Your words make a lot of sense. If you help her level, you’d take a big load off of our shoulders. The guild’s development is at a crucial moment right now. Boss’s decision is very wise.” Ye Xiu hastily corrected himself.

Tang Rou had turned to look at them and was holding back from laughing. Ye Xiu’s bunch of words had calmed Chen Guo down a lot. Chen Guo sat down, not knowing whether to laugh or to cry: “Then how do you think we should do this?”

“For leveling, my character is actually the most crucial! Boss, if you really care, help me level!” Ye Xiu said.

“Help you…..” Chen Guo’s interest had clearly gone down. If it was before, she would have gone crazy from excitement if she could help Ye Qiu level. But after knowing that Ye Qiu was Ye Xiu, Chen Guo’s adoration for the God had weakened.

“Okay……” She still agreed though.

“Don’t sound so disheartened. My account is very fun to play! See……” Ye Xiu quickly switched forms for the Thousand Chance Umbrella, showing what parts of Lord Grim were “fun”.

“Got it.” Chen Guo nodded her head. The Thousand Chance Umbrella really was fun to play with. It was just that Chen Guo wasn’t familiar with other classes. The few times that she had played on Lord Grim were all played as if Lord Grim were a Gunner. If she was going to substitute level, then she could try some other things.

“Let me tell you something first! I can’t play as crazily as you guys. When you’re not using it and I get tired, I won’t be leveling it.” Chen Guo bluntly stated her condition.

“What if it was Su Mucheng’s account?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo narrowed her eyes. Are you saying, how can I be compared to her? Ye Xiu was helpless. He was clearly more of a God than Su Mucheng.

While Ye XIu chatted with Chen Guo, he was also playing in the Thousand Waves Lake dungeon. Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter were veterans. They didn’t need Ye Xiu to tell them much. His hands moved effortlessly and the Thousand Chances Umbrella continuously switched forms. All sorts of low-level skills were used. He was definitely the team’s nucleus.

With him watching over the team and no beginners to mess things up, their team easily cleared the dungeon.

At this moment, Blue River was feeling quite down. He had taken care of his subordinates as a kind guild leader, giving the position to be in a four-player team to others. His dungeon run was filled with dangers and frustrations. In the end, they were unable to hold off the second BOSS. Someone made a mistake and the BOSS wiped their team out.

The difficulty of the dungeon was much more difficult than leveling out in the wild. Dying was a very common occurrence. There was no benefit in dying to a dungeon. Players would still be penalized. At the start of the game, quite a few players criticized this setting. But Glory was ten years old now. The veterans were completely used to this setting and were too lazy to say anything about it anymore.

The only convenient part about dying in a dungeon was that after reviving, players would be sent to the dungeon entrance. They wouldn’t be revived back in the city, where they would have to run back to the dungeon if they wanted to try again. Right now, the three were gathered outside of the dungeon entrance. They consoled themselves, while waiting for the Critically Ill state to wear off. At this moment, Blue River received another message from Ye Xiu: “Died?”

Blue River stared blankly. If his death had been known, could that mean that one of the two brothers in front of him were from the other side?

“How did you know?”

“The level standings……”

Blue River immediately flipped open the level standings and looked. He hadn’t leveled much on his account these past five days. With his death, his experience slid down. Lord Grim and Tang Rou had surpassed him now.

“Oh……” Blue River replied after looking at the level standings.

“We’re lacking one player……” Ye Xiu repeated.

Blue River stared blankly for a bit and then said to the other two: “You, go with Lord Grim’s team. They have a spot there.”

“Ah?” That player was startled.

“Bound Boat, you go with Flower Lantern’s team. It seems like they’re having some trouble without a Cleric.” Blue River said to Bound Boat. Their team of three had a Cleric, which would help keep them safe. However, because of the Cleric, their damage output would be weak. But without a Cleric, they weren’t confident in beating the dungeon just through skill alone. This was why their team composition was a bit difficult to deal with.

“What about you?” the two said nearly simultaneously.

“I haven’t leveled in five days. Missing one day won’t be a big deal. I’ll go dungeon at Sin City.” Blue River said to the two of them. He contacted Ye Xiu and sent their guild member over.

“Oh, what about you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’ll go look around somewhere else.” Blue River was quite relaxed.

“You don’t have a team? That means you have nothing to do! Why not help carry some players?” Ye Xiu suggested.

“Get out of here! I’m busy!” Blue River set off.

“…..” Ye Xiu sent him some ellipses.

No more words were said that night. After finishing the dungeon, everyone leveled at Thousand Waves Lake and everything was finally peaceful again. The top guilds were still a bit nervous, but after seeing that Lord Grim really wasn’t going to attack them because he had received their materials, they gradually began to relax. He would even say hi sometimes, when they came near.

However, his greetings were too nasty. Their names were right there, but he never said them. He always yelled something like you died two times, you died three times, you died four times. What a God! He had even counted how many times the little shrimps had died. That was too improper! Everyone could only silently curse in their hearts.

Chapter 392 – What’s So Good About Excellent Era?

A peaceful night passed. The nervousness that was felt from that day had calmed down. When the light came out and it was time for everyone to rest, the guild leaders suddenly received a message from Lord Grim: “Don’t forget tomorrow’s materials!”

“WHAT!!!” All of the guild leaders were taken by surprise. The wind whistled and roared and their hands trembled. They were unsure about how to reply.

Another message soon followed: “I’m just joking.”

“F*CK!!” Some of them accidentally typed it into the global chat. Those who didn’t know about the situation didn’t know the reason for the curse. Of course, those who knew about the situation knew who the curse was supposed to have been sent to.

Everyone logged off and their substitutes came on. On Ye Xiu’s side, Chen Guo had been with him the entire time, enjoying the show and had even slept even later than Su Mucheng did. When daylight came, she still hadn’t gotten up yet. Tang Rou still had to go to work later that day, so she didn’t delay and logged off in order to rest. Ye Xiu leveled by himself for awhile, up until Chen Guo woke up. In accordance with what they had discussed last night, Chen Guo took over his character to continue leveling.

“I’m telling you, again. If I don’t want to play, then I’ll stop.” Chen Guo emphasized.

“Yeah, I know. I pretty much haven’t done any of the quests yet, so you can do the quests while leveling.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Chen Guo nodded her head and started her work as a substitute leveler. As someone who was straightforward with what she said, the reason Chen Guo stressed her words was because she had played Glory for many years. She had experienced practically everything in the game, so it was very easy to get tired and bored of playing by herself. Apart from special events, there were very few people who could patiently level the entire day like Ye Xiu and Tang Rou could.

Chen Guo felt like she would stop playing after two or three hours, which was a testimony to how well she understood herself. Whether it was doing quests or killing monsters, nothing was new to her. Sure enough, she quickly got bored. The only thing that allowed her to hang on for so long was because of the Thousand Chance Umbrella.

“I’ll stop once I finish this quest.” Chen Guo carried this type of mentality with her and continued…… all the way until Ye Xiu got up. Chen Guo was still busy running about, doing a quest. She had no idea how many times she had said to herself, “This is the last one. Once I finish this, I’m done.”

“Not bad. You level very quickly. You really deserve to be called a veteran at the game.” Ye Xiu said. However, Chen Guo had her headphones on and was too focused on killing monsters to hear him.

“Boss, it’s time to get off work!” Ye Xiu could only get closer and yell in her ear.

“Ah?” Chen Guo leaped up in surprise. She turned her head and saw Ye Xiu behind her. With a look of astonishment, she looked at the time. It was almost three o’clock in the afternoon already.

“Didn’t you say you’d stop playing once you got tired? You had that much energy?” Ye Xiu saw the experience bar and knew that Chen Guo pretty much, hadn’t rested. If not, she couldn’t have gained so much experience.

“Ah, yeah……” Chen Guo said.

“You’re still not tired? If you’re not tired, you can continue.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s yours.” Chen Guo got up. She was quite surprised when she left. When did so much time pass? She had gotten bored quite a while ago. What had allowed her to continue playing for so long? Chen Guo walked around in a circle. In the end, she came back to see what Ye Xiu was doing. Ye Xiu was just continuing to level, killing the monsters that she hadn’t killed and doing the quests she hadn’t completed. It was nothing out of the ordinary. There was nothing to say. Even so, Chen Guo still stood there stupidly for a long time. She discovered that her current situation was: leveling was boring, but not leveling was even more boring……. Her interest in Glory seemed to have entirely gone into the tenth server, into the tenth server’s Guild Happy, and into Lord Grim, an important member of their future team.

“Unspecialized……” Chen Guo scratched her head. If Lord Grim really did appear in the Pro Alliance, what a sight that would be. Against the famous Vaccaria, Desert Dust, Troubling Rain, and even One Autumn Leaf, how would Lord Grim fare against them?

“Oh? You finished this quest.” Ye Xiu suddenly interrupted Chen Guo from her daze.

“Hm?” Chen Guo looked at the quest Ye Xiu was talking about and nodded her head in confirmation, “Yeah, I finished it.”

“Okay……” Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more and continued with his business. Chen Guo pulled a chair over to the side and sat there like a general giving out orders. Even though she knew that she was only displaying her slight skill in front of an expert, she was still full of enthusiasm, especially when Ye Xiu did as he was told. It was truly an amazing feeling of accomplishment.

When dinner arrived, a different sort of excitement took over the Internet Cafe and it became even louder than usual. This was because it was another pro match day. Happy Internet Cafe projected Team Excellent Era’s match today like a movie theater. This had already become a big feature of Happy. Whenever this day came, there would always be more customers than usual. Those at a computer had to play. As long as one didn’t block another’s view, then anywhere else was fine to stand around at.

Today, after dinner, Chen Guo directed the employees to begin setting everything up. The broadcast began a few minutes before the match began and it was projected directly onto a screen. The host and the commentator were already chatting with each other. But once everyone heard the content, they felt like something wasn’t quite right. The customers who were paying attention and watching the broadcast had already begun calling out.

“Boss, what’s going on?” Questions began being asked one after the other.

“What do you mean, ‘what’s going on’?” Chen Guo stood next to the projection screen with her hands at her waist.

“Excellent Era! Today’s TV broadcast isn’t showing Excellent Era’s match. Hurry and switch it to the online stream.” someone shouted.

The Glory Pro Alliance had a total of twenty teams. When match day came, ten matches would be shown at the same time. The TV broadcast was limited. It would choose the most popular match, the match with a feature, or a match that had to be broadcast by contract. That was the best way to get ratings.

For example, today, one of the matches was between Tiny Herb and Blue Rain. A match between Excellent Era and a weak team couldn’t compare to this. If one wanted to watch Excellent Era’s match, it could only be watched online. The online streams showed all ten matches, so one could watch whichever match one liked.

At Happy Internet Cafe, Chen Guo had always projected Excellent Era’s matches, so the audience members were all loyal fans of Excellent Era. As long as there was an Excellent Era match, they wouldn’t watch a match like the one between Tiny Herb and Blue Rain. But today, Happy Internet Cafe was projecting the TV broadcast, Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain, not the one everyone wanted to watch. Of course, they would hurry and remind the boss.

“Excellent Era is fighting Bright Green today. What’s there to watch? Good matches can’t be missed, so we’re obviously going to watch Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain.” Chen Guo said loudly.

The entire audience was completely astonished. They had come for this special event and were undoubtedly all frequent customers. How could they not know that the beautiful boss of Happy was a loyal fan of Excellent Era? There were also rumors that she often fangirled over Su Mucheng. In private, it was quite a topic for discussion.

But today, the extremely loyal fan actually said that there was nothing to watch in Excellent Era’s match. Did some sort of devil curse her?

After a moment of astonishment, someone finally yelled out: “Boss, don’t joke with us. Hurry up and switch the match. It’s about to start.”

“Yeah! Yeah!” A bunch of shouts sounded out. Many of them thought that Chen Guo was only joking. There was no way they were going to miss Excellent Era’s match.

“Who’s joking? Today, we’re showing Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain!” Chen Guo’s voice held no doubts, making them feel that she really wasn’t joking.

“EXCELLENT ERA! EXCELLENT ERA!!! WE WANT EXCELLENT ERA!!!!!” Quite a few audience members protested intensely, shouting and yelling, whistling and booing, throwing around stuff.

But Chen Guo didn’t cower back. She rushed towards the projection screen and jumped onto a chair: “We’re watching Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain! If you want to watch Excellent Era, go back home!”

The fans were clearly more loyal to Excellent Era than the Internet Cafe. Seeing that today, the boss really wasn’t going to show Excellent Era’s match, they became furious. Quite a few clamored, “I’m never coming back”. After a few more shouts, the majority of the audience left. Some had even trashed the place, throwing mice and smashing keyboards, breaking all sorts of things. Chen Guo saw this, but she couldn’t do anything to stop them. She didn’t say anything as she sent them off.

The remaining customers, besides those who weren’t watching the match, were more mature. They wouldn’t be so angry over something like this. The match wasn’t going anywhere. If they wanted to watch Excellent Era, then they could just look up the match on the computers and watch, no?

On the projection screens, the two powerhouses had already begun fighting. The Internet Cafe had turned cold and cheerless in a mess. Keyboards and mouses were on the ground. There were countless broken ones, too. Some of the monitors had been smashed. Luckily, the computers were locked inside the table, otherwise they would have been destroyed as well.

The employees in the Internet Cafe quietly cleaned up. They were thinking that with the boss’s temper, she might collapse from anger and were too scared to call out to her.

Ye Xiu got up from where he had been playing and walked to directly in front of the projection screen. He grabbed a chair and sat down in a comfortable position. His mouth moved: “You’re very right. There’s nothing good about Excellent Era’s match today. Of course, you have to watch Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain. They don’t know what it means to appreciate a good match. The ma’am over there. Could you move to the side? You’re blocking the screen.”

“Ha…..” Still standing on the chair, Chen Guo unexpectedly laughed. After jumping down, she pulled over her chair and sat down next to Ye Xiu without even wiping her chair.

“Cough……” Ye Xiu suddenly coughed.

“What is it? Do you need to smoke?” Chen Guo narrowed her eyes.

“No……. Don’t you think that we’re sitting a bit too close?”

Chen Guo raised her head and looked up at the gigantic projection screen. She nodded her head: “A bit.”

“Let’s hurry up and get farther away in case they feature Wang Jiexi. If not, his two disproportionate eyes will scare us to death.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 393 – Absent Minded

“Do you count that as a personal attack?” Chen Guo wanted to laugh, but she had to warn Ye Xiu seriously, too.

“No way. I’m just saying the truth. If you don’t believe me, you can stay there!” Ye Xiu said as he moved his chair far away. Chen Guo hesitated for a moment. With the way Ye Xiu said it, she felt like he was right and hastily lifted her chair and chased after him.

By the time the two had found their new sitting positions, the individual matches were nearly over. The Blue Rain player beautifully comboed a Tiny Herb player to death, winning the victory for his team.

“Nice!” When Chen Guo sat down, she saw the result and began shouting.

“Which side are you rooting for?” Ye Xiu couldn’t help but ask.

“Doesn’t matter.” Chen Guo.

“Then why are you shouting so much?”

“If they play well, then I cheer for them!” Chen Guo explained calmly. The Internet Cafe was empty. Let alone match days, even normal days never had so few customers at peak hours. In the messy space, they were the only two people looking at the big projection screen.

“If you’re not rooting for anyone, the match is kind of boring to watch.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then which side are you rooting for?” Chen Guo asked.

“Me? I’m a pro, so I look at the match with a studying eye. Look, these guys will be our future opponents.” Ye Xiu pointed to the two pro players who had just finished their match.

Chen Guo’s spirit rose when she heard this, especially when Ye Xiu said “our”. It made Chen Guo feel like she had taken a step into the Glory pro scene.

The second match began. In the entire Happy Internet Cafe, there were still the only two people paying attention to the projection. The others who were watching the competition stayed at their computers, quietly watching Excellent Era’s match.

In truth, how could Chen Guo feel calm, seeing Happy Internet Cafe in such a state? Happy Internet Cafe had always appealed to Excellent Era fans because of its proximity to the Club. Moreover, Chen Guo also happened to be a loyal fan of Excellent Era, so she was able to easily make the business into a gathering place for them. Her actions today had undoubtedly offended many loyal Excellent Era fans and had hurt her own brand. Chen Guo was worried about the road ahead. However, she wasn’t the type of person to swallow her anger. Excellent Era had already turned into an enemy to her and she wasn’t willing to specially serve these Excellent Era fans. Her actions had been impulsive today, but if she had another chance, Chen Guo was sure that she would do the same.

She was worried, but she couldn’t let others see it, so she tried her best to show that she didn’t care. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, truly seemed like he didn’t care at all. Amidst the mess, he watched the match as if nothing had happened.

“Beautiful!” Ye Xiu suddenly shouted, almost scaring Chen Guo off her seat. She was pretending to enjoy the match and didn’t want to show any weaknesses, so she immediately added: “Yeah, yeah. Beautiful.”

Her focus returned to the match. This time, Tiny Herb’s player clearly held the advantage. Chen Guo had no idea why Ye Xiu had shouted “Beautiful!” and she couldn’t ask him either. Controlling her temper, she watched as Tiny Herb’s player dominated his opponent. When the highlight montage was shown, Chen Guo’s question was answered. Tiny Herb’s player had been losing, but was able to punish a mistake to turn the situation around, making even a God like Ye Xiu praise him.

In the third round, Chen Guo felt that it would be too embarrassing to get distracted again. But this time, when she watched, she accidentally glanced at Ye Xiu and discovered that Ye Xiu was the one to get distracted. He wasn’t watching the projection screen. His gaze was on one of the customer’s computer screens.

This customer was watching Excellent Era’s match. Chen Guo glanced at it and noticed that the one fighting on Excellent Era’s side was Su Mucheng…….

The two people sitting right in front of the projection screen both turned their heads and squinted their eyes to see the Excellent Era match, naturally because they cared about whether Su Mucheng won or lost.

In the end, Su Mucheng won the match beautifully. Excellent Era’s opponent, Bright Green, was truly a low-tier team. Their goal was to stay in the Alliance. The players in the team weren’t that good and the their accounts were relatively weak. Even on paper, the difference between them and an All-Star like Su Mucheng was too great. Su Mucheng’s performance was very steady and she won with relative ease.

At that instant, the two spectators immediately turned back after seeing Su Mucheng’s match. Both of them sensed what had happened.

“Cough……” The two people lightly coughed. Just as one of them was about to say something, one of the Internet Cafe employees was deceived by boss Chen Guo’s act and felt like the boss was abnormally calm today. The Internet Cafe had almost been ripped apart, but she didn’t seem angry at all. As a result, the employee bravely went forward and reported their clean up progress.

“Got it. You can throw them away if they’re broken. I’ll have someone replace them tomorrow.” Chen Guo calmly said after hearing how many items had been broken and continued to pretend as if nothing had happened.

“Without discarding the old, there would be no coming of the new.” Ye Xiu recited.

“Are you trying to console me?” Chen Guo asked.

“No, I’m just saying a fact.” Ye Xiu said.

At this moment, the individual competition between Tiny Herb and Blue Rain ended. Tiny Herb won two matches, gaining two points. Blue River won one match, gaining one point. Chen Guo had been too preoccupied with her thoughts to pay attention to the three matches and didn’t have any impression of them in her head.

After a short break, the Group Arena competition began. The commentator and honored guest began to get excited. They took out the players list for the competition and saw an extra name on Team Tiny Herb’s side: Gao Yingjie.

“If I remember correctly, before the All-Star Weekend, Gao Yingjie has never gone up on stage in an official match, right?” the commentator asked.

“Correct. Though I’m sure everyone still remembers Gao Yingjie’s brilliant performance at the All-Star Rookie Challenge. It seems like his performance has finally won him a place for himself on Team Tiny Herb.” The honored guest took the chance to start up a discussion.

“We just don’t know whether or not Gao Yingjie will appear in the final team competition. We don’t have the players list for the team competition yet.” the commentator said.

“If he can show the type of performance that he did during the All-Star Weekend, I feel like he’ll definitely be able to grab a spot on the main roster in the team competition.”

“Tiny Herb has raised an amazing rookie!”

“They really have. There’s no one in the Alliance at his age that can fight evenly with a top-tier God like Wang Jiexi.”

“And he even won.”

“A single victory isn’t enough to say whether Gao Yingjie is better than Wang Jiexi.”

“But for someone to have such skill at his age, has there ever been a player like this in the Alliance?”

“Uh……” The honored guest clearly hadn’t done his homework in this area. He couldn’t fill in this hole and could only evade the question embarrassingly. Luckily, the match had started and the commentator quickly switched topics and began to commentate the match.

“Gao Yingjie. Is this kid really that good?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“He’s quite amazing.” Ye Xiu said.

“If he fights with you?” Chen Guo asked.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed, but didn’t say anything.

“Tell me!” Chen Guo chased.

“I have to see him in actual combat. It’s hard to say.” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying even you aren’t completely confident?” Chen Guo asked.

“In the pro scene, there’s no one who is absolutely confident.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh.”

“I usually say I’m 90% sure. I have to give myself some leeway!” Ye Xiu added.

“……” Chen Guo had no words to say.

When the match started, it showed that Gao Yingjie really had gained confidence from his match in the All-Star Weekend. In this match, he performed outstandingly. However, Gao Yingjie’s amazing performance didn’t win any big advantage because his opponent wasn’t weak either.

Team Blue Rain’s Yu Feng was an All-Star level player. Gao Yingjie was still too green compared to him. In addition, the two sides had an absolute disparity on paper: their characters.

Yu Feng’s Berserker, Brilliant Edge, might not be a god-level account, but it wasn’t far. In comparison, Gao Yingjie’s Witch, Kind Tree, was very far below being a god-tier character.

Gao Yingjie was being raised by Tiny Herb as the one to inherit Vaccaria. Vaccaria would be his character in the future. Team Tiny Herb didn’t have any double Witch strategies, so the Club didn’t spend much effort on Gao Yingjie’s Kind Tree. It could be said that they had made the account in passing while raising Gao Yingjie. This type of character couldn’t compare to an All-Star’s account.

It was true that Gao Yingjie’s brilliant performance in the All-Star Weekend had won him confidence, but it had also made every team be cautious towards him. No one would underestimate him because he was an inexperienced rookie. Yu Feng had this attitude. It could be said that the reason why Gao Yingjie looked more dominant was because of his outstanding performance. However, it would be better to say that it was because Yu Feng was letting him attack in order to get a better feel for him.

After all, as a rookie that had never been in an official match, the teams only had very limited intelligence on him.

At the All-Star Weekend, they were able to see his skill. But what was his style like? What habits did he have? What type of skills did he like to use? These types of intelligence could only be slowly gathered. Without a good understanding of his opponent, Yu Feng’s attitude in the match wasn’t odd.

“Young people! As soon as they break free from their chains, they really are reckless in pushing forward!” Ye Xiu watched the match and sighed. He understood Wang Jiexi’s motive at the All-Star Weekend.

Chapter 394 – Cross Swords

“Who are you talking about?” Chen Guo didn’t understand. In eSports, the pro players were all extremely young, so any of them could be considered as a “young person”, even for those “old” pros who were going to retire like Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu was showing off his seniority calling them young people, but Chen Guo really couldn’t tell if he was talking about Gao Yingjie or Yu Feng. She even though that he was talking more about Yu Feng. In Chen Guo’s eyes, Gao Yingjie was too young to even be considered as a “young person”.

“I’m talking about this future of Glory!” Ye Xiu was still acting like he was talking to himself.

“What are you talking about…….” Chen Guo muttered to herself.

“This Yu Feng is playing more and more with substance.” Ye Xiu said again.

　　

“He was never bad!” Chen Guo said. She had some understanding of Yu Feng. He was an All Star level player and was considered as one of the top players in the pro scene. For famous players, even if she wasn’t a fan of them, she would still know some information about them from their popularity and reports.

“He wasn’t in the All Star Weekend last year was he? He improved a lot this year.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, really?” Chen Guo recalled. Last year’s All Star players…… she couldn’t remember them.

“In my opinion, Blue Rain’s environment for growth is the best among all teams.” Ye Xiu said.

“What about Tiny Herb?” Chen Guo couldn’t help but ask. After all, Tiny Herb had raised Gao Yingjie, a talent that was unrivalled in his age group.

“Tiny Herb…… perhaps because of their Champion status, the requirements for their rookies might be too harsh.” Ye Xiu sighed. He thought of Qiao Yifan. Qiao Yifan might not shine as brightly as Gao Yingjie, but he was also an unpolished gem. If he was carved carefully, he could also mature. Tiny Herb must have seen something in him when they took him in. But they didn’t raise him with care. It was truly a pity.

Even though the players list for this match hadn’t been completely revealed, with Qiao Yifan’s performance in the All Star Weekend, Ye Xiu doubted that he would be able to grab a spot in the main roster like Gao Yingjie.

　

During their discussion, the circumstance in the match had changed. Yu Feng, who was letting his opponent attack, finally found an opportunity to counterattack. His single move turned the tide and he began attacking relentlessly. The sudden suppression made Gao Yingjie panic and he lost his cool. After all, this was only his first official match. Even though the Rookie Challenge at the All Star Weekend had helped him win much confidence, the circumstances right now were different. The pressure and burden of an official match far surpassed a match that was just for show. Any new player would feel stifled in this situation. If everything went well, they might be able to perform well the entire time. But as soon as a bump in the road appeared, they might not be able to perform under the pressure.

Gao Yingjie’s luck wasn’t good either. He had to face an All Star player in his first match. From an experience and character point of view, he was at a disadvantage. Under a dominant performance, the opponent suddenly reversed the situation. It was hard to avoid having his mentality crumble. Whether or not his new found confidence could help him hang on was up to him.

“Tiny Herb isn’t look too good, no?” Chen Guo saw it.

“If he doesn’t take any risks, he won’t be able to bring it back.” Ye Xiu sighed. From what he saw, Gao Yingjie had already missed three opportunities he could have tried. Even though the opportunities weren’t one hundred percent guarantees, they were at least a chance for him break out from the predicament.

Another one!

Ye Xiu silently thought. This time, Gao Yingjie acted. Seizing the moment Yu Feng’s character turned around, he used an extremely low and short distance flying movement to enter Yu Feng’s dead angle. Yu Feng woke up with a start and hastily turned around to attack, but Gao Yingjie was one step faster. Kind Tree swung his broom, sweeping Yu Feng into the air.

It was a risky move and couldn’t really be considered as an opportunity. This was a contest between reaction and hand speed. In this instant, Gao Yingjie displayed his confidence and took back the initiative in one move.

“Not bad.” Ye Xiu praised with a smile. And at this moment, the person who was much more nervous and excited was obviously Tiny Herb’s captain Wang Jiexi. He understood Gao Yingjie better and understood the importance of this tiny detail. If he had failed to seize that opportunity, it would have been a huge blow to Gao Yingjie’s confidence. If he succeeded, it would certainly strengthen his confidence. Even if Gao Yingjie lost later, it wouldn’t matter. At the very least, he would know that he was good enough to have a chance at winning. He would know that he had such skill.

Gao Yingjie’s following performance made Wang Jiexi even more excited. His torrent like offense made him look utterly fearless. Gao Yingjie was clearly doing his utmost to finish the match.

Wang Jiexi obviously wanted to see this type of result. But unfortunately, Gao Yingjie’s opponent showed why he was an All Star. Taking advantage of the fact that a Berserker had higher endurance than a Witch and that his character was superior to Kind Tree, he relied on patiently whittling down Kind Tree in order to defeat Gao Yingjie.

Wang Jiexi was still satisfied with the result because he was certain that Gao Yingjie could also see that he hadn’t lost in skill, but rather because of the difference in character accounts. If Gao Yingjie had used Vaccaria, the result may have been different.

This reasoning wasn’t anything complex. The commentator and honored guest pointed this out while they were talking about the results. After a short break, the second round began. Yu Feng had relied on his character’s superiority to slowly whittle down his opponent, so he had taken significant damage. Not long after the second match started, he was quickly taken down. Blue Rain’s second player fully utilized the small advantage that Yu Feng had been able to set up and defeated his opponent.

The third round! Tiny Herb’s pillar, team captain Wang Jiexi took the stage. With his god level character and skill, he finished off the second Blue Rain opponent without taking much damage. But Blue Rain’s third player to take the stage was also their team’s ace, Huang Shaotian.

This sort of match between God level players was a common occurrence in the Group Arena. The two team’s’ strongest players would be their anchor. This type of arrangement was considered an obvious arrangement. This was also the round everyone was looking forward to.

The commentator and honored guest hyped up the match. The wait for the third round seemed to be longer than any of the previous rounds.

Start!

The two sides hadn’t even touched each other yet, when a storm of messages attacks. They were only hurrying forward to get to each other. How could Huang Shaotian be capable of staying silent? It didn’t matter if he was repeating himself as long as they were words. However, trash talk didn’t work on everyone. Wang Jiexi was clearly one of those players who wasn’t affected by trash talk. He ignored Huang Shaotian’s messaging attacks and quietly had his Vaccaria quickly fly to his opponent’s position.

　　

Huang Shaotian, on the other hand, seemed to have gotten addicted to chatting and didn’t hurry to face his opponent. His character had made his way into a side alley. By the time Wang Jiexi found him, it had already been nearly three minutes……

But once this moment came, the messages abruptly stopped and sword light filled the sky!

Wang Jiexi had been on the initiative the entire time, but once the two characters met, Huang Shaotian was the first to move. Moreover, he began with the Blade Master’s most powerful skill: Formless Phantom Blade.

There hadn’t been any set up for this skill. But having no set up was actually a perfect cover up. Wang Jiexi clearly hadn’t expected it. At the start, Huang Shaotian had been hiding like a cat and seemed to be very patiently waiting. But then he suddenly made such a reckless move. This powerful skill truly caught Wang Jiexi completely unprepared.

It hadn’t been easy to find Troubling Rain, so when his Vaccaria found him, he dove straight down, but was then hit by a gale of sword light. Surprised, Wang Jiexi reflexively responded. Vaccaria, which had been diving down, suddenly shot up and turned around in order to try fly away from the danger.

　

However, Troubling Rain’s sword light abruptly rose and followed after Vaccaria, preventing him from completely escaping. As soon as the sword light touched, Vaccaria was chopped down from the sky and engulfed by the dazzling sword lights. Wang Jiexi had taken a huge blow from Huang Shaotian’s move.

“Hm hm hm, not bad.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

　

“Hey hey hey!” Chen Guo felt a bit unhappy with Ye Xiu’s tone. Even though Ye Xiu was his favorite God, Huang Shaotian and Wang Jiexi weren’t any weaker than him! He was commenting on these same leveled Gods like they were noobs. Chen Guo felt annoyed when she heard it.

　　

“Hey who?” Ye Xiu didn’t feel it at all.

　

“You you you……” Chen Guo said you a bunch of times, but didn’t know how to express what she wanted to say. In the end, she changed it to: “What do you think?”

“It’s only just started.” As soon as Ye Xiu finished speaking, the Formless Phantom Blade stopped. The final hit had a strong Blow Away effect, knocking Vaccaria into a wall.

　

Vaccaria was briefly stunned from being knocked into a wall. Troubling Rain was briefly stunned by the ending lag from his powerful skill. Huang Shaotian had already calculated these two stun durations. After his stun wore off, his Troubling Rain used a Triple Slash to quickly close in onto Vaccaria.

　 　

If he really was able to reach Vaccaria before the stun was over, then that would be best. But in this type of situation, there was no possibility of it happening. Huang Shaotian had done everything he could, but even so, there was a small gap. Wang Jiexi wasn’t the type of person to let this go. As soon as the stun wore off, Vaccaria rode his broom and rushed straight into the air.

But then he heard the sound of a blade whistling through the air. Huang Shaotian had forcefully cancelled his Triple Slash and used a Rising Dragon Slash mid-animation. Wang Jiexi’s retreat had been predicted by him.

Chapter 395 – A Dangerous Balance

In a high skill leveled fight, only looking at mechanics and hand speed wasn’t enough to fully appreciate it. In the match with Huang Shaotian against Wang Jiexi, the two reads made it looked like Wang Jiexi was already going to lose.

Rising Dragon Slash split the air as it rose towards Wang Jiexi’s retreat path. But this time, Wang Jiexi reacted in time as if he had expected this would happen. Vaccaria leapt off his broom and switched directions. He didn’t fly out and instead waved his broom twice. The stream of air created by the two waves made Vaccaria move a tiny bit. This miniscule movement was enough to cause Troubling Rain’s Rising Dragon Slash to miss, brushing past Vaccaria’s side and into the air.

Huang Shaotian knew that the situation wasn’t good. It seemed like he could see Wang Jiexi’s two disproportionate eyes flashing out a calculating glint despite Vaccaria’s expressionless system face. This time, he had been caught in Wang Jiexi’s trap!

Two crashes sounded in the air and on the ground. Two magic flasks had been shattered one after the other.

Acid rained down from the sky and lava burned on the ground. Vaccaria turned his broom around and headed towards Troubling Rain with the Witch skill: Broom Tornado.

Huang Shaotian didn’t want to take a hit. However, Wang Jiexi had already calculated all of his possible moves. The two flasks had been thrown down very quickly. That small window of time wasn’t enough for Huang Shaotian to do anything, when the Broom Tornado flew forward. The huge area of effect magic storm spread out as Wang Jiexi spun. This skill covered an extremely wide area. Even though Huang Shaotian wanted to quickly use a Falling Light Blade in order to get to the ground, but just like how Wang Jiexi had tried to escape from his Formless Phantom Blade before, Huang Shaotian was swept away. Vaccaria’s broom slapped him around like a tornado all the way from the air to the ground.

The combined damage from the three skills to Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain was greater than the damage from the single powerful skill to Vaccaria. Even worse, Wang Jiexi had the initiative. Being slapped to the ground wasn’t the end……

Huang Shaotian didn’t have any problems using Quick Recover. The instant his character hit the ground, his character rolled backwards and then jumped away. Vaccaria had to Quick Recover as well when he hit the ground after using Broom Tornado. If not, he would also crash to the ground. Even though there wouldn’t be any fall damage, being knocked to the ground would be a huge opportunity for the opponent. Wang Jiexi rarely made mistakes for something as basic as this. His character also rolled backwards and jumped away.

The two characters’ movements looked like they had been rehearsed beforehand.

Following afterwards, a sword light flashed from Troubling Rain, while a black mist rolled out from Vaccaria.

During the jump backwards, the two players each executed a skill, a Sword Draw and a Shadow Cloak. But because the two chose to roll and jump in opposite directions, they instantly pulled away from each other. The two skills both missed, neither side was injured.

With the distance between them, the Blade Master didn’t have anything he could use. But the Witch had a few ways to attack from mid range. Immediately, Magic Missiles began shooting towards Troubling Rain. Huang Shaotian couldn’t do anything to retaliate, so he straight up used a big skill. Troubling Rain’s silhouette flickered, instantly creating six images. He had used the high leveled skill, Shadow Steps.

This skill relied on the controller’s experience and technique. Huang Shaotian was considered to be at the top of Blade Masters. When this skill came out, even Wang Jiexi couldn’t tell which was the real body. If not, then the skill would be completely useless.

Six Troubling Rains rushed forward.

Wang Jiexi had no way of directly distinguishing the real from the fake, so he could only test them with attacks. However, Shadow Steps was much stronger than the Ninja’s Shadow Clone Technique. The Ninja’s Shadow Clone was only a clone that didn’t move and also only had limited health, so a few attacks was enough to make it disappear. Shadow Steps was different. The afterimages created didn’t have health and couldn’t be destroyed. However, because they were afterimages, if an attack connected, the attack would go right through the afterimage. By testing each afterimage one by one, the real one could be found.

Wang Jiexi quickly threw out a few mid ranged Magic Missiles and immediately figured out two afterimages. However, Huang Shaotian wouldn’t be found out so easily. The six characters shifted positions with each other in a blur. The commentator and honored guest gasped in amazement. With such complex movements, it was hard to say if Wang Jiexi could locate which of the two afterimages he had tested out.

Indeed, Wang Jiexi had no way of following the two targets he had tested out with such movements. But he had known that Huang Shaotian could do this, so from the very beginning, he had only tried to follow one of the two afterimages he had tested out. This was something that he was capable of doing. Next, he did another wave of tests, naturally avoiding that afterimage and only attacking the others.

It had to be known that Huang Shaotian wasn’t going to simply get hit by Wang Jiexi’s attacks. He was also constantly dodging. In the end, only one of the Magic Missiles hit and it hit an afterimage.

Wang Jiexi knew that it wasn’t possible to find the real one by testing. An attack towards the real one would definitely be dodged. Huang Shaotian wasn’t stupid.

The two waves of testing had only figured out two afterimages. During this time, the six Troubling Rains were able to envelop Vaccaria. The six characters maintained a distance away and spun around Vaccaria.

“Which one’s the real body?” Chen Guo couldn’t tell and asked Ye Xiu.

“I don’t know either.” Ye Xiu shook his head. Huang Shaotian’s mastery of Shadow Steps was already at the peak.

However, Shadow Steps couldn’t be used forever. It was only a skill to confuse the opponent. In a match, a victory could only be obtained by killing the opponent.

The instant the afterimages faded away, a mass of sword light gathered together.

Even though Wang Jiexi had been extremely careful, he was still hit by the attack. If the attack had missed, then Huang Shaotian’s efforts in using Shadow Steps would have been for nothing.

“Who do you think will win?” Chen Guo was impatient. She liked to know the result beforehand.

Ye Xiu slowly shook his head without saying anything.

Chen Guo was helpless. She could only continue watching the match. This match between two Gods was truly spectacular. Finally, those Internet Cafe customers who had originally been watching Excellent Era’s match couldn’t help but take a glance at the projection screen from time to time. In the end, everyone became traitors and they all began to watch who would win this match.

None of the two Gods were able to pull a big advantage over the other. The two sides fluctuated between who was on the offensive and who was on the defensive, two evenly matched adversaries. The health bar on the two characters also dropped very equally. It was impossible to tell who would win until the very last moment.

“Wang Jiexi has a slightly higher chance of winning.” Ye Xiu suddenly made a prediction.

“Why?” Chen Guo hastily asked.

“Wang Jiexi is good at these types of even match ups. Huang Shaotian is good at chaotic fights. The more chaotic the fight, the easier it is for him to find opportunities. However, this match is certainly intense, but it isn’t chaotic at all. You come I go. The one on the offense and the one on the defense keep switching. It’s all very orderly. In other words, if things keep going on like this, Huang Shaotian isn’t going to be able to seize an opportunity to win. If the fight continued at this even pace, in the end, Wang Jiexi will make the final attack.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really?” Chen Guo liked to ask, but after asking, she wasn’t so sure.

“Just watch!” Ye Xiu said.

As a result, Chen Guo began to count. This time, Huang Shaotian was attacking. Next, Wang Jiexi was attacking. Then……

She continued to count all the way until the match was about to end. The two sides were both in red blood. Chen Guo had counted all day and had a bit of experience now. Seeing the situation, she gasped in astonishment: “It looks like……. It looks like it really is going to go like how you said.”

Ye Xiu stayed silent, staring at the match.

“Huang Shaotian doesn’t have any hope?” Chen Guo asked. She felt a bit disappointing for things to steadily go like this.

“There is.” Ye Xiu only said two words.

“What is it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Watch.” Ye Xiu pointed at the screen with his head, indicating Chen Guo to watch.

Chen Guo had been counting the entire time. Now that she looked at the scene, she immediately realized that something wasn’t right.

“It’s not right! It should be Huang Shaotian’s chance to attack, why is it…….”

After muttering for a bit, she suddenly realized something and immediately exclaimed: “Right! He purposefully gave the chance to attack to Wang Jiexi. This way, he’ll be the last person to attack.”

Chen Guo’s excitement had only lasted three seconds because she already saw Ye Xiu looking down on her. After thinking again, she suddenly understood: the two sides only have a certain amount of health. Letting one chance go means that it won’t progress in the same way as before. If they go back and forth, Huang Shaotian will still be the first to die because he’ll have lost more health.

“Huang Shaotian only wants to break the even situation, so he intentionally put himself at the disadvantage.” Ye Xiu finally explained.

“Putting himself at a disadvantage is an opportunity?”

“Compared to continuing on like that, it’s at least a chance. Of course, it’s not a good chance. I still believe that Wang Jiexi will see through Huang Shaotian’s intent. To be able to direct such a scenario, I think that he has some way of controlling it so that Huang Shaotian won’t be able to find a way to kill him in one move.” Ye Xiu said.

“Huh, if Wang Jiexi wins, then Tiny Herb will have four points and Blue Rain will only have one.” Chen Guo calculated.

Chapter 396 – Winner

Glory!!

A single giant word appeared on the projection screen as if it were about to pounce towards everyone’s faces. It wasn’t just Ye Xiu and Chen Guo. The players who had been watching Excellent Era’s match all let out a breath because this intense match had finally ended. For this type of match, even if the spectators didn’t care about any of the teams, they would still feel extremely satisfied watching such a spectacle.

All of the spectators watching the match forgot to turn back, seeming to have forgotten that Excellent Era’s match was still going on.

“It really is like you said……” Chen Guo told Ye Xiu as she watched the match’s replay and listened to the commentator’s and honored guest’s post match discussion.

Ye Xiu nodded his head and didn’t say anything more. He had said everything he could say earlier. At the final stretch of the match, Huang Shaotian intentionally gave up his chance to attack in order to break the balance, but Wang Jiexi was able to seize this chance to end the match without giving Huang Shaotian any chance to find an opening. There was nothing Huang Shaotian could do. He could only struggle and try to create an opportunity, where there were no opportunities. However, this really wasn’t one of his strengths, especially when he was against Wang Jiexi, who wasn’t any less skilled than he was. In the end, he was defeated.

So far, Team Tiny Herb had won four points, while Blue Rain had only won one point. The team competition though was worth five points. The competition only counted points, not victories. Even though Blue Rain had only won one pitiful point so far, the team competition was another beginning. Five points could still be fought for.

However, several defeats in a row would definitely have a serious impact to their morale. Blue Rain’s fans watched on with heavy hearts.

The break after the group Arena was relatively long. After all, the players participating in the team competition were usually the six players in the individual and group arena competitions. They were allowed to play again, so they were given some more time to rest.

Ye Xiu got up and strolled around, smoking his cigarette. Only then did Chen Guo look for her employees to confirm their losses tonight. When the two returned, the host and the guest were still chattering about the previous battle between Huang Shaotian and Wang Jiexi. But after hearing Ye Xiu’s simple analysis, Chen Guo could only feel like the two speakers weren’t good enough. They kept on talking about this and that, but they didn’t get to the point.

After a short wait, the team competition officially began. Because of the brilliance of the match, when the team competition began, the players watching Excellent Era’s match were beginning to glance at the projection screen again, conflicted on which match to watch.

Just as expected, there weren’t any major changes towards the player roster for the two teams. It was basically the same players from the previous rounds. The only difference was that one of the players on Blue Rain’s side was switched out to the team captain, Yu Wenzhou.

This switch was a common occurrence for Blue Rain. Yu Wenzhou’s hand speed was innately bad. If he actually fought one on one, he would be at a huge disadvantage, so Yu Wenzhou rarely went up on stage for the first two rounds. But in the team competition, this Master Tactician was never absent. Not only that, ever since his first showing, he was often the opposing team’s first target to kill, commendable yet worrying at the same time.

The match soon began. Besides the two reserve players, ten players entered the map and set out.

Looking at Ye Xiu, who was staring at the projection attentively, Chen Guo endured for a good while, before asking: “How is it?”

“Boss, with you like this, what’s the point in watching. You should go to sleep. When it’s done, I’ll tell you the results.’ Ye Xiu said helplessly.

“No. I just want to listen to your opinion. I can’t do that?” Chen Guo said.

“If you keep on asking for my opinion, then this will turn into a spoiler!” Ye Xiu said.

“……” Even though Ye Xiu had seen through the situation and predicted the result on more than one occasion, saying that his analysis was like a spoiler was too shameless. Chen Guo didn’t know how to respond. The golden image of her God crumbled a bit more. Chen Guo felt that if she and Ye Xiu continued with this sort of close relationship, in at most a month, her respect for her God would completely disappear without a trace.

“Let’s watch quietly. It’s started.” Ye Xiu said.

The brilliance of the team competition wasn’t any worse than the match between the two Gods. It was true that Yu Wenzhou was one of the four Master Tacticians of Glory, but if the number of Master Tacticians wasn’t limited to four, the fifth Master Tactician would certainly be Wang Jiexi.

From this, it could be seen that although Wang Jiexi didn’t have this type of title, he had the skill. Leading Tiny Herb to win two Championships wasn’t an accident.

This team competition had both strategy and skill matchups, sneak attacks and brute force. The map was enveloped in flames of war with hundreds of bright patterns bursting out. Not long after, the fight had progressed midway. The camera repeatedly switched points of view. The broadcast crew didn’t have it easy either. There were too many brilliant moments to see. Giving up even a single segment made them feel it was a pity.

“Wang Jiexi…… is carrying too much of the weight.” Ye Xiu suddenly said at this moment.

“Hm?” Chen Guo replied absentmindedly. She watched this team competition very attentively and had even forgotten to ask about his opinions.

“It’s not looking good for Tiny Herb.” Ye Xiu said.

“No way? You saw through it again?” Ye Xiu wouldn’t say it when she asked. Now that she didn’t ask, Ye Xiu ran over to become a talk host.

“Wang Jiexi truly needs someone who can help share the burden!” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? What about Deng Fusheng? Li Yihui?” These two Team Tiny Herb players had been chosen as All Stars.

“Whether you believe me or not, if they weren’t in Tiny Herb, they probably wouldn’t have been chosen to go to All Stars.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re saying……”

“The All Stars selection isn’t on skill, but rather popularity. The fans make the vote. Even though they need to have good performances too, there are other areas to consider too. For example, in a weak team, it’s easier to see an individual’s skill. But in a strong team, the team’s outstanding performance might cover up their weaknesses.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re saying Deng Fusheng and Li Yihui belong in the latter category and that it was only because of Team Tiny Herb’s Champion status that they were chosen?” Chen Guo said.

“I’m mainly saying this so you understand that being chosen for All Stars doesn’t necessarily mean you’re the most skilled. For example, I feel like Team 301’s Xu Bin is better than Deng Fusheng’s Knight.” Ye Xiu said.

“Grind King Xu Bin…….” Chen Guo obviously knew who he was.

“Yes.” Ye Xiu nodded his head, “If Tiny Herb doesn’t have Wang Jiexi or if Wang Jiexi performs badly, they will lose miserably. They rely on Wang Jiexi too much.”

“Nowadays, Glory can’t be won by a single individual hero. The gap between players is continuously shrinking. One plus one is greater than two. That’s the sort of strength a team has to have in order to be outstanding.” Ye Xiu continued.

“Do you feel like any team in the Alliance has that sort of strength?” Chen Guo asked.

“Blue Rain.” Ye Xiu said without hesitation, “The team closest to this sort of development is definitely Blue Rain. But it’s also somewhat unfortunate……. Team Blue Rain’s captain, Yu Wenzhou, is extremely key. But because of his crippled hands, he also holds them back.”

“I’ve heard.” Chen Guo nodded his head. Yu Wenzhou’s crippled hands, similar to Huang Shaotian’s chatter, weren’t a secret.

“But….. luckily his weakness is his crippled hands. He’ll definitely be the longest player to stay in the Alliance. In truth, with his hand speed, there’s no way it’ll go any lower. I’m really wondering whether this guy is intentionally not practicing hand speed in order to maintain his crippled hands condition and prolong his ability to stay in the pro scene.” Ye Xiu said.

The two chatted and the match didn’t show any signs of stopping for a rest. As the battle progressed, it went like Ye Xiu predicted. One of Team Tiny Herb’s players was the first to fall. In a team competition, this was definitely a dangerous sign. It became even more clear as the fight went on. By the time Tiny Herb had finally killed one of Blue Rain’s players, Tiny Herb had already lost three.

Three versus five. Against a strong team, turning around this type of situation was extremely difficult. In the end, Blue Rain defeated Tiny Herb, winning their team five points. The late-comer lives above. Blue Rain won a total of six points, beating Tiny Herb by two points.

“If a long term problem isn’t resolved, the opponents will take advantage of the weakness to win.” Ye Xiu commented. He was naturally pointing towards Tiny Herb’s weakness of depending on Wang Jiexi too much. Meanwhile, the commentator and honored guest were discussing the gains and losses for the small details in the team competition. The accumulation of these led to Tiny Herb’s eventual defeat. Out of all of these, they picked out which was the decider for the match. However, from start to finish, there was no mention of the issue Ye Xiu had talked about.

Chen Guo listened in a trance. In truth, she had heard what Ye Xiu said, but she couldn’t see it. On the other hand, she felt like the analysis of the commentator and honored guest had substance to them. Ye Xiu’s words sounded far away to her.

“It seems like I’m just not good enough……” Chen Guo grieved. If this was before, she would have questioned whether Ye Xiu was just bragging. But now that she knew Ye Xiu’s identity, even though he was somewhat shameless, Chen Guo felt that his words felt more weight to them than the commentator or the honored guest.

“Okay, done!” Ye Xiu stood up and waved his arms: “Time to level.” Before he finished speaking, he was already walking towards his fixed seat.

Chen Guo felt conflicted when she looked at him walking away. He was someone who could completely see through those Gods’ intent and could even predict who was going to win, yet he was stuck in her Internet Cafe in a new server killing monsters and doing quests like a normal player. What a waste!

“He has to make it back!” Chen Guo turned her head back to the projection screen and shook her fists.

Chapter 397 – Words That Hadn’t Been Seen in a Long Time

Life in the game continued, players continued to clear dungeons, kill monsters, and complete quests. After all, these are the three main parts of Glory, everything else is just to make these more interesting. These basic frames have never been changed.

All of the guilds agreed to step down, but Ye Xiu didn’t loosen his guard. Since the moment he established the guild, he knew that the other guild leaders would be his enemies forever. They were only temporarily stepping down. It was just that they hadn’t found any ways to fight back yet. If they ever thought up a new scheme, a violent offensive would immediately be carried out, without any warning, of course.

The best method of collecting information was to use someone condemned and hated by everyone — a spy. But Guild Happy had just been established. It wasn’t that there wasn’t anyone who could be trusted. Even if there were, they weren’t high enough leveled to join any of these guilds backed by Clubs.

However, from this point, it could be seen that Guild Happy was actually very high end. It had been established not too long ago, yet it was already considered as an opponent to those guilds backed by Clubs. This had never happened before in the history of Glory, even in new servers.

Guild Happy could only develop step by step because those sorts of methods wouldn’t work. Blue River went back to his Blue Brook Guild Leader account. Peerless Looks hadn’t logged in since then. However because Ye Xiu disabled the join guild feature, the number of members stopped increasing. The existing members had all been organized appropriately by Blue River. Everyone was simply grinding monsters to gain experience now. The guild atmosphere was happy and fun. No unexpected problems occurred. Compared to the first few days the guild was established, the excitement had fallen a bit. This could be seen from the guild experience bar. These days, the enthusiasm for doing guild quests had calmed down. It wasn’t like the first few days, where guild missions were everything.

It wouldn’t be good for Happy to force them to do anything; letting the guild grow peacefully was for the best. During these few days Ye Xiu was keeping an eye on the situation at Thousand Waves Lake and also asking other guild members on the situation at other leveling areas. The atmosphere in the game was unusually calm as if all conflicts had disappeared from the game.

In a blink of an eye, five days had passed and Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter successfully joined Guild Happy. Once midnight arrived, Guild Happy could begin challenging the Thousand Waves Lake dungeon record as well.

During these five days, the Thousand Wave Lake’s dungeon record had been broken a few times. Ye Xiu noticed these, but he was certain that as soon as he came up to the stage, beating them would be easy. It wasn’t like the walkthrough he sold was imperfect. Ye Xiu would be using the same strategy as the guide. The difference was in technical skill.

The higher the level, the harder the dungeon. The elite players of other guilds were experienced players, but level 40+ dungeons were already too difficult for three of their players to beat. In newbie areas like Green Forest and Spider Cave, three of their players was more than enough to beat the dungeon with ease. The more difficult the dungeon, the more Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng and even Tang Rou would stand out.

This could directly be seen by the fact that Ye Xiu’s party still didn’t need a Cleric. While for the other dungeon teams, few dared to go without a Cleric at this level stage.

The closer things got to this moment, the more careful and cautious Ye Xiu became. The main reason the other guilds hated him was because of his ability to monopolize dungeon record. The other guilds must also know that Guild Happy was going to seize the dungeon record in Thousand Waves Lake. They might have had plans for this long ago, but were waiting for this moment to use!

The clock finally hit midnight. Ye Xiu’s five man party arrived at one of the Thousand Wave Lake’s dungeon entrances. Ye Xiu checked carefully around, but didn’t find anyone from other guilds. In that case, he didn’t have to worry about getting ambushed when they came out of the dungeon.

“Is it really going to be this peaceful? I’m not used to this.” Ye Xiu scratched his head, while saying this to his team.

“You aren’t happy it’s peaceful? Is it because your name isn’t red that you’re not feeling comfortable?” Chen Guo look at him disdainfully. For such an important day like challenging a dungeon record, Chen Guo felt that as the boss behind the scenes, she should personally give some advice.

The several players at Thousand Waves Lake were used to suddenly hearing a woman’s voice from Ye Xiu’s character and apparently, she was Ye Xiu’s boss. Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter were terrified after hearing this. Ye Xiu’s boss? What kind of background did she have?

Hearing the voice today again, they know the boss was personally watching the battle and she clearly considered this dungeon record as something very important. The two of them sat up straight, not daring to make any careless mistakes.

“Cough, let’s enter the dungeon” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim entered the dungeon first and the other four members followed afterwards.

Challenging the dungeon record was something Tang Rou liked to do. Because it had been awhile, she was in high spirits. But she also knew how important every detail was when challenging the dungeon record. This was something Ye Xiu had reminded her before. The five of them had run the dungeon together these past few days, so they were already very practiced with the strategy. If they had wanted to, the record could have been made a few days ago. It was just that in order to get the record under Guild Happy’s name, they had delayed it. After all, it was just the five of them. If they had broken the record earlier, it was hard to say if they could do it again. This was something that even Ye Xiu couldn’t say. Surpassing oneself wasn’t easy to do.

Ye Xiu was confident with this team beating the record. Although Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter weren’t as skilled as Steamed Bun Invasion, Steamed Bun Invasion’s newbie playing was like a ticking time bomb. Setting a new record required precision. Ye Xiu would actually feel more worried bringing Steamed Bun Invasion. Even if Steamed Bun Invasion practiced well to the dungeon, Ye Xiu was afraid Steamed Bun Invasion would do some weird stuff. Ye Xiu felt more at ease with experienced players like Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter.

In accordance with their daily practice, this time, everyone went all out. Ye Xiu ran to the front. This was the position for the tank in a normal team, however all his teammates knew that Ye Xiu wasn’t a normal tank. A normal tank used skills to pull aggro and control the monsters. Then, the DPS classes in the team would have to be careful not to off tank or attack the wrong monster.

However Ye Xiu’s tank, pulled aggro through pure damage, so his teammates didn’t have to worry about going off tank. It could be said Ye Xiu himself took most of the difficulty of the dungeon. His teammates had much less to worry about. With this strategy, Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter would be embarrassed if they made any mistakes because the tasks they had to do were too simple.

Two Battle Mages and two Launchers. They were both DPS classes. With Ye Xiu being the core, and Su Mucheng as the support, they rolled through the dungeon at full speed.

Although Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter had cleared the dungeon with them many times, this was the first time they noticed how pro players really played.

“Amazing!!!” The two of them praised. Of course they were talking to different people. Thousand Creations was a Ye Xiu fan and Horse Shooter was a Su Mucheng fan.

But this wouldn’t change relationship between the two because everyone knew that Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were very close. If their fans couldn’t remain peaceful, wouldn’t that be a slap to their idols’ faces?

Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter fought in excitement, killing all the small monsters. In a blink of an eye, they reached the boss. They weren’t worried at all. With godlike teammates, they couldn’t feel the difficulty of the dungeon at all. All they had to do was look at their cooldowns and mana.

Boss number 1 was killed quickly. Chen Guo looked at the time and was very excited. The only problem was that she couldn’t find anyone to share the joy with. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou were both focusing on the dungeon, so she didn’t want to disturb them.

The dungeon progressed smoothly. The second boss was killed even faster. Chen Guo looked at the time and she couldn’t help but run to get a drink to celebrate.

The latter part of the Thousand Waves Lake dungeon was in the water. This was another advantage for Ye Xiu. In PvE, the elites might not feel as awkward in the water, but they couldn’t compare to Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng in this area. As for the others, they were already familiar with this part of the dungeon.

Advance, advance, advance. Chen Guo wasn’t looking at the fight anymore. She just stared at the time, while drinking.

This Level 40 dungeon had three mini bosses and one final boss. After the second boss, they slaughtered their way to the third one too. Although the strategy wasn’t the same, the result was the same. There were no trip ups and the third boss fell.

“The final part. Everyone stay focused!”

This was the first time Ye Xiu spoke from the beginning to the final boss. The whole team worked together perfectly. There was no need to speak.

“Yessir! “ Everyone replied.

“Keep up the good work!” Everyone also heard the boss behind the scenes speak.

“Go!” Ye Xiu only said a single word. As always, Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist started the aggro and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim followed up.

Gunfire, battle spear!

Because of the duplicate classes, the effects repeated a lot. In terms of visual effects, it didn’t look as beautiful as when multiple classes burst forth. However, in terms of efficiency, they wouldn’t lose out one bit. The final boss’s health bar wasn’t being slowly whittled down, but instead fell rapidly at a speed that could be seen with the naked eye.

“Die die die………” Chen Guo didn’t dare to make a sound, holding her mobile with both hands, muttering silently in her mind.

“ITS DEAD!!!” Finally, she didn’t need to control herself. She could shout out this sentence. The final boss in Thousand Wave Lake had fallen.

.

A system announcement flew out: Congratulations to Guild Happy’s players Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Chasing Haze, Thousand Creations, Horse Shooter for breaking the Thousand Wave Lake dungeon record, time: 30:25:41.

Having not seen this for a long time, Tang Rou smiled in satisfaction.

Chen Guo looked a bit regretful. She saw Ye Xiu and Tang You look at her and said: “Guild Happy…..It doesn’t sound good, we should have called it Happy Valley or something……”

Chapter 398 – Too Silent

While everyone was happy that they broke the record, this boss behind the scenes suddenly talked trash about the guild name. This was something that even the experienced Ye Xiu hadn’t expected. Chen Guo’s sound had been directly relayed to everyone from Ye Xiu’s mic. The whole team was in an awkward silence.

After a moment of silence, the first to talk was the experienced Ye Xiu. He continued with the trash talk on the guild name: “Let it be right what it is right now! We can change it when we reach the Heavenly Domain. After all, that will be our main server.”

“That’s reasonable.” Chen Guo nodded her head and then spoke again as if she had thought of something, “Then should we create our guild on the other servers, too?”

Ye Xiu said with a handful of sweat, “It’s still too early……”

“Okay……” Chen Guo answered. She had finally stopped talking. However, the random trash talking had killed everyone’s excitement. Continuing to be excited after all that felt a bit dumb. In the end, Ye Xiu faced the rest of the squad like a great general and said: “Let’s keep dungeoning……”

Only a single run had been needed to beat the record. They still had two more chances to run the dungeon, so, of course, they would use them. It was a very logical choice. The other four members didn’t have any objections. As a result, while their guild members were still celebrating the new record, the five main characters were already back to their usual leveling life.

If truth, their excitement hadn’t calmed down that quickly. It was just that they had been interrupted by a random thought and didn’t know how to continue. For example, after beginning their second run, Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter couldn’t help but open up the dungeon record rankings, admiring their own names in the Thousand Wave Lake dungeon record, as well as the time of 30:25:41, and giggle to themselves.

Due to that, the two weren’t focused enough and weren’t able to keep up with the team, making mistakes here and there. Their second run clearly wasn’t going to be good enough to beat the record. Thousand Creations and Horse Shooter immediately apologized. Ye Xiu told them not to worry. The current record was more than good enough. The time of 30:25:41 was already four minutes ahead of the second place time. It could be said that this was mainly because of Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s strong control over the monsters. In addition, the synergy between the two was considered to be at the top, even on the professional stage.

It was that same reason again: the harder the dungeon, the bigger the advantage Ye Xiu’s team had because of their skill as pros.

Ye Xiu was already very satisfied with the record, but he felt like the reactions from the top guilds were somewhat strange. It was too quiet. So quiet that it didn’t fit the game. The moment that they had exited the dungeon, Ye Xiu had paid close attention to his surroundings, but didn’t notice any movements. Had the guilds really given up on competing with him?

Ye Xiu couldn’t believe it, but that’s how it seemed to be. With Ye Xiu’s experience, there had to be some scheme going on. The top guilds weren’t making a move because they had a plan in mind that was waiting to be used.

What could it be?

Ye Xiu thought as he sent a message. The first person he would contact was, of course, Blue Brook Guild’s tenth server guild leader, Blue River.

“What do you think? Amazing, no?” Ye Xiu began the conversation like this.

“What?” Blue River answered.

“Record! Did you not see it?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Oh, I saw it. But that’s expected.” Blue River replied calmly.

“Oh, so what are you guys planning to do?” Ye Xiu asked.

Blue River understood what he meant, but saying it in such a straightforward manner left him speechless. He could only use “……” as a reply.

“Come back on Peerless Looks when you have time. A lot of our members miss you and they often ask where you are. See, if you had told them that Blue River is your main account, they would message Blue River directly and that wouldn’t be convenient. After all, you’re a spy, no?” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River was speechless again. This was really weird! The boss knows you’re a spy, yet still takes care of you. It was really…… weird! Blue River couldn’t find any words to describe his feelings right now.

“Then let it be! Everyone is going to be out of Thousand Waves Lake soon. Do you have something planned for the next leveling area? To be honest, I’m really looking forward to it!” Ye Xiu added a “hopeful” emoji to his last sentence.

Blue River’s heart stopped beating for a second upon seeing this.

They had tried countless number of plans, but Ye Xiu managed to outsmart them and take advantage of them every time. From this point of view, it was quite reasonable for Ye Xiu to look forward to their plan.

“It looks like you’re going to be disappointed this time…….” Blue River replied.

This reply surprised Ye Xiu. Did it mean that, this time, the guilds won’t be making any moves?

Giving up Thousand Wave Lake made sense because the skill gap in a water battle was too large. They were truly helpless. But for levels 44-46, the map went back to the ground. There was no reason for them to be so obedient!

Ye Xiu could not understand their plan at this moment. He could only go step by step.

Two days after breaking the record for the Thousand Waves Lake dungeon, everyone in the party reached level 44, which meant that they could begin setting the record for the next dungeon. The other guilds’ elite members had already left Thousand Waves Lake. But the war in Thousand Waves Lake left a side effect. The deaths had caused characters who were originally around the same experience level to have significant differences between them. The guilds used to level at the same speed, but it was all messed up now. However, even though there was an experience difference, they were still ahead of Ye Xiu. Their characters were all gathered together already.

The new dungeon was their main task after midnight. This time, Ye Xiu obviously stopped selling his dungeon guides. With him participating, the guide wouldn’t be a guarantee for breaking the record, so no one would buy it. The guide had become an exercise for Concealed Light to train his researching skill.

“Everyone, be careful.”

Midnight was about to arrive. Ye Xiu and his team had already grouped up. He reminded them as they headed toward the leveling area and dungeon.

Because of the difference in levels, the new leveling area was still controlled by the ninety nine characters. Here, Ye Xiu’s team would not have an advantage in the water because there was no water. If they gathered their forces and attacked Ye Xiu’s five player team, it would not be easy to deal with. Ye Xiu understood this, so starting from this level, he had to be more careful in every aspect.

It turned out that level 44-46 level up area Gloom Forest was like its name – quiet and gloomy. Besides the monsters hiding in the forest, Ye Xiu didn’t find any threat from other players.

The more peaceful it was, the more focused Ye Xiu became. Chen Guo, who was beside him, saw his expression and asked curiously, “What’s wrong?”

“Nothing. But that’s what’s wrong.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Could they be scared?” Chen Guo said.

“Even if they’re scared, because of the competition between Clubs, they still have to think of a way and move forward. It’s just like a pro match between a weak and a strong team. The weak team can’t just surrender and not fight. They still have to think of a way to win, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“But this isn’t a pro match with rules. It’s just a game……” Chen Guo replied.

“Game…….” Ye Xiu mumbled the word while his character and his team arrived at Gloom Forest’s dungeon entrance.

“What should we do?” The other four were waiting for instructions from Ye Xiu.

“Let go in then….” Ye Xiu couldn’t do anything. If nothing was happening, he could only follow the normal route.

Level 44-46 Gloom Forest dungeon. Even if Ye Xiu wasn’t selling walkthroughs anymore, he still had to break the record. Therefore, he needed to do research. It was the first time that the team was clearing the dungeon, so it wasn’t that easy. From the beginning to the end, how to aggro, who to attack, etc. Ye Xiu explained every little detail. For the first time, no results came out. His team could not remember every single thing Ye Xiu said. They missed a few details here and there. Three times a day was not enough practice.

This was the same for the other guilds. Gloom Forest’s dungeon record was still the system’s for now. Tyrannical Ambition got the First Clear record though.

The next day was the same as the previous day. However, Ye Xiu’s strategy was based on the synergy between Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. Su Mucheng did not need Ye Xiu to remind her of anything a second time. The two didn’t need any time to get used to the dungeon. With the two of them at the core, the tasks for the other three were very simple. As a result, Ye Xiu’s team was able to get used to the dungeon very quickly, even when practicing the strategy.

On their last run of the second day, they finally managed to get on TV and the system announced that they had set a new record.

The world was filled with admiration and astonishment towards Lord Grim. There was no doubt that Lord Grim was the number one player in the tenth server. The guilds who fought for the records as if it were a life-or-death struggle were nowhere to be seen.

On the third day, they broke their own record. Three runs, two new records. Guild Happy had the first three places on the dungeon record standings.

On the fourth day, they set a new record another two times and occupied five places on the standings.

The fifth day….

The sixth day….

Ye Xiu was intentionally breaking their record over and over again. On Gloom Forest’s dungeon record standings, the same guild and the same characters dominated every spot from one to ten. It was incomparably beautiful. But the top guilds were still as quiet as before.

Chapter 399 – The Coming of the Spring Festival

Fighting for the dungeon records was not as exciting as it had been without all the ruckus caused by the big guilds. It’s just like how a marathon is only exciting when the winner emerges from a large group of runners. If there is only one runner in the whole race, then the race would be very boring. There won’t be any suspense to the results.

This was the case with Guild Happy hogging Gloom Forest’s dungeon records. They had turned one of the most anticipated competitions into a dull monologue. Conquering the top ten positions on the standings awed the players of the tenth server time after time. The members of Guild Happy couldn’t be more proud about this. However, this was getting rather tiresome for the five people who were creating the records and monopolizing the rankings.

Horse Shooter and Thousand Creations were not exceptions to this. After making ten records in a row, their initial excitement was already history. In the end, everyone was bored with making records.

“New record?”

“Yep, new record.”

Even the exclamation mark was gone this time.

“What’s next?” Tang Rou asked Ye Xiu. It was clear that she hated the lack of challenges.

“It’s good that there are no more troublemakers. Let’s keep leveling up!” Ye Xiu was more realistic. His doubts about the lack of response from the big guilds were nowhere to be seen.

Therefore, everyone continued with dungeon crawling, monster killing, missions, and other necessary leveling up works. Due to the difference in levels, the team members stayed the same everyday. A multiplayer online game now just feels like a singles player stand-alone game. It was getting a bit repetitive. However, Ye Xiu was still quite into it. In addition to leveling up his own character everyday, he would also spend some time on guild matters. He also helped out Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, these two promising young players.

He paid attention to Concealed Light’s skill progress and dungeon research time after time as well.

One day, two days….. Time passed like this day by day. Everyone continued to level and pro matches continued to be played.

Ever since that day, Happy Internet Cafe maintained its tradition of broadcasting matches on match day. However, Excellent Era no longer became the sole match. Other exciting matches were chosen instead. Because of this, the cohesiveness of the guests declined greatly and the match days lost much of its former excitement in the Cafe.

After all, in the past, the loyal spectators during match day were there because they supported the same team. They were all friendly with each other because they shared a common language. These spectators might not necessarily like that big projection screen, but they certainly loved cheering and cursing together as a crowd, encouraging their favorite team.

Happy Internet Cafe’s match day event had been so successful because of this type of atmosphere. But now, without the cohesiveness from supporting Team Excellent Era and only that projection screen, the results were completely night and day. On these match days, when an attractice match came on, the Internet Cafe was able to gather quite a few spectators, but it was never as exciting as it had been before.

Many people felt that it was truly a pity. Some of them even tried to persuade Chen Guo to return to the original format, but Chen Guo always rejected them without hesitation.

Happy Internet Cafe couldn’t compare in popularity to before on match days, but the regular business wasn’t affected. The flow of customers every day was as strong as ever.

The peaceful days went by quickly. During the entire leveling process from Levels 44-46 in Gloom Forest, Guild Happy didn’t receive any challenges from the top guilds and, just like that, the dungeon records were conquered.

In the blink of an eye, it was already near the end of the month, and it was time for the Spring Festival. Glory had released Spring Festival events awhile ago. The Spring Festival events were the same every year, with plenty of rewards.

However, no matter how amazing the event was, it would be very difficult for it to upsurge the Internet Cafe’s business.

After all, the Spring Festival wasn’t on the same level as Christmas in China. Even for the Pro Alliance, no matches were held during the Spring Festival. The usual frequent customers went back home during this time.

Chen Guo was a generous boss and had let her employees go on vacation quite early.

“What about you?” Chen Guo asked the employee that had been hired this year.

“What about you?” the employee Ye Xiu asked back.

“This is my home.” Chen Guo said.

“Let me stay here…..” Ye Xiu said decisively.

“You’re not going back home?” Chen Guo frowned.

Ye Xiu slowly shook his head.

Chen Guo sighed, but didn’t say anything. Family matters were his business. Even though the two of them could be considered as friends, Chen Guo didn’t understand his family situation too well, so she didn’t feel qualified to say anything.

“Not bad. I’ll have someone to accompany me this year.” Chen Guo welcomed Ye Xiu to stay.

“What about Little Tang?” Ye Xiu asked.

“She’s packing her things!”

“She’s going back home?” Ye Xiu’s question was a bit weird.

Chen Guo nodded her head.

“Where.. does she live?” It was the first time that Ye Xiu had asked about Tang Rou’s personal life.

But Chen Guo unexpectedly shook her head: “I don’t know.”

“Hm….. Don’t you think that Little Tang’s background is quite mysterious?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo only laughed: “So what? It’s not like she’s a bad person.”

“That’s true.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. He turned around and continued to play the game. Tomorrow was Chinese New Year’s Eve. There wasn’t a single customer in the Internet Cafe. Only the sounds of Ye Xiu’s mouse and keyboard could be heard. The other employees had been given their red envelopes already and had gone back home happily to celebrate the festival.

Chen Guo walked around, bored. Soon afterwards, she saw Tang Rou carrying her luggage downstairs and hurriedly went over to help. However, Tang Rou shook her hand: “It’s not heavy!” and carried it down herself.

“Everyone’s gone?” Tang Rou looked around the Internet Cafe and said after her gaze landed back onto Chen Guo.

“I’m still here!” A hand was raised behind a computer in the corner. The hand waved around, answering the question for Chen Guo.

“You’re not going back home?” Tang Rou called out.

“I don’t have time. I have work to do.” Ye Xiu replied.

Tang Rou and Chen Guo couldn’t help but laugh. They had a general understanding of Ye Xiu’s situation though and knew that he was just joking. That obviously wasn’t a reason not to go back home. In reality, what family didn’t have a computer in this day and age? The Internet Cafe provided a type of atmosphere. For a special time like the Spring Festival, everyone had their own important atmospheres to experience. Those who liked to frequent the Internet Cafe temporarily went back home to play.

“Don’t forget to keep leveling when you go back! Don’t be like Steamed Bun and lag behind after the event is done.” Ye Xiu stopped doing his “work” and went over to sincerely warn the departing Tang Rou several times.

“Got it……” Tang Rou chuckled.

“Come here, take the red envelope.” Chen Guo handed over a big red envelope.

“Thanks, boss. Happy New Year.” Tang Rou smiled splendidly and didn’t decline it.

“What about me?” Compared to not declining it, there was also someone taking the initiative to ask for it.

“What are you in a hurry for!” Chen Guo rolled her eyes.

“I’m not even going back home. I should be getting money for working overtime.” Ye Xiu asked.

“Little Tang, let me help you call a taxi.” Chen Guo ignored Ye Xiu. After months of working together, Chen Guo deeply respected Ye Xiu’s skill, but she no longer adored or revered him anymore.

“Have a safe trip home!” Ye Xiu waved his hands to send Tang Rou off.

“Happy New Year!” Tang Rou waved her hands towards Ye Xiu and hopped into the taxi. Chen Guo and Ye Xiu sent her off until she could no longer be seen.

“How cold! Let’s go back!” Ye Xiu rubbed his neck and called after Chen Guo.

“Mm.” Chen Guo replied and the two went back to the Internet Cafe.

“You’re going to leave it open?” Ye Xiu pointed to the Internet Cafe’s entrance.

Chen Guo looked at it: “It’s not like it matters. Just leave it open!”

“There was even a tree for Christmas. You’re not going to put anything up for the Spring Festival?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo stared blankly for a long while: “That….. I hadn’t thought about it.”

“You have no common sense.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ve always been by myself. I’ve been too lazy to do it.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh, but not this year. The weather’s nice today. Why not go out and buy some decorations?” Ye Xiu said.

“The weather’s not bad? Didn’t you just say that it was cold outside?” Chen Guo asked.

“It’s cold because I’m wearing too little.” Ye Xiu rushed upstairs to wrap up a makeshift overcoat. Chen Guo stared dumbly at him for a long while.

“You don’t have a second jacket?” Chen Guo said.

“It’s true!” Ye Xiu said.

“Didn’t you move over from across the street? How could you be so lazy! You didn’t bring anything?” Chen Guo said.

“You have to know that I wasn’t prepared to retire and work at your Internet Cafe!” Ye Xiu said.

“Then where’s your stuff?” Chen Guo asked.

“Probably.. at Su Mucheng’s place?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah!” Chen Guo immediately grew excited, “How about I come with you to get it? We can go a hundred times. There’s no rush.”

“There’s nothing to be in a rush for.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s not important.” Chen Guo clearly wasn’t concerned with Ye Xiu’s stuff.

“Chasing after a star? Don’t be in a hurry. She’s also on break. I’ll just have her come over some time.” Ye Xiu said.

“What day? What day?” Chen Guo hastily asked.

“What day would you like?”

“Every day!”

“…… I’ll go ask.”

“Okay, let’s go get the decorations first though.” Chen Guo was excited.

After cleaning things up for a bit, the two left the Internet Cafe.

“I say…… Your jacket can’t be the only piece of clothing you brought, right?” Chen Guo began to wonder.

“What do you want to say?” Ye Xiu glanced sideways.

“Have you washed and changed your clothing before?”

“Since we don’t have the same work and rest schedule, I’ll forgive your poor observational skills.” Ye Xiu said.

“But how come I’ve never seen you buy anything?” Chen Guo questioned.

“Taobao, miss!”

“……”

Chapter 400 – I’m Ye Qiu

The New Year’s Chen Guo wasn’t any different than her usual unrestrained self. Traditional or modern. Decoration or food. Useful or not. As long as she liked something, she wouldn’t haggle over the price and just hand over her money. Afterwards, she pointed towards Ye Xiu and gave her blessings with a big smile, saying “Happy New Years” or “May you be happy and prosperous”. Then, she stuffed her bags into Ye Xiu’s hands.

Chen Guo clasped her hands behind her back, walking forward high and mightily. Hearing Ye Xiu huffing and puffing behind her, she was certain that she had bought a good amount.

“This, this and this one too. How are you selling these, sir?” Chen Guo decided that she would buy a bit more. She arrived at yet another vendor’s booth and without even looking clearly at what items were being sold, she pointed to a few that caught her eye and asked. While she asked, she turned her head around in delight to look behind her.

But…… there was no one there! Ye Xiu, who had been behind her the entire time, had disappeared. When she had paid for the goods just before, Chen Guo still remembered that Ye Xiu was behind her.

Tomorrow was New Year’s Eve. There weren’t many people who waited until this day to buy New Year goods, though there weren’t too few people either. Chen Guo stood on her tiptoes to look around, but wasn’t able to find any trace of Ye Xiu. She could only carry the goods she had just bought by herself and search by backtracking.

But after just a few steps, she choked in anger. Ye Xiu had pushed the New Year goods that had just been bought to one side and was sitting on a folding stool, which came from who knew where, sitting and smoking leisurely. The purchased goods that had been pushed to one side looked kind of like he had set up a small vendor booth.

Ye Xiu’s eyes weren’t bad. He quickly found Chen Guo and waved warmly at her.

Chen Guo stomped her way over with a dark expression on her face, but she didn’t know what to say. Seeing the pile on the ground, Chen Guo realized that she really had bought just a tad too much. Telling him that he couldn’t take a rest was a bit mean.

“Is that enough?” Ye Xiu said modestly. All of this was more than enough to last five Spring Festivals. Just duilian alone, she liked this one and that one. In the end, she had bought a total of seven. Ye Xiu calculated. There was Happy Internet Cafe’s main entrance, the restroom, the door leading to his, Chen Guo’s, and Tang Rou’s rooms, the two doors to the two bedrooms, his small storage room, plus the restroom. There were a total of seven doors, so it was the perfect number. It was hard to say if Chen Guo had actually thought of this though……

“Is it too heavy?” Chen Guo asked.

“Obviously.” Ye Xiu wasn’t Tang Rou and conceded. He wasn’t going to carry them all stubbornly.

“Okay, let’s go back then!” Chen Guo said, while picking up a few of the bags.

“Finally.” Ye Xiu heaved a sigh of relief. He picked up the rest and went back home.

By the time they got back to Happy Internet Cafe, the two were soaked with sweat despite the cold winter day. As soon as Chen Guo went through the entrance, she immediately found a nearby seat to sit down and pant. When she looked back, Ye Xiu had already thrown down his stuff, though the person himself wasn’t anywhere to be found.

“Where’d he go?” Chen Guo muttered, but then heard a sound from behind her. She looked back and saw that someone had walked into the Internet Cafe. The sunlight was blinding outside, so Chen Guo wasn’t able to see the person clearly. She thought that it was a customer, so she immediately got up to welcome the person. When she got up and saw the person clearly, she blurted out: “What are you doing?”

The person who had come in was Ye Xiu. He was dressed in formal attire. Draped across his arm was an overcoat. His elegant and stylish demeanor was bewildering. When the person heard Chen Guo speak, he was also startled, but he quickly regained his composure and gave a polite smile: “May I ask if Ye Xiu is here or perhaps Ye Qiu?”

Chen Guo was surprised.

The moment she saw Ye Xiu looking like this, she had felt like she had made a mistake. As soon as this person spoke, Chen Guo realized that she really had made an error.

This person, without a doubt, looked like the spitting image of Ye Xiu. His face might look alike, but more importantly, his hair style and build were a bit different.

Ye Xiu quietly slipping away and switching attire to scare her was something she could believe, but switching his hair and his build in that short amount of time definitely wasn’t possible.

“You are…..” Chen Guo already felt like there was no need to ask this question. The two looked practically the same. Who else could he be?

“I’m his younger brother.” The person introduced himself.

“Twins?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yes. Could I ask who you are?”

“Oh, I’m the boss here. Ye Xiu is here.” Chen Guo said, “He was just here, now…… YE XIU!!” Chen Guo shouted.

“RESTROOM!!” A similarly loud shout sounded back.

“Oh, he’s over there…….” Chen Guo pointed to where the restroom was.

“I’ll wait for him.” The person nodded his head.

“You can sit wherever you’d like.” Chen Guo also nodded her head.

The person walked around a few steps and then asked in a casual manner: “So he’s using the name Ye Xiu here?”

“Yeah!” Chen Guo walked to the refrigerator and after opening the door, she indicated for him to look: “What would you like to drink?”

“Fanta, apple. Thank you.”

Chen Guo grabbed a bottle of Fanta and threw it over. She also grabbed a bottle and asked, while twisting the cap: “What do you go by?”

The person had jumped in fright at Chen Guo throwing the bottle over to him. With great difficulty, he was able to catch the bottle and regain his composure. When he heard Chen Guo’s question, he immediately replied: “My name is Ye Qiu.”

“Ah?” Chen Guo was startled, “You’re Ye Qiu?”

“I’ve always been……”

“Then he borrowed your name?” Chen Guo asked.

‘Yes. He even borrowed my credentials.”

Chen Guo was somewhat baffled. Their conversation stopped for a short moment, when they heard the sound of rushing water from the restroom. Soon after, the sound of a door opening and closing could be heard. Ye Xiu walked over sloppily. Seeing Ye Qiu standing near the entrance, he immediately went “Oh?”

“He’s looking for you.” Chen Guo said.

“Clearly.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

With the two in front of her, Chen Guo could distinguish between the two. Indeed, from only their face, the two looked exactly the same. But apart from that, there wasn’t anything else about them that was alike.

One of them was wearing neat and tidy attire, while the other was wearing the same jacket he had been repeatedly wearing for the past two months. Because their work and rest schedule were different, Chen Guo didn’t even know whether he had ever washed his jacket before.

One of them had an immaculate appearance, while the other had only just gone out to buy some stuff and his face already looked dirty.

Then, she looked at their posture. One of them stood perfectly straight, even the curve of his arm looked as if they had been paid particular attention to. As for the other…… Chen Guo couldn’t help but compare. The guy looked like he hadn’t even worn his pants on properly. When he walked, his head was lowered and his posture was slouched.

“What are you doing here?” Chen Guo saw Ye Xiu walk over unsteadily and greeted his completely different younger brother.

“I’m here to pick you up to go back home and celebrate New Years.”

“Who said I was going to go back?” Ye Xiu asked.

“If you don’t go back, what are you going to do?”

“I’m going to work overtime!” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo immediately discovered another difference between the two: their tone of voice.

Ye Xiu’s tone of voice was bold and confident as if everything he said was right. Even though Chen Guo had to admit that he was correct most of the time and everything should be like he said, but his tone of voice still made others want to punch him. In comparison, his younger brother had a very formal tone of voice. It was polite and proper. His tone of voice made it so it was impossible to tell if there was anything wrong. Chatting with such a person wouldn’t be unpleasant.

“Did she introduce herself? This is my boss.” Ye Xiu introduced Chen Guo to Ye Qiu, “She’s the one who told me to work overtime.”

“Is that right?” Ye Qiu looked towards Chen Guo with uncertainty.

“He asked for it. I approved.” Chen Guo wouldn’t be unjustly blamed like that.

Ye Qiu’s gaze immediately switched back to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu exposed a helpless expression: “I won’t go back. It’ll be the same as always. Why ask why?”

“It’s different now. Didn’t you retire this year? Then what are you doing drifting around outside?” Ye Qiu said.

Chen Guo’s heart thumped. She suddenly recalled the guess she had made with Tang Rou that night. Had Ye Xiu’s retirement been caused by his family pressuring the Club from behind the scenes? If not, why would his family immediately want him to come back after he retired?

“Retiring doesn’t mean anything. You outsiders wouldn’t understand.” Ye Xiu said.

“Retiring….. Even if you want to come back, it will still take a year, no?” Ye Qiu said.

“Oh, you even know of this?”

“It’s not like you have anything to do this year. Why not come back home and take a rest?” Ye Qiu said.

“I can rest anywhere. It’s all the same.” Ye Xiu said.

“Father’s health hasn’t been too good recently……”

“That’s what you always say……”

“Fine! Actually, mother’s…….”

“You’re lying!”

“Little Dot died!”

“It’s about time. He’s already lived long enough!” Ye Xiu said coldly.

Chen Guo couldn’t listen any longer, but she felt like she had to understand something: “Who’s Little Dot?”

“A dog.” Ye Xiu said.

“……” Chen Guo suddenly realized the brother deserved to be the brother. Twins really were twins. These two people had some understand with each other on some areas. The specifics would need more observation. Chen Guo pondered. She retreated two steps and sat in the chair behind her. She took two sips and continued to watch the show.

“Should I record it?” Chen Guo felt the phone in her pocket. She had even thought of doing this.

“You really should come back.” Ye Qiu continued to urge him.

“Heh…….” Ye Xiu chuckled, “If I go back, it’ll make it easy for you to run away. Is that it?”

The very proper Ye Qiu had maintained his poise the entire time. This time, it seemed like his heart had twisted. Chen Guo watched as he suddenly shot forward like an arrow towards Ye Xiu and grabbed Ye Xiu’s clothing with his two hands.

Chen Guo started. She stood up and then heard Ye Qiu say angrily: “You shameful brother! That year, you stole the luggage that I had meticulously prepared. You went too far!”

“It’s more like I promptly discovered that my stupid little brother was about to run away from the family like an immature child and decided to take his place to teach him a lesson by example.” Ye Xiu answered.

Chapter 401 – Temporary Guest

Shameless!” Ye Qiu tugged at the collar on Ye Xiu’s jacket. In the end, he wasn’t able to get anything out of it though and could only grind his teeth in anger. Chen Guo suddenly empathized with his hateful, yet helpless expression because Ye Xiu frequently put her in this sort of situation as well.

“It looks like you weren’t educated well enough.” Ye Xiu’s expression was the same as usual.

“Come back home with me!” Ye Qiu gnashed his teeth.

“No way.” Ye Xiu said.

Ye Qiu’s gaze was deep and profound as if he were about to pull off some powerful move. Chen Guo continued to watch, waiting for it to happen. However, the scene froze and stopped playing…….

“Are you tired? Hurry up and let go. Show some respect to your elders.” Ye Xiu said and made a slap. It seemed like Ye Qiu’s hands weren’t using much force and were slapped aside by Ye Xiu.

“Your overcoat seems pretty nice?” Ye Xiu, with his sole jacket, looked at the overcoat that had been hanging on Ye Qiu’s arm the entire time.

“No way!” Ye Qiu resolutely hid the overcoat behind him.

“How selfish.” Ye Xiu disdained.

“When are you going to give back the stuff you took from me?” Ye Qiu said.

“Didn’t I give you back your proof of identity?”

Ye Qiu suddenly choked. He had clearly forgotten about that part.

Chen Guo raised her hand: “Could you go into more details? The story behind the proof of identity.”

“Oh….. that one……. That time, when I was going to join the Pro Alliance, I obviously needed to use official documents as proof of my identity. However, even though I was old enough, because I ran away from my family, I didn’t have anything I could use as proof.” Ye Xiu said.

“When this disgrace went back home to steal some proof, he wasn’t able to steal the household register, so he took my proof of identity instead.” Ye Qiu immediately followed.

“I was borrowing. Didn’t I give it back to you?” Ye Xiu said.

“You didn’t tell me, so that’s considered stealing!”

“I did tell you later.”

“So it’s like that!” Chen Guo suddenly understood. This explained why Ye Xiu used “Ye Qiu” in the pro scene.

“Yeah, it’s not like I could have used a fake proof!” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo began to sweat. Isn’t using someone else’s proof of identity and using a fake identity practically the same? They were twin brothers, so it was hard to tell the difference.

“Luck you, look how famous your name is now.” Ye Xiu said to Ye Qiu.

“Tch.” Ye Qiu coldly expressed his disdain.

“You used such a familiar name. You weren’t worried that your family would find you?” Chen Guo asked.

“If I had used Ye Xiu, then that might have been troublesome. But since I used a weak, common street name like Ye Qiu, there was no need to worry.” Ye Xiu said.

“Nonsense! The key point is that no one had imagined that you would run away from the family to play games. You’re the weak one!” Ye Qiu shouted.

“Oh? Then when you wanted to leave the family that time, what were you planning on doing?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Uh….. I……” Ye Qiu tried hard to recall.

“Or maybe you had a dream you wanted to fulfill?” Ye Xiu asked.

“My dream at that time…… was to leave the family……” Ye Qiu said.

…… Chen Guo nearly spat out her drink. She suddenly felt sorry for the parents of these two brothers. What type of family environment was this, to make these two brothers want to leave the family? Chen Guo was very curious.

“That’s the difference between me and you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Tch.” Ye Qiu expressed his disdain.

“Actually, I stopped hiding after a while. The family could easily force me to come back, but do you know why they never did so?” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Ye Qiu couldn’t help but ask.

“Because my dream was the game and that was all.” Ye Xiu said.

“Huh?” Ye Qiu and Chen Guo asked.

“An eSports career favors the young. I’m already considered old as a pro. Even if I persisted, I wouldn’t be able to go on for much longer. This is why my dream will end at an early age. When that time comes, I’ll naturally come back because that place will forever be my home. And at my age, there’s still time for me to make a turn around at life. This is why my family left me alone.” Ye Xiu said.

“And you? You’re different. Your dream was only to leave the family. You’re clearly even more rebellious than me. I at least knew what to do after I ran away. You? You wanted to run just for the sake of running away. If you ran away, would you think of coming back? From my view, you probably wouldn’t, so it’d be best if you just stayed in the family like an obedient child. Leaving home…… did you really think that it would be fun?” Ye Xiu said.

Ye Qiu was stumped for words. He had even forgotten to express his usual disdain. Chen Guo was also surprised. Ye Xiu was actually a good brother. He was more sensible than his brother and saw the issue more thoroughly.

“So I won’t be going back to celebrate New Years. When the time comes, I’ll come back on my own.”

After Chen Guo heard this, she suddenly wondered whether Ye Xiu was only saying all of that as an excuse to not go back home.

As for Ye Qiu? After a short pause, he suddenly smiled: “It won’t be too late if I come back home tomorrow.”

He turned his head to look at Chen Guo: “Boss, is it okay if I stay here for the night?”

Chen Guo nodded her head: “You can even stay here for a few nights if you want.”

“Can you not look for trouble.” Ye Xiu immediately stopped her, “Look how evil this guy looks.”

”

“Tch!” Ye Qiu’s usual disdain rebooted. After a hmph, he walked around the first floor of the Internet Cafe. Then, he went to the stairs and asked: “Do I go upstairs?”

“Yes. I’ll bring you there.” Chen Guo went over the lead the way.

“Thank you.” Ye Qiu nodded his head in thanks. As long as he wasn’t talking to Ye Xiu, his words and actions showed propriety and politeness.

“It’s not a problem.” Chen Guo waved her hands, leading Ye Qiu upstairs. Ye Xiu didn’t say anything. Seeing the two go up the stairs, he shook his head, lit a cigarette, and looked for a computer to log into Glory.

“We sleep here.” Chen Guo opened the door to the living room and showed Ye Qiu around.

“It gives off a very comfortable feeling!” Ye Qiu praised after entering the room.

“Doesn’t it?” Chen Guo replied happily. As the room’s owner, of course, she would be happy about praise towards it.

“Where does Ye Xiu live?” Ye Qiu asked.

“Uh……” Chen Guo stared blankly. She looked somewhat embarrassed. Ye Xiu’s living space really was quite embarrassing to talk about. As the owner, who had arranged Ye Xiu’s living space, it was quite awkward to talk about in front of Ye Xiu’s relative.

“This way.” Even though she felt embarrassed, Chen Guo didn’t hide it. She opened the door to the storage room, but in the end, she still added: “It’s only temporary.”

She wasn’t lying. In the beginning, Chen Guo had only temporarily put Ye Xiu here. However, Ye Xiu didn’t care and seemed pretty happy with his living space, so Chen Guo didn’t feel like she needed to be in a rush towards this.

“Good, good!” Ye Qiu replied. He had already seen everything there was to see in the storage room. His face didn’t show any expression of being in disbelief like Chen Guo had imagined. He seemed quite happy and delighted. He even turned around and said earnestly: “It’s very good.”

“Oh?” Chen Guo was surprised, but she quickly realized why. The guy saw that his shameful brother was living in such a place, which was why he was so happy.

“Where will I be sleeping?” Ye Qiu asked.

“Oh….. you can come to my room!” Chen Guo led Ye Qiu out and pointed to her own room.

“Then what about you?”

“I’ll sleep next door. The sis over there went back home to celebrate New Years, so she won’t be here for the new few days.” Chen Guo was obviously talking about Tang Rou’s room.

“You all…… live together?” Ye Qiu looked at the three rooms.

“Yeah!”

“There aren’t any problems are there? Living with my shameless brother? You must be careful!” Ye Qiu said.

“No way.” Chen Guo laughed. Even though Ye Xiu was sometimes a very infuriating person, he didn’t have any faults in this area. He had been living with the two beauties for quite a while and nothing embarrassing had happened yet.

But if that guy did anything embarrassing, he would probably resolve it in a shameless manner. Chen Guo suddenly thought.

“It wouldn’t be convenient living in a lady’s room! Can I sleep on this sofa?” Ye Qiu pointed at the sofa in the living room.

“It’s not a problem!” Chen Guo said.

“Okay, then I’ll sleep here!”

“I’m saying that you sleeping in my room isn’t a problem.” Chen Guo explained.

“Don’t worry, don’t worry. I’ll sleep here!” Ye Qiu said and expressed that he wasn’t going to give in.

“Okay, then you can……” Chen Guo didn’t urge it and asked: “Do you have any luggage?”

“No.”

“Okay, are you going to rest for a bit?” Chen Guo asked.

“No need. No need. I’m going to go down and see what that guy is up to!” Ye Qiu turned around and pulled open the door. Like a gentleman, he gave priority to ladies and asked if Chen Guo was going to go out too.

The two went downstairs back to the Internet Cafe and saw Ye Xiu diligently playing the game.

“You only know how to play! You’re not going to tidy up all the stuff we bought?” Chen Guo scolded.

“Exactly. He only knows how to play games. Shameful.” Ye Qiu stood by Chen Guo and acted all mighty.

Ye Xiu lifted his head helplessly: “How do you want to do it.”

Chen Guo carelessly pointed around: “Use everything that’s useful!”

Ye Xiu said powerlessly: “Do you know how much of the stuff you bought is useful?”

Chen Guo stared blankly. She had only bought whatever she liked. She didn’t know what exactly she had bought and was already having trouble remembering.

“Shut your mouth! Cut his salary, boss!” Ye Qiu incited.

“How about you first figure out what you’ve bought!” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

“Even the useless stuff has to be tidied up!” Chen Guo said and then ran over to study what she had bought.

“Ye Qiu, go help.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why don’t you go?”

“I’m working.”

“You’re just playing a game……” Ye Qiu mumbled to himself, but still went to help out. He wasn’t the type of person to sit on the side and tell others to work without doing anything himself.

Chapter 402 – Experience Life

“How tiring!” Ye Xiu stretched from his computer. The two people behind him who were tidying up the New Year goods, glared at him in anger.

“How’s it going? Did you finish cleaning up?” Ye Xiu walked over with his two hands behind his back as if he were an inspector.

Chen Guo lifted her hand and threw something at him. Ye Xiu was quite nimble though. He raised his hand and caught it. He looked at it and saw that it was an apple.

“Go wash the fruit!” Chen Guo gave Ye Xiu as task to do. But shortly afterwards, she heard a “crunch” and the apple she had thrown at Ye Xiu had a bite taken out of it.

“What? You hadn’t washed it yet……” Ye Xiu, who had taken a bite out of the apple, was as tranquil as ever. He spat out the apple he had taken a bite out of and tossed the eaten apple back at Chen Guo.

Chen Guo didn’t catch it. She let the apple go flying past her directly towards the entrance, where it fell and rolled on the ground.

“Come here and work.” Chen Guo said expressionlessly.

Ye Xiu toddled over and the three began organizing the items they had just bought.

Even though it was nearly New Years, the Internet Cafe had some business. It was just that the people who occasionally passed by and took a look around were scared by the scene they saw.

“Boss…… are you preparing for a party?” One person saw the various ornaments scattered around and asked in astonishment.

Chen Guo was delighted. This misunderstanding was a type of acknowledgement as a result of their hard work.

“Come, come, come. You can sit anywhere. The candy, melon seeds, and peanuts are free!” The customers who were lured in all received free candy and snacks as a gift.

“Not bad.” The tidying up they had done the entire afternoon made the Internet Cafe look like there was a party going on. Chen Guo wiped some sweat from her forehead and said happily.

“Come here. Both of you get a red envelope.” Chen Guo turned her head and gave the two brothers a reward.

“Thanks, boss.” Ye Xiu replied without batting an eyelid.

“Ha ha, there’s even a red envelope!” Ye Qiu didn’t decline.

“You’re going back tomorrow, right? Then, let’s have a good dinner tonight.” Chen Guo said.

“What do you mean by eat a good dinner?” Ye Xiu had already lived in Happy Internet Cafe for two months and had experienced Chen Guo’s idea of a “good dinner”. It was usually just a few more dishes.

Chen Guo stared at him: “Let’s see it’s still possible to order some.” She took out her cellphone. This time, she was planning on having an actual “good dinner”. She was going to order a feast.

“Don’t, don’t, don’t.” Ye Qiu jumped out to stop her, “There’s no need to go through all that trouble. What do you two usually eat? We can just eat the same!”

Chen Guo was surprised when she heard this and then laughed: “I understand. You want to experience what life here is like?”

“However…… you probably won’t be able to get a realistic experience today!” Chen Guo looked at the restaurant near them. That restaurant had good business relations with the Internet Cafe. She would order food from the small restaurant there. But today, the restaurant owner had gone home to celebrate New Years, so it wasn’t open.

“Just a general feeling would be fine.” Ye Qiu said.

“Okay!” Chen Guo nodded her head. She took her purse and gave a few hundred yuan bills to Ye Xiu : “Go out and make a left. There will definitely be a few restaurants that haven’t closed yet. Hurry.”

She pointed at the running Ye Xiu to Ye Qiu: “Look, that’s a part of our life.”

“Ha ha ha, how wonderful!” Ye Qiu laughed.

“How about you go? To get the experience.” Ye Xiu handed the money over to Ye Qiu.

“No need. I’ll skip this part!” Ye Qiu wasn’t an idiot. Running errands wasn’t anything he needed to experience.

Ye Xiu held a cigarette in his mouth and left the building. Chen Guo called Ye Qiu over and set up the dining table they usually used in their day to day life. Then, she pointed at the few customers: “There isn’t really anyone here today. Usually, there are a lot of customers at this hour. Some of them will have food with them and the entire Internet Cafe will smell like delicious food.”

“How unfortunate. We won’t be experiencing it today.” Ye Qiu sighed.

“If you ever get the chance, feel free to come again!” Chen Guo said.

“Okay, I will definitely!” Ye Qiu nodded his head.

The two sat at the dining table and chatted. Ye Qiu told Chen Guo quite a few stories about Ye Xiu when he was young. Chen Guo really wanted to know about these, so she could use them as revenge against Ye Xiu. When she thought carefully, ever since Ye Xiu had arrived at Happy Internet Cafe, she was often the one who suffered. Chen Guo didn’t want to be that kind of story character.

“I’m back.” Ye Xiu finally came back with two bags full of food.

“It smells amazing.” Ye Qiu was already beginning to grow impatient.

“Oh, did we not eat this afternoon?” Chen Guo recalled.

“If you’re hungry, just eat more.” Ye Xiu put down the food and smoked his cigarette first.

“Let’s see what we have here.” Ye Qiu took out the boxes of food.

“Oh, pretty good, pretty good.”

“Ah, very good, very good.”

“Hm? Not bad, not bad.”

“How great! I like all of these.” Ye Qiu looked at the food and nodded his head repeatedly.

“It’s hard to tell, but you’re actually a good brother.” Chen Guo said.

“I’ve always been. It’s just that young people don’t know what they’re doing, which is why such a misunderstanding came about.” Ye Xiu said.

Young people…… Chen Guo was somewhat speechless. They were twins. Even though one was a bit younger and the other was a bit older, in reality, the difference was negligible.

“No alcohol?” Ye Qiu opened up a box of food and realized that there was nothing to drink.

“That’s right! You didn’t buy any alcohol?” Chen Guo asked.

“I don’t drink alcohol.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?” Chen Guo was surprised.The smoker, Ye Xiu, actually didn’t drink alcohol. She hadn’t expected this.

“Too much alcohol and your hands will shake.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, got it!” Chen Guo understood. A pro player had to have two steady hands. A minor micro mistake could have serious consequences. As a pro player, one had to be careful when drinking alcohol.

“You don’t drink, but we do!” Ye Qiu said.

“That’s right!” Chen Guo also thought, “We do!”

“You two…… I don’t have the hands……” Ye Xiu was helpless.

“Oh.” Chen Guo realized and then got up: “I still have some alcohol upstairs. They’ve been up there for awhile and haven’t been touched. I’ll go grab them for us to drink. Ye Xiu can help.”

Ye Xiu had only just sat down, but had to get up again. The two went up, while Chen Guo asked: “What type of alcohol does your brother like?”

“I haven’t been home in ten years.” Ye Xiu reminded. He really didn’t know what type of alcohol Ye Qiu liked.

“Go ask.” Chen Guo said.

As a result, Ye Xiu went back down. Not long after, Ye Qiu went up. Chen Guo was speechless. She called Ye Qiu over to personally pick the alcohol.

“Come, come, come. We’ll just pretend that today is New Year’s! Happy New Year, Happy New Year.” After all, Chen Guo was the real host. She raised her cup and began calling the two brothers over.

Ye Xiu said he didn’t drink alcohol, but he still poured a bit into his cup. The three touched cups and drank. The Internet Cafe still had a few customers, who saw the three celebrate the holiday as if there weren’t anyone around them.

There were numerous dishes. Chen Guo had grabbed quite a few drinks too. But this feast turned out to be extremely short-lived. No one had imagined that Ye Qiu would get drunk so quickly. He was completely drunk and after a short moment, his head suddenly dropped to the table. No matter how much they yelled and yelled, he wouldn’t wake up.

“How weak.” Ye Xiu shook his head.

“He can’t drink?” Chen Guo was also astonished.

“I really have no idea.” Ye Xiu said.

“You guys don’t even know if you’re allergic to alcohol?” Chen Guo began to worry.

“I’m not allergic. We have the same DNA, so I doubt he’s allergic.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do we do?”

“Are you done eating?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Not yet.”

“Then keep eating.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo took some food and suddenly remembered something: “You aren’t going to be like him and drop dead after drinking such a small amount right?”

“Impossible.” Ye Xiu denied.

“You’ve never drunk any alcohol, so you don’t actually know either, right?” Chen Guo said.

“Uh……” Ye Xiu didn’t know how to reply.

“The same DNA. Tsk tsk tsk.” Chen Guo sighed.

“We’ve got different futures ahead of us. Tsk tsk tsk.” Ye Xiu also sighed.

“You’re just saying that! He seems like he won’t be someone with no future like you.” Chen Guo said.

“Of course, I was just saying that.’ Ye Xiu said.

Ye Qiu lied on his stomach for a good two hours. When he woke up, he was still in a daze.

“Are you okay?” A bowl of vegetables was quickly given to him. Chen Guo looked at him.

“Oh? Did something happen?’ Ye Qiu asked, confused.

“You got drunk.” Chen Guo said.

“Really? For how long?” Ye Qiu asked.

“Two hours.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh no. It’s late now, isn’t it?” Ye Qiu said. He looked at the time and stared stupidly. When he recalled, he realized how quickly he had fallen drunk. It was certainly a length of time that would make others worry.

“Cough……” Ye Qiu was too embarrassed to say anything.

“How are you now?” Chen Guo asked.

“I’m fine, I’m fine. It’s all good!” Ye Qiu got up and wanted to prove himself. But as soon as he got up, he nearly fell.

“Ah, I’m so dizzy.” Ye Qiu shouted. Chen Guo hastily supported him.

“If you’re dizzy, go up and have a rest!” Chen Guo said.

“No need. No need. You don’t need to help me. No one needs to help me.” Ye Qiu insisted that he was fine. After swaying back and forth for two steps, his hands slapped the wall: “I’ll just use the wall……” He paused.

Chen Guo didn’t know whether to laugh or cry and called Ye Xiu over.

“What a useless person.” Ye Xiu was helpless.

“Do you still remember where the stairs are?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I know. I know.” Ye Qiu said.

“Where?”

“Hm, the other side of the wall…..” Ye Qiu said.

“Get out of here!” Ye Xiu extended his hands to support him. Chen Guo also helped. This time, Ye Qiu didn’t insist and he was dragged up to the second floor.

“Should we have him sleep at my place?” Chen Guo said to Ye Xiu.

“No need. No need. I’ll sleep here!!” Ye Qiu was still awake and he stubbornly pointed his finger. But his finger went astray and he pointed at a table in the guest room.

“Throw him over to my place……” Ye Xiu opened his own door and really did throw Ye Qiu into his room. He took off his shoes and put the blanket over him.

“It’s quite nice having a brother, no?” Seeing Ye Xiu help tidy up Ye Qiu, Chen Guo chuckled.

“It’s not so bad.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 403 – Happy New Year

After tidying Ye Qiu up appropriately, Ye Xiu left the room and closed the door. He saw Chen Guo standing outside and said to her: “It wouldn’t be too good if we’re all up here and no one’s down there, no?”

“Right!” Chen Guo thought of this problem and immediately headed downstairs.

Ye Xiu went back to the first floor soon after as well and saw Chen Guo quietly sitting at the front desk. There clearly hadn’t been any problems in those short few minutes they had been gone.

The dishes on the dining table had already been cleaned up. It was just that because Ye Qiu had been lying on the table, they weren’t able to pack away the dining table. The barely touched alcohol was also sitting on the table. Ye Xiu picked up the bottles and shook them in front of Chen Guo: “Where do I put the alcohol?”

“Give it here!” Chen Guo extended her hands.

Ye Xiu walked forward and handed them over. Chen Guo followed: “The cups too.”

“Hm? You still want to drink more?” Ye XIu asked.

“It’s not like I have anything else to do! Do you want to try a bit? Let’s see if you’re as weak as your brother.” Chen Guo asked.

“There’s no need to test it out for me to know.” Ye Xiu said, but he still grabbed a bottle and poured out two cups.

“Since we’re celebrating, it’s fine if I drink a little.” Ye Xiu said.

“Mm hm, as long as you don’t drink often, it won’t affect your hands.” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu finished pouring out two cups of wine and handed one over to Chen Guo. Chen Guo took it and swirled it around like she was playing with a toy.

“It really is quite nice having a brother.” Chen Guo suddenly lamented, “Even if you often get into arguments with him, it looks like both of you are having fun.”

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu quietly replied. He knew that Chen Guo wasn’t lecturing him in any way. She was probably feeling a bit of sentiment towards her own life. After having been in Happy Internet Cafe for two months, even though Ye Xiu hadn’t personally heard about Chen Guo’s circumstances from her personally, Ye Xiu had good understanding from listening to others. Chen Guo had lived by herself for many years and probably yearned for this type of family love from the bottom of her heart.

Unfortunately, this type of family love couldn’t be replaced. Ye Xiu didn’t know what to say to comfort her, so he just quietly listened. Whenever Chen Guo took a drink, he would also take a sip.

The few customers in the Internet Cafe had finally all left. Today, not a single one wanted to stay overnight. After sending the last customer off, Chen Guo stood outside of Happy Internet Cafe for a good while. She let out a long strand of white air, turned around, went back in, and locked the doors.

“We’ll be closed today.” As she spoke, she turned off the majority of the lights. The only spot with the lights left on were where they usually sat to play on the computers.

Ye Xiu stood up from the front desk. His body swayed a little and looked at the computer over there. He stretched: “It’s been a long day. I’m a bit tired, so I’ll probably go to sleep a bit earlier today.”

As he spoke, he headed towards the stairs.

Chen Guo was surprised. She took a glance at the front desk and saw that there was an empty wine cup, where Ye Xiu had just left from. A sudden realization came to her.

“So he really is bad with alcohol too…..” Chen Guo laughed quietly. Ye Xiu had probably gotten drunk too! It was just that he was a bit better at controlling himself and didn’t get completely drunk like his younger brother.

Tonight, Chen Guo drank the most, yet she was doing the best. It was quite late already. Seeing Ye Xiu leave, Chen Guo closed off all the lights and went upstairs as well.

“Do you want to sleep in my room?” When Chen Guo went up, Ye Xiu had just gotten into the room.

“No need. I’ll just sleep here.” Ye Xiu was clearly doing better than Ye Qiu. He could at least point to the sofa properly.

“No, you should go to my room. I’ll go to Little Tang’s room.” Chen Guo said.

“I’ll leave a bunch of ash on your bed!” Ye Xiu said.

“Just try and leave a bit!” Chen Guo glared.

“That’s why I’ll sleep here.” Ye Xiu said and laid down on the sofa: “If you can lend me something to cover myself though, that’d be great.”

“Hold on.” Chen Guo went into her room, took out something and threw it at Ye Xiu.

“See you tomorrow.” Ye Xiu covered himself and called out to Chen Guo.

“See you tomorrow……” Chen Guo didn’t say anything more and went to her room to sleep. Even though she hadn’t gotten drunk, the alcohol still had some effect. Chen Guo slept well that night. When she woke up, it was already bright outside.

She got up and looked outside. It was bright, sunny, cold winter day.

Chen Guo put on her clothes and opened up the door to look. There was already no one on the sofa. The door the storage room was still closed shut though.

“Did he get up and go play games?” Chen Guo muttered and washed her face, rinsed her mouth. After coming downstairs, she saw that the dining table had been set up. There was some stuff on top. Someone was sitting next to it and sipping some milk.

“Morning!” Seeing Chen Guo, the person immediately waved his hands to greet her.

“Oh? You’re the one that got up……” Chen Guo recognized him as Ye Qiu. The method to distinguish them was very simple. Ye Xiu and Ye Qiu wore different clothing.

“Yes, yes. That guy is still sleeping. I threw him over there. I went out and took a stroll. I bought some stuff back. Do you usually eat this sort of food for breakfast?” Ye Qiu said.

“Oh, we usually buy some food from the little stalls around here. They might not be open because of the holiday today though.” Chen Guo said and walked over. She saw the food and drink on the table. They had clearly been purchased from the supermarket.

“So it’s like that. What are you going to eat? You can choose whatever you’d like!” Ye Qiu said.

“Okay.” Chen Guo nodded her head. Ye Qiu had finished drinking his milk and went to the computer Ye Xiu usually used.

“That guy usually plays games here everyday?” Ye Qiu asked.

“He plays games every day, but it’s not always over there.” Chen Guo said.

“How do you put up with a guy who plays games all day.” Ye QIu shook his head.

“You don’t play Glory?” Chen Guo asked.

“I don’t.” Ye Qiu shook his head.

Is it because you don’t like to play or because he’s playing, so you won’t play?” Chen Guo asked with a laugh.

“I really have no interest in it.” Ye Qiu said as he sat down. Before turning on the computer, he asked Chen Guo for permission: “Can I?”

“I have to turn on the server computer first.” Chen Guo said and went to turn on the server computer, “It’s all good to go now.”

“Mm, thank you.” Ye Qiu replied.

。

Chen Guo saw Ye Qiu quickly put on his headphones. She really wanted to see what Ye Qiu, who didn’t play games, would do on the computer, when she suddenly heard a knock from outside on the roller shutter. Even though Ye Qiu had gone outside before, when he returned, he closed all the doors like they had been before.

“There are still customers today?” Chen Guo questioned. She opened up the door and pressed on the button to open the roller shutter. With a “whoosh”, the roller shutter rolled up.

“HAPPY NEW YEAR!!”

Chen Guo heard someone yell excitedly outside of the door. At the same time, there was a “BANG!” and colored paper flew out everywhere all over her face. Someone had used a party popper towards her.

Chen Guo jumped up in fright. But in any case, it had been done in celebration, so she couldn’t get angry. Especially, when Chen Guo saw who it was standing outside. She even felt very humbled.

Outside standing was Su Mucheng.

“Oh no!! I’m so sorry!!!” Su Mucheng saw that the person she had party popped was Chen Guo and felt very embarrassed. Seeing Chen Guo covered in colorful paper from head to toe, she hurried over to help clean it up.

“It’s nothing it’s nothing it’s nothing!!!” Chen Guo was too excited seeing her idol right in front of her. How could she care about all of that?

‘Come in come in come in.” Chen Guo hastily welcomed her.

“I’m so sorry! I thought Ye Xiu was pulling an all nighter, so I thought he would be the one to open the door.” Su Mucheng explained.

“Don’t worry don’t worry.” Chen Guo immediately said. To have her idol apologizing repeatedly in front of her was too humbling. She hated how she couldn’t just throw out her heart to let Su Mucheng know that she really didn’t mind at all.

“You…… can sit anywhere you’d like!” In front of her idol, Chen Guo’s mind was all over the place. She wasn’t sure what she should do. Should she bring some fruit over? Or should she go get some candy? Or should she grab something for her to drink? Should she give her a red envelope???

With her mind in a daze, Chen Guo completely missed Su Mucheng asking her where Ye Xiu was. By the time she turned around and looked, Su Mucheng was already tip toeing her way to behind Ye Qiu and quietly took something out of her pocket. It was another party popper. Seeing Chen Guo look towards her, she put up a finger to her mouth to make a “shh” face.

“Ah, that…….” Chen Guo only had time to say two words, when Su Mucheng cheered with a loud “HAPPY NEW YEAR!” and popped the party popper with a “BANG!” at the same time. Colored paper flew out, covering Ye Qiu.

“What the heck!” Ye Qiu shouted in fright and leaped up out of his seat.

Amidst the colorful paper, the two looked at each other.

“Eh? You’re not Ye Xiu. Are you Ye Qiu?” Su Mucheng said.

“Who are you?” Ye Qiu asked.

Chen Guo was astonished. Ye Qiu actually didn’t know who Su Mucheng was and Su Mucheng could instantly recognize that Ye Qiu wasn’t Ye Xiu. It looked like her relationship with Ye Xiu was quite close.

“I’m Su Mucheng.” Su Mucheng said.

“Su Mucheng?’

“You don’t recognize me anymore!” Su Mucheng said. This time, she didn’t hastily make an apology. Instead, she took the already used party popper in her hands and said in an upset voice: “I made a mistake again. I don’t have anymore……”

“None of what?” Ye Qiu asked curiously.

Su Mucheng raised her party popper up.

“If you don’t have any left, you can just buy more!” Ye Qiu said.

“I made these myself.” Su Mucheng said.

“I thought so! I’ve never seen a such a filled party popper before.” Ye Qiu said. She and Chen Guo were covered from head to toe with colorful paper. That wasn’t all either. The colorful paper that had flew out hadn’t all fell down yet. There were still some floating in the air!

Chapter 404 – Ye Qiu Leaves

When Chen Guo came over, she and Ye Qiu were covered in colorful paper. They looked at each other, but didn’t know what to say. Chen Guo felt her heart pained seeing Su Mucheng upset and went up to take a look at the party popper in her hands: “You can’t use it again?”

“No. Once it’s used once, it breaks.” Su Mucheng said.

“Let me see.” Ye Qiu extended his hands out.

Su Mucheng handed it over. Ye Qiu received it and studied it carefully. Soon after, he also let out a sigh: “Yes. It’s broken. It can’t be used.”

“Do you understand?” Chen Guo scrambled over. She wasn’t happy with Ye Qiu giving it a death sentence so quickly.

“Look, over here. This place……” Ye Qiu pointed it out to Chen Guo, “The reason she’s able to shoot out so much colorful paper is because it has a fairly strong explosive power, which is why it breaks after one use. Even if it wasn’t broken, this place can’t be closed up, so it won’t be able to shoot out again.”

Chen Guo clearly wasn’t prepared for Ye Qiu’s logical explanation. After thinking about it for a few seconds, she couldn’t find the crucial spot Ye Qiu was talking about. She looked at the popper again: “Can’t you find a makeshift fix? Like manually popping it?”

Ye Qiu shook his head.

For a moment, Chen Guo didn’t know what to say. Taking the already broken party popper, she didn’t know whether she should hand it back to Su Mucheng or not.

Su Mucheng herself had moved past her regret and took the broken party popper from Chen Guo. She examined it for a few moments and then put it back in her pocket.

“Where’s Ye Xiu?” Su Mucheng asked.

“He’s not up yet.” Chen Guo replied.

“Did he just go to sleep?”

“No, he slept last night. He had drunk a bit of alcohol yesterday.” Chen Guo said.

“Alcohol……” Su Mucheng smiled, “He’s really no good with that.”

“That’s certainly true.” Chen Guo also smiled.

“Really? Really? He got drunk too?” Ye Qiu immediately asked after hearing this.

“Not really. He knew when it was time for him to stop drinking, unlike a certain someone.” Chen Guo said.

Ye Qiu still remembered his heroic attempt last night to pretend like nothing had happened. He coughed embarrassingly and then went back to his computer. At this moment, footsteps could be heard from above and Ye Xiu’s figure quickly appeared at the top of the stairs. Seeing Su Mucheng standing below, he waved his hands: “You’ve come over.”

“Yeah!” Su Mucheng nodded her head with her hands behind her back.

“Did that guy leave yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo moved to the side, letting Ye Xiu see “that guy” she was blocking.

“I’m about to.” Ye Qiu had already turned off the computer and then stood up.

“You’re going back already? Why don’t you stay and eat lunch with us?” Chen Guo said.

“I have to go.” Ye Qiu said helplessly, “If I don’t, I won’t be able to make it in time for dinner. I’m not like this unfilial person.”

“Yes. You can even take my portion of the meal. Go home and be an obedient child!” Ye Xiu said.

“Hmph! My dream hasn’t been achieved yet! Hurry up and come back home.” Ye Qiu said.

Chen Guo had black lines coming down her face. Was this brother still thinking about running away from the family? Had he come here to call Ye Xiu back as the representative for the Ye family or had he wanted to call his brother back so he could run away?

“I’m going now.” Ye Qiu leaving clearly hadn’t been a decision he made on the moment. His overcoat and clothing had been brought down earlier. After tidying his clothes, he politely gave his farewells to the two ladies. He stopped them from sending him off and left by himself. When he got to the entrance, he turned around to wave at Ye Xiu: “I’m leaving, disgraceful brother!”

“When did the event start?” Ye Xiu had already immersed himself into the game.

Seeing the face that was completely the same as his with a never before seen look of concentration, Ye Qiu was originally going to say something, but his lips only moved slightly. In the end, he didn’t say anything and waved a final goodbye to the ladies and left.

“He left.” Chen Guo said to Ye Xiu.

“I know. I heard.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then why didn’t you respond.”

“I did. My heart almost broke.” Ye Xiu said.

“…..” Chen Guo was speechless.

“The event starts in the afternoon! It’s still early. Bring me to where you live and let me take a look.” Su Mucheng said.

“Oh sure.” Ye Xiu got up.

“Ah…..” Chen Guo was startled. It was obvious how close Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were, yet she had given Ye Xiu such a living space. What if Su Mucheng saw it and wasn’t happy with it? Chen Guo didn’t want to give her idol any discomfort! But at this moment, she couldn’t do anything.

Ye Xiu led Su Mucheng upstairs. Chen Guo was conflicted on whether she should follow them.

When Ye Xiu pulled open the door to the small storage room and presented it to Su Mucheng. Chen Guo had even closed her eyes.

“Ah, not bad. It really fits you.”

Chen Guo heard Su Mucheng say this and from the sounds of it, it didn’t seem like she was mocking him. Chen Guo glanced at Su Mucheng and saw that she wasn’t at all displeased. Right now, she was below the small window and testing her height to see if she could see outside.

“Do you want to climb up?” Ye Xiu commented on her movements.

“What can you see from out the window?” Su Mucheng asked.

“I can’t see anything either!” Ye Xiu said.

“Look!”

“What’s there to see.”

“I’m trying to see if I can see my window.” Su Mucheng said.

“Oh, let me think……” Ye Xiu didn’t do it half-heartedly. From his experience and skill in game, he was quite adept with angles and judging distance. He had lived in Excellent Era for several years too, so he was very familiar with it. Recalling where Su Mucheng’s room was, he nodded his head: “I should be able to see it.”

“Really? Let me see.” Su Mucheng said.

“How are you going to see it.” Ye Xiu was helpless. Su Mucheng clearly wasn’t tall enough.

“Help me up.” Su Mucheng said.

“You’re not talking to me, right? Boss, it’s time for you to show your enthusiasm as a fan!” Ye Xiu said.

Black lines ran down Chen Guo’s face. No matter how crazy of a fan she was, she wasn’t that crazy!

“I’ll go get a stool.” Chen Guo could do this though.

Su Mucheng was finally able to look outside using the stool to stand on.

“I really can see it.” Su Mucheng was satisfied.

“Really? Really? Where? I want to look.” Chen Guo chased after her star and went up.

“Boss, isn’t that too much?” Ye Xiu said.

“What?”

“You can see it from your window. Why waste your efforts to use this one?” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? Point it out to me.” As a result, the three went to Chen Guo’s room. At the window side, Ye Xiu counted up and down, left to right, telling Chen Guo the position.

“It feels so close.” Su Mucheng said.

“Yeah, yeah!” Chen Guo exclaimed.

“We can even say hi to each other in the morning.” Su Mucheng said.

“Of course!” Chen Guo continued to be excited.

“Let’s try it next time.” Su Mucheng said.

“Okay! Okay!” Chen Guo said.

“Have my phone number, so we can get in touch easier.” Su Mucheng took out her cellphone.

Chen Guo was already going dizzy from happiness. She obviously knew that Ye Xiu had ways to contact Su Mucheng, but she felt too embarrassed to just ask for it. Now that Su Mucheng did it on her own, she obviously wouldn’t refuse it.

“Okay, let’s go down now! There’s no one downstairs.” Ye Xiu reminded.

“I’m a bit tired. Let me go to your place to sleep for a bit!” Su Mucheng said after coming out of Chen Guo’s room.

“Sleepy?” Ye Xiu said in confusion.

“Happy New Year!” Su Mucheng suddenly cheered and her two hands stretched out from behind her back. Ye Xiu immediately retreated back to dodge. Chen Guo was astonished as well. She thought Su Mucheng was prepared, but when she looked again, Su Mucheng was still holding onto the already broken popper and this time, no colorful paper flew out.

“Ha ha, it’s already broken.” Su Mucheng gave the party popper for Ye Xiu to see. Even though it was broken, she still successfully surprised him. There may not have been any colorful paper that shot out, but she was still satisfied with the results.

“Oh?” Ye Xiu took it and looked, “Another one that you made yourself?”

“Yeah!”

“You were working all night on this, which is why you’re sleepy?”

“I didn’t really sleep much.” Su Mucheng said.

“Then go sleep!” Ye Xiu pushed Su Mucheng over to his storage room.

“Do you want to sleep in my room?” Chen Guo blurted out. She stared blankly shortly after because she realized that she had already said these words three times since yesterday. She had been politely rejected the first two times and this time she had the same premonition.

“No need! It’ll just be a quick nap.” Su Mucheng politely refused and pounced onto Ye Xiu’s bed.

“Call me over when the event starts.” Su Mucheng said.

“You can sleep longer. Give me your account card.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’ll play on two accounts?” Su Mucheng asked.

“No need. Let my boss help you play!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes yes yes! Let me, let me. I play the Launcher too.” Chen Guo said. Ye Xiu’s suggestion had hit two birds with one stone. Su Mucheng could sleep more and Chen Gou could happily play on Su Mucheng’s account.

“You can come down when you’ve got enough sleep.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Su Mucheng nodded her head.

Ye Xiu and Chen Guo left the room and went downstairs. The Internet Cafe was decorated the same as yesterday. The emptiness couldn’t be covered up though. But Chen Guo couldn’t care about this right now. She went down and hung up a “CLOSED” sign on the door. Then, she took Su Mucheng’s “Cleansing Mist” account and ran over to the game impatiently. She was even more energetic than Ye Xiu.

“Guess who I am!” Ye Xiu saw that as soon as Chen Guo went online, she immediately sent a message.

“Guo Guo?” The other side replied. Chen Guo had sent her message to Tang Rou’s Soft Mist. Even though this girl wasn’t in the Internet Cafe, it seemed like she still had Glory in her heart.

Chapter 405 – A Peaceful Spring Festival Event

Ye Xiu soon logged into the game. He wasted yesterday sleeping and didn’t use today’s dungeon runs yet. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist was the same, as was Tang Rou. Both of them were online and hadn’t run the dungeons. Horse Shooter and Thousand Creations weren’t online.

The level gap still existed between the players who participated in the Christmas event with Ye Xiu and the others. This gap eliminated any open teams. The only hope for a full five person team was to join the players of the other guilds. However, it was New Year’s Eve today, and each major guild was going with their own agenda. Ye Xiu glanced down at his friends list. A few of the guild leaders of the tenth server were online. He sent messages to every one of them, asking if they had any open teams. In the end, none had any available. Some already used up the dungeon runs while the others didn’t have space for three.

This wasn’t a big problem for Ye Xiu. If there was no team open, then he would manage. With his level of skill, three people was more than enough to challenge a five-person dungeon. The only downside was the efficiency, which wasn’t going to be very satisfactory.

On the other hand, considering this was a special occasion, he didn’t need to hold such high expectations. However, this was the first time Chen Guo had ever participated in work with such high difficulty. In addition, she was using Su Mucheng’s account. If she accidentally killed her idol’s character, she would surely die of guilt. As a result, Chen Guo was clearly way too nervous. Her maneuvers were rigid, her mind was often half a beat too slow, and she made countless careless mistakes. She only survived because of Ye Xiu, who had to save her frequently.

It was fortunate that Chen Guo sat right next to Ye Xiu. Through the latter’s constant hints and reminders, she soon recovered. She quickly realized that this was much easier than she had expected.

Chen Guo was no amateur, so she quickly figured out that this dungeon raid was easy because Ye Xiu took care of most of the difficulty. The rest was split between Tang Rou, who took the majority, and Chen Guo. Chen Guo obviously wouldn’t be dealing with anything too hard.

Nevertheless, three people running through a five-person dungeon was pretty slow. After three times, it was already noon. The special event for New Year started on 12:00 pm sharp. Tang Rou had already left to fix lunch. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo also called for delivery.

“What are going to have tonight?” Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo while munching on the delivered food.

After all, today was New Year’s Eve. The dinner on New Year’s Eve, according to Chinese traditions, was one of the most important meals throughout the year. Fast food would be a miserable excuse for such an important feast.

“Don’t worry. I’ve got it covered.” Chen Guo replied.

“Oh?” Ye Xiu was curious.

“I made a reservation at a restaurant. “ Chen Guo spoke.

“Will it be okay? I mean, if there are any Glory fans, especially ones like you.” Ye Xiu insisted.

Chen Guo glared angrily at Ye Xiu for awhile, then added, “I reserved a room. It should be fine.”

“Mm, not bad.“ Ye Xiu approved Chen Guo’ s decision. Chen Guo rolled her eyes and said nothing. Ye Xiu had no chance of being discovered by fans. It was Su Mucheng who was the problem. On the other hand, Su Mucheng was Chen Guo’s idol. How could Chen Guo not have considered everything?

“The event is about to start. What do you think of it?” Chen Guo asked.

“From the information released, there are no shortcuts. We can only rely on our luck and skills this time.” Ye Xiu explained.

“So there is no chance of repeating what happened last Christmas?” Chen Guo continued.

“Nope. That would be impossible.” Ye Xiu shook his head confidently.

“What level do you think you’ll be by the end of this event?”

“Do you think I’m some sort of god? I can only tell you things after doing the quests for some time. How can I know all of the things just by looking at the quest chain?” Ye Xiu complained.

“After level 50, you’ll be starting the Heavenly Domain Challenge right?” Chen Guo checked.

“I have to. Otherwise I can’t continue to level up.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Will it be hard?” Chen Guo inquired.

“Nope. It’ll just be like killing time. “ Ye Xiu responded.

Ye Xiu had said a while ago that he would be doing the Heavenly Domain Challenge once he reached Level 50. Chen Guo thought he was crazy then, but she found it easier to accept his casual reply now. For a top tier God like Ye Xiu, killing time was a fitting description for such a task.

The Heavenly Domain Challenge consisted of two parts.

One part had to do with the Arena. It required that the player achieve a certain number of victories. However, there was another criteria: the opponent’s level cannot be lower than one’s own level. Ye Xiu was having troubles with that requirement. His level was too high. He was in the group of players with the highest level in the tenth server. Even when that group reached level 50, there still wouldn’t be a lot of people that matched Ye Xiu’s criteria. In addition, these people were all the elites of the top guilds. They had old accounts in other servers. These job of these players was to level up their tenth server account as fast as possible to fight for the dungeon records. Arena was just something they did to waste time, so they rarely went.

As a result, Ye Xiu was in a bind. It’s just like how the best craftsman can’t make anything without the basic materials. There was no doubt that he can obtain that many victories, but the problem was that there were no opponents to beat. What could Ye Xiu do? Challenge someone over and over again? Unfortunately, the system of Glory had already thought of that. There was another rule: after ten victories against the same opponent, any more victories against the same person wouldn’t count.

The officials always treated the Heavenly Domain very seriously. The goal of the Heavenly Domain Challenge was to test the true skills of the player. Thus, the Heavenly Domain Challenge tried its best to avoid any loopholes. The only way to cheat was like Chen Guo, who asked someone else to do it for her. The officials of the game couldn’t do anything about that.

The other part of the Heavenly Domain Challenge were the PvE quests. Even these quests tested for the player’s skills. For example, some missions asked the player to collect a certain number of monster drops.. These items would not drop unless a certain criteria was met, such as a certain number of combos. No one could rely on luck to fulfill the Heavenly Domain Challenge.

Ye Xiu had no problem with these quests that tested for skill. Ye Xiu’s problem was killing the monsters. The Heavenly Domain Challenge always matched the level cap. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was only level 50, while the mission’s level was 70. This disparity would cause a huge level suppression on him, making every battle extremely difficult for Ye Xiu. He wasn’t worried about combos though because each battle demanded a tremendous amount of time, which would be more than enough for him to fulfill all the combo requirements. The only thing he had to worry about was endurance.

Endurance didn’t just indicate life and mana, but also Ye Xiu himself. He needed to be highly focused the entire time to ensure no mistake was made.

Even if Ye Xiu could accomplish all of that, he could not change the fact that the battles were going to be extremely long. This was the reason why Ye Xiu said this was going be a time killer.

“I hope everything will go smoothly…….” Chen Guo shuddered at the thought. On the other hand, Ye Xiu seemed to be thinking of something else.

At 12 o’clock, the special event for New Year started. Ye Xiu, Chen Guo, and Tang Rou all returned to the game. Ye Xiu checked his friends list again. Most people were on break for the holiday. Much to Ye Xiu’s satisfaction, Steamed Bun Invasion stayed online constantly.

After the last Christmas event, Steamed Bun Invasion had been left behind. Ye Xiu had always found that to be a pity. Ye Xiu even asked for Steamed Bun Invasion’s phone number to avoid such a tragedy again. Steamed Bun Invasion had logged in early today for this event, so he wasn’t late for it.

After completing the quest chain several times, Ye Xiu got a pretty good idea of the event. This year’s New Year event was just as good as the past years. The speed of leveling up for this event was way better than usual. Plus, there was a super high chance of getting all sorts of goodies.

Much to Ye Xiu’s disappointment, there was no loophole to take advantage of. This event definitely gave him no chance to get more stuff than others.

When the event first started, all the players participated excitedly. There weren’t a lot of people on his friends list, but Ye Xiu still felt that the maps were overcrowded when he completed the missions. The global chat was changing constantly, boasting of rewards good enough to make any player who missed the event regret.

The clearest proof of this was Chen Guo. Chen Guo was extremely focused on playing her idol’s character, but after seeing all the fancy rewards, she couldn’t help but want to abandon Su Mucheng’s account and log in on her own account.

Chen Guo didn’t have to struggle over this decision for long. An hour after the event started, Su Mucheng woke up and took over. Chen Guo immediately logged into her own account and started doing the quests in the Heavenly Domain.

“How do you do the quest?” Su Mecheng asked right after she got her own account back. She hadn’t read the description for this special event.

Under Ye Xiu’s guidance, Su Mucheng soon finished the first round of missions. There were a few battles here and there, but they posed no threat for a pro player.

“It’s not very interesting.” Su Mucheng commented after the first round.

“Yep. The rewards aren’t bad though.” Ye Xiu answered.

“It’s the same every year. “ Su Mucheng sighed and then started her second round of quests.

Both Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were experienced pro players, so no reward would surprise them too much. Chen Guo, sitting next to the two, was feeling the pressure though.

There were several times where she wanted to cry out in joy for the rare items the two won, but after seeing no reaction from the winners, Chen Guo felt embarrassed for over reacting.

“Actually, the best thing about New Year’s event is that there is no conflict.” Ye Xiu suddenly spoke.

“True. It’s a holiday, after all! No one wants to have a bad time during the holidays! For the Spring Festival, peace is very important.” Su Mucheng agreed.

Chapter 406 – New Year’s Eve

Things with rankings always aroused competition. It was the reason why the Christmas Event turned into a huge war between the top guilds. However, the Spring Festival wasn’t like this. Players quietly did their quests and the system quietly gave out the rewards. Players could form parties with each other to do quests, but it wasn’t necessary. You could easily complete the entire quest chain playing alone.

It could be said that the Spring Festival event had temporarily turned Glory into a single player game. Everyone could play on their own without any interaction. Of course, seeing others obtain beautiful rewards would make anyone envious, but there was nothing that could be done about that. The event quests were right there though. If they were envious, then they just had to complete them. The system gave out the rewards for the event fairly, so that more players would participate in the event.

But no matter how great the rewards were. The later it got today, the fewer the number of players there would be online. Just before six, Ye Xiu took one last glance at his friends list before he logged off. All of the names were gray. Not a single one of them was online, even those enthusiastic fans from the top guilds.

Soon afterwards, three people headed over to the restaurant Chen Guo had reserved and went there to eat dinner. Chen Guo suddenly felt like she was in a dream seeing the two guests in front of her. If this was in the past, she would never have thought that she would ever get the chance to eat with the two of them, let alone eating with them at New Year’s Eve.

Chen Guo was obviously very excited, but she also knew that Ye Xiu and his brother were both a mess with alcohol. As a result, even though she poured alcohol into Ye Xiu’s cup, it was only a little bit. She didn’t force him to drink either. Ye Xiu spent most of his time drinking other drinks to dilute it.

The three chatted about Glory.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were two top tier pros. Who knew how much gossip and secrets they knew about in the pro circle. Just from the two gossipping, Chen Guo had her eyes opened to a new world.

Though for gossip, the top tier God Ye Xiu couldn’t compare to Su Mucheng. Su Mucheng deserved to be called a girl. Her ability to gossip was far better than Ye Xiu’s.

That night, none of them talked about any serious topics. The atmosphere was even more harmonious than when doing the Spring Festival quests. At the end of the dinner, the two were clearly drunk. They repeated the same piece of gossip five times and were still laughing at what they were saying. Ye Xiu had drunk very little alcohol, so he was wide awake. Seeing that the other two were having fun, he didn’t stop them and just quietly sat there on the side.

“Ah? There’s no more alcohol.” Su Mucheng picked up the alcohol bottle and shook it around for awhile. She was only able to shake out two more drops. Then, she peeked through the bottle opening to look at the back of the bottle and then raised it up announcing her findings.

“Then, shall we go back?” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay!” Su Mucheng immediately stood up.

“Aw……” Chen Guo had wanted to say they could get more alcohol, but seeing that her idol wanted to leave, she swallowed what she was about to say and shakily stood up using the table as a support.

“Careful……” Ye Xiu saw that the two girls were unsteady and didn’t know which one he should help. In the end, the two girls supported each other and swayed left and right towards the exit. Ye Xiu followed behind them, ready to rescue them at any time.

They paid the bill and then left.

It wasn’t early and it was still quite cold at night, but the two drunk girls couldn’t feel it. After leaving the restaurant, they didn’t hurry to get back home and walked along the road. The two laughed and giggled the entire way back. Ye Xiu, who was following behind them, was too distracted to hear what they were saying clearly.

“Will it be far if we go back through there?” Ye Xiu heard Su Mucheng say this clearly and was so frightened, his body broke out into cold sweat.

“Hm, it’s quite far. We can walk for a bit and then get a taxi!” Luckily, Chen Guo still had her common sense.

“Oh, oh. Let’s walk for a bit.” Su Mucheng said.

The two girls continued to walk forward in large strides. Ye Xiu didn’t stop them and just followed close behind in case they tripped or something.

Looking at both sides of the street, all of the houses had their lights turned brightly on. In the night, the lights shined even brighter than the stars. Suddenly, there was a “Bang!” and then from who knew which window, a string of fireworks shot into the sky and exploded, dimming the stars even further.

The string of fireworks was like a signal and one after the other, all sorts of fireworks were set off. The sound of firecrackers also sprung up from all around, filling up the area with booms and crackles. Among these sounds was the sound of a clock. It was finally midnight!!

The two girls were almost within reach and Ye Xiu could see them opening their mouths and shouting something, but their voices were drowned out by the other sounds around them. Even worse, after the fireworks exploded into colorful flowers, raindrop like things began falling. Chen Guo was the first to be hit.

“Oh no!” The nearby Ye Xiu was able to hear Chen Guo shout this out.

“Run!!” The two girls called out to Ye Xiu. The two had already begun running. But the problem was that along this road, besides business buildings, the residents were all firing off their fireworks and firecrackers. This “rain” was dropping all along the road. Where would they run to?

The two girls didn’t seem to understand this logic. As they ran and dodged, they were having a lot of fun. Ye Xiu followed after them and finally understood. The two were pretending this was a game!

Ye Xiu paid attention to the road. During this special occasion, there were very very few taxis around. Even though he was looking for one, there was still no sign of one even after a long time.

“I’m so tired. Let’s rest a little bit!!” The two girls ran towards a bus stop to take shelter and then looked up together to see the skies filled with colorful flowers.

“Look over there. That one looks good.”

“Yeah, yeah. Over there!”

The two pointed around and continued to laugh, swaying from side to side. Ye Xiu also took cover at the bus stop and looked up. The beautiful flowers covering the sky truly was very gorgeous to look at. Unfortunately, no matter how beautiful the flowers were, they would only stay for so long before fading away.

The three under the bus stop watched the show put on by the neighborhood families. After the show was done, everything became exceptionally quiet. There would occasionally be a few sounds of fireworks going off, but it only further showed the emptiness after moments of beauty.

“It’s over……” Su Mucheng mumbled as she looked into the sky.

“It’s not done yet! We still have some at my home. Let’s hurry back and set them off!” Chen Guo said.

“Really?” Su Mucheng immediately became excited again.

“Hurry up and find a taxi.” The two impatiently urged.

But it wasn’t easy to find a taxi. The three waited for a long time before they found one. By the time they got back to the Internet Cafe, the families who didn’t care to see the New Year had probably gone to sleep already.

The two excited girls didn’t care about this though. After returning to the Internet Cafe, Chen Guo took out all of the fireworks she had bought yesterday. These fireworks had been bought based off of how good their names sounded to Chen Guo. She didn’t actually know what they were like though. After pushing them all outside, the two girls went to ask Ye Xiu to light them up.

Ye Xiu lit two of them, one for each of the two girls. The two girls played around with them, firing them off and commenting on them. Previously, they had been spectators. This time, they were participating. Even though no one else was really doing it right now, the two still looked for that type of fun from competing with others and expressed how their fireworks looked better than the others from before.

“Not bad, not bad.” Ye Xiu added and acted as the fire giver.

Chen Guo had truly bought a lot of fireworks. The two girls set them off for a good half an hour. They were finally satisfied and then went back to their rooms to rest.

“What should we do next?” They were done playing with the fireworks, but they clearly weren’t ready to stop yet.

“We can dungeon……” Ye Xiu suggested.

The two looked at each other and thought about it for a bit. They really didn’t have anything to do, so they accepted Ye Xiu’s suggestion.

When they came on, quite a few names on the friends list had lit up. Tang Rou wasn’t there though.

“Oh? There’s only us two.” Ye Xiu said to Su Mucheng.

“Then let’s go with just us two!” Su Mucheng didn’t care.

“You won’t fall asleep halfway right?” Ye Xiu wondered. The two girls had played crazily and had kept up their high energy the entire time. Now that things had quieted down, if the alcohol got to them, they would probably doze off.

“You’ll be okay by yourself, no?” Su Mucheng said.

“Okay, let’s go then!”

The two dungeoned together. Chen Guo hated how she couldn’t play with them. She could only go on her Chasing Haze and play by herself.

Ye Xiu’s worries had been right on the mark. Not long after they began playing, Chen Guo, who had been playing by herself in the Heavenly Domain, was the first to get sleepy and she struggled to keep her eyes open. In the end, she wasn’t able to hang on and she slumped in her chair and fell asleep.

As for Su Mucheng, because she was playing with someone else, her situation was better than Chen Guo’s. But halfway through the dungeon, she began struggling to keep her eyes open.

“Hey hey!”

“Hey!”

“Hey hey hey!” Ye XIu repeatedly reminded. Right now, Su Mucheng was no longer his best partner, but the dungeon’s secret spy, giving Ye Xiu trouble from time to time.

“Hurry up and go to sleep.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m not sleepy!” Su Mucheng struggled. She lifted her cannon and began firing at monsters. Ye Xiu had his character turn around and run. The monsters at hand hadn’t been completely killed off, yet she pulled another mob over…….

Trapping them using the terrain, moving around, kiting, pulling a train…….. Ye Xiu used everything at his disposal and with great difficulty, he was able to clear away the giant mob. He turned his head to urge Su Mucheng to go to sleep, but discovered that she had already fallen asleep on her chair.

Chapter 407 – Spring Festival Long Vacation

“Hey hey hey! Go up and sleep.”

“Hey hey hey! Go up and sleep.”

Ye Xiu patted to the left and to the right. The one on the left moved to the left and the one on the right moved to the right. Both of their mouths were muttering something. In any case, they were in a deep sleep and had no intentions of moving.

Ye Xiu patted to the left and right again. The two still ignored him. Helpless, Ye Xiu ran upstairs and grabbed blankets for them and then went back to the game.

Just like Su Mucheng said, for Ye Xiu, soloing a dungeon wasn’t a problem, but it was still more troublesome. Ye Xiu didn’t have any other choice though, so he pressed on forward through the dungeon. Moreover, Su Mucheng may be sleeping, but her character wasn’t dead. In order to not waste experience, Ye Xiu had Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist follow behind Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu let out a sigh of relief after getting out of the dungeon. Even though he had the ability to solo the dungeon, it taxed him heavily and certainly wasn’t efficient. Still running over to solo a dungeon was very stupid, especially while an event was going on. Ye Xiu hadn’t drunk much, so he was still clear headed. When he exited the dungeon, he had Su Mucheng’s character log off and then went to do quests.

The Spring Festival events weren’t difficult in the first place. If it wasn’t a problem for normal players, how could it be a problem for Ye Xiu? After mechanically repeating the quests over and over, he had even gotten on TV a few times, but he didn’t really get anything worth being amazed at. Experience was Ye Xiu’s main priority though and from this perspective, the efficiency was very satisfactory.

Early in the morning, Chen Guo’s and Su Mucheng’s alcohol and fatigue had eased up by quite a bit because of the sleep and the two woke up.

“Go up and sleep!” Ye Xiu called to them.

“Oh……” Chen Guo was struggling to wake up.

“What are you doing?” Su Mucheng was also trying hard to open her eyes.

“Doing quests!” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ll go do some too. I don’t want to be left behind.” Su Mucheng rubbed her eyes and extended her hands out to grab the mouse.

“Don’t worry! When I get to Level 50, the Heavenly Domain challenge will take me a long time to finish.” Ye Xiu said.

“The quest chain won’t be bad, but the requirements for the Arena might be troublesome in the new server.” Su Mucheng checked the level standings and said this after studying the tenth server’s character levels. Lord Grim was too high leveled. He was at the same level as the top guilds’ elite accounts and those accounts probably wouldn’t go the Arena at Level 50.

“A blessing yesterday, a misfortune today!” Ye Xiu sighed.

Ye Xiu couldn’t think of a way. Su Mucheng couldn’t either. She could only be helpless along with Ye Xiu. On the other side, Chen Guo was struggling to stand up, but after seeing that Su Mucheng didn’t intend on sleeping, she stretched and then sat back to down to log in.

“What, you’re not going to sleep either?” Ye Xiu asked.

“All nighter. What sleep?” Chen Guo opened her eyes wide, but she couldn’t open them very wide. She simply didn’t have the energy to do so.

“All nighter it is!” Ye Xiu wouldn’t urge her and quickly returned to his game.

As a result, the three each took a computer station and were able to complete the all nighter tradition. Many players used this as an excuse to play games all night.

And tonight, the might of the Spring Festival events could be seen. On the level standings, those who were online all day since the start had a huge advantage over those who hadn’t. Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s character had both risen up several ranks.

After the sun came out, the three logged off and went to sleep. Su Mucheng had originally planned on sleeping at Ye Xiu’s place, while Ye Xiu slept on the sofa, but Chen Guo stubbornly refused. Under her invitation, Su Mucheng went to sleep together in her room, while Ye Xiu slept in the usual storage room.

When they got up, they ate some food and then went to play Glory. For dinner, Chen Guo had reserved a restaurant again and so the three headed over there to eat another feast. They didn’t party as hard as yesterday and the two girls didn’t get so drunk that they were tipsy. After returning, they went to play Glory. This time, they didn’t insist on playing all night and went to rest if they felt tired.

This lifestyle went on for three days. The pattern remained the same, but they were quite happy with it. After all, Glory was their favorite hobby. During a long vacation, doing what you liked without having to worry about work was what most people did for their vacation. Their way of celebrating the holiday wasn’t anything out of the ordinary.

On the fourth day of the Spring Festival, Chen Guo had to go out. It wasn’t like she didn’t have relatives. It was just that she wasn’t very close to them. She still felt like she had to visit them for New Year’s. Chen Guo left in the early morning. When Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng got up, they only saw a slip of paper left by Chen Guo.

“Oh, today there’s only us two!” Ye Xiu read the slip of paper.

“What should we do?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Have you bought any new clothes for the New Year’s?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I haven’t!” Su Mucheng said.

“Let’s go shopping then!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay!” Su Mucheng didn’t refuse.

As a result, today, the three didn’t sit at the Cafe playing the game all day. Chen Guo went out to visit her relatives. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng went out walking around the city. They ate and took a stroll. It was like a vacation from the game.

Chen Guo finished visiting her relatives in one day. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng didn’t have any new goals after walking around the entire day either. The three returned to their previous life and played Glory during the vacation.

The long vacation for the Spring Festival usually lasted for seven days. But for the Pro Alliance, the vacation only lasted five days. This was because the Alliance wanted to take advantage of the vacation to add to the players’ fun. The seventh day of the Spring Festival was a match day.

On the night of the fifth day, Su Mucheng had to go back to the team to get ready. During these few days, Chen Guo had been able to establish a deep friendship with Su Mucheng. Being able to become friends with her idol was something she had never dared of dreaming about before. Right now, her dream had become a reality. She had a smile on her face the entire day. When Su Mucheng left, Chen Guo had sent her who knew how many things as a gift. Ye Xiu watched, a bit speechless: “I say, it’s not like she’s leaving to somewhere far away! She’s just across the street.”

“What do you know. It’s not convenient for Mu Mu to come over, especially because we’re at an Internet Cafe.” Chen Guo said.

“How could I not know……” Ye Xiu looked up at the sky. The boss was regarding him less and less like a pro player.

“It’s really too much. I can’t carry it all! I’ll leave it here for now and I’ll come pick it up when I have time.” Su Mucheng said.

Her other reasons could be accepted. The four words “when I have time” made Chen Guo unbearably happy. She obviously welcomed Su Mucheng to come over often, so she quickly split the gifts: “So it’s like that…… Okay, you can come pick these up later!”

Su Mucheng left. Now it was only Chen Guo and Ye Xiu that remained in the Internet Cafe. Chen Guo had given her employees seven days of vacation. Her reason for closing the Internet Cafe these past few days was mainly in order to concentrate on taking care of Su Mucheng as a guest. Now that Su Mucheng had left, Chen Guo could feel at ease opening up her Internet Cafe.

The Internet Cafe’s business was doing quite well today. In particular, there were many young faces. Many of them couldn’t even take out their proof of identity. They tried every way possible to try and trick their way in. Clearly, after receiving their New Year’s money, they wanted to go out and spend it. Chen Guo was very lawful towards these people though. She wouldn’t care about that small amount of business. Those who didn’t have their proofs of identity wouldn’t be able to enter. The helpless kids could only take their red envelopes and leave the line. Who knew how many kids she had to send away today. Chen Guo wasn’t so soft.

On the seventh day of the Spring Festival, the final day of vacation, the Glory Pro Alliance specially prepared a match day in order to give their Glory fans a happy ending to the vacation. This day had been carefully considered long ago during the planning for this season’s schedule. The entire day was filled with highlight matches.

Excellent Era versus Tyranny. Even though their current placings were very uneven, their many years of rivalry made this match a match worth seeing. No Excellent Era fan or Tyranny fan would miss this match.

Tiny Herb versus Samsara. After Excellent Era’s dynasty, the new generation two-time Champion team would be facing the up and coming Samsara. It would be a match between the old and the new.

Blue Rain versus Thunderclap. Both teams had Master Tacticians leading. Even though in terms of individual strength, Blue Rain had the advantage, the existence of Thunderclap’s Xiao Shiqin would give any team trouble. How the two Master Tacticians would devise their battle plans would definitely attract countless players who were interested in strategy and tactics.

Hundred Blossoms versus Misty Rain……

Mysterious Fantasy versus Bright Green……

Every match had something to be noted. Whether that be drama or controversy, all of the matches were filled with hype. The only unfortunate thing was that the competition schedule had been set before the season started. Many hot topics that came out during the season couldn’t be arranged into the schedule.

For example, Tang Hao versus Lin Jingyan, the fight between the new generation and the old generation was a fight that had only erupted during the season. Moreover, the two were both powerhouses in their respective teams. If this had been known earlier, a match between Hundred Blossoms versus Wind Howl would have definitely been arranged for today.

Such a dazzling array of hyped matches to watch would make any player very conflicted on which one to watch. The TV station had chosen to broadcast the match between Excellent Era and Tyranny. However, this season, Excellent Era’s record was quite poor. The two teams weren’t on the same competitive level. The match was entirely on their history as rivals. This wasn’t something that the people planning the season schedule could have predicted. The highlight match that had been planned for the Spring Festival had lost a lot of hype because of this reason. Luckily, the drama between Sun Xiang and Han Wenqing during the All Star Weekend made it so that there was something to look out for in this match. Even Chen Guo, who no longer liked Excellent Era, decided to choose this match to watch.

Chapter 408 – Su Mucheng’s Transformation

At Happy Internet Cafe, everyone was still on break. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo were the only ones working. When it was about time for the match to be broadcast, the two bustled about, running back and forth and had even let out a little sweat doing so. Luckily, Chen Guo had plenty of experience. In the past, she had tried doing everything herself like this and knew what troubles would happen with just a few people helping out. As a result, she took precautions beforehand, so they wouldn’t miss the match’s broadcast.

However, because she had offended many of the Excellent Era fans, even though today they were broadcasting an Excellent Era match, there weren’t many who came today specially for the match.

Chen Guo didn’t care about this. It was true that the Cafe had lost that atmosphere from before, but there was still a good audience size, especially since Excellent Era’s match was being broadcasted today. A few passerbyers saw this and joined in.

As a business, someone had to watch over the front desk. The two weren’t able to get a good seat, so they sat together at the front desk.

The commentator and honored guest had already begun doing their pre-game talk. There was a lot less to talk about though because of Excellent Era’s poor season record. Right now, the commentator and honored guest were discussing the challenge from Sun Xiang to Han Wenqing at the All Star Weekend, hoping to arouse their audience’s feelings.

Reality confirmed that it worked. The Excellent Era fans in Happy Internet Cafe were bubbling with excitement. They hoped that today, Excellent Era would be able to crush Tyranny, especially Tyranny’s captain Han Wenqing. The uglier the loss, the better. It has to be known that at the All Star Weekend, Sun Xiang had taken the initiative to challenge Han Wenqing, yet Sun Xiang was the one to lose. This defeat was something that Excellent Era fans could only lower their heads, even when Tyranny fans laughed at them. The battle had received not just a few mocking remarks from Tyranny fans, but the Excellent Era fans could do nothing in retaliation.

Win the match versus Tyranny!

After the All Star Weekend, this had become the number one hope this season for Excellent Era fans. As for making it into the playoffs, it was only a possibility in theory. They didn’t have any hope of it actually happening.

A match that was looked highly upon by supporters would make it an important match for the teams too. Excellent Era had expressed their confidence and determination in the pre-game briefing.

The match soon began. For the first round in the individual competition, Excellent Era started off with Su Mucheng and her Dancing Rain. Chen Guo immediately put down her task at hand and stared attentively at the match.

Having not projected Excellent Era’s matches in a while, Chen Guo only felt that it was a pity because she couldn’t watch her idol play. Even though she later found VODs to watch, it wasn’t as exciting as watching it live. Today was a rare opportunity. Chen Guo would give her a good cheer.

“Wow, Excellent Era starts off with Su Mucheng! Speaking of her, ever since the All Star Weekend, Su Mucheng has been performing exceptionally.” The commentator said.

“Yes. You’re right.” The honored guest affirmed.

“Do you think that it has anything to do with Ye Qiu appearing at All Stars and expressing his return with a Dragon Raises Its Head?” The commentator began instigating the drama, obviously for the audience to listen to.

“It might be because of that, but it’s only a guess. In recent interviews, Su Mucheng always avoids answering these types of questions.” The honored guest said.

“There’s already rumors that Ye Qiu is preparing to create his own team and return to the Pro Alliance that way. If that’s true, with Su Mucheng’s and Ye Qiu’s relationship, she’ll definitely be a central part of Ye Qiu’s team, no? Coach Li, what do you think?”

Today, the commentator and honored guest was once again Pan Lin and Li Yibo. In the Glory eSports scene, the two were well-known casting duos. They would often be sent out for the more exciting matches.

“This…… the earliest Ye Qiu can come back would be next split in the winter. It’s not possible to directly have his team enter the Alliance at that time. In other words, if Ye Qiu creates his own team and plans on joining the alliance, if everything goes well, it will have to be at the tenth season. As for Su Mucheng’s contract? She still has half a year left. When the tenth season arrives, her contract will have expired. It really is possible. In terms of time, there aren’t any hindrances. However, there’s still half a year of time. Even if Ye Qiu creates his own team, it’s only a rumor right now. We can’t make a conclusion so easily.” Li Yibo’s words were spoken in a somewhat roundabout way. The current him no longer made conclusions so bluntly. His words would often have many extra words to them.

“Oh oh. Let’s first pay attention to the match.” After introducing the players who would be appearing on stage, the first round of the individual competition began and the commentator Pan Lin immediately switched the topic to the match.

“Coach Li, don’t you feel that Su Mucheng’s style has changed after the All Star Weekend?” Li Yibo’s commentating style had changed, but Pan Lin’s was still the same. Pan Lin often brought up topics for Li Yibo to talk about.

Li Yibo was quite confident with this question. He didn’t answer in a roundabout way and replied directly: “In truth, when Su Mucheng partnered with Ye Qiu, she spent the majority of the time supporting him. But recently, she has clearly become much more proactive, whether she plays solo or with the team. She now looks like a main attacker.”

“Then Coach Li, do you feel that this change is due to some type of breakthrough she’s made as an individual? Or do you think it’s because the team requires it?” Pan Lin asked.

“That’s hard to say, but I believe that no matter the style or strategy, every player has victory as their end goal.” Li Yibo elaborately avoided answering the question.

In the past, Chen Guo had liked to hear what the commentator and honored guest analyzed, but after hearing Ye Xiu’s explanations and deductions several times, when the time came, she turned her head out of habit to see what Ye Xiu had to say.

This time, Ye Xiu didn’t say anything. Chen Guo didn’t like this and tapped Ye Xiu’s shoulder: “Hey, say something.”

“Say what?” Ye Xiu was puzzled.

“They’re saying that Mu Mu’s style has changed.” Chen Guo and Su Mucheng had become good friends and now addressed her as “Mu Mu”.

“They’re correct. Her style has changed.” Ye Xiu said.

“How has she changed?” This was the question that Li Yibo had avoided.

“She’s gotten better as an individual.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really?” Chen Guo was happy, but she quickly realized that Ye Xiu had something more to say: “Then what about from a team perspective?”

“They’ve already said it. She’s changed from a support role to an attacker.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is that change good or bad?” Chen Guo asked.

“That can’t be seen from a 1v1 match. You have to look at the team’s situation to see.” Ye Xiu said.

“Just tell it to me straight!” Chen Guo was anxious.

“For the current Excellent Era, this type of change has probably increased the team’s strength!” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“Because currently, Excellent Era’s core player is still a relatively solo player. In the past, Su Mucheng’s supportive play style didn’t just revolve around the core player’s tempo and add to it. Her play style required both sides to work together. When the core player attacked, the core player had to consider what she would do. Sun Xiang might have the ability to do this, but right now, he doesn’t have that type of awareness, so Su Mucheng’s playstyle wouldn’t be very effective. It’d be better if she became an attacker to increased the team’s battle strength.” Ye Xiu said.

“Sun Xiang is a piece of trash!” Chen Guo immediately disdained.

“If he really was trash, then there’s no one in the Alliance that would dare call themselves good.” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

“Trash is trash!” Chen Guo violently cursed.

“Let’s watch the match.” Ye Xiu said helplessly.

The first round of the individual competition wasn’t short or long. Both sides played well, but Su Mucheng had seized a crucial opportunity and helped Excellent Era win one point.

“Beautiful! Amazing!!!” Chen Guo clapped wildly.

“Yeah yeah!” Ye Xiu added.

“So halfhearted!” Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu’s tone.

“Yeah yeah!” Ye Xiu repeated himself to save time.

Chen Guo restrained herself from picking up her stool and throwing it at him. She could only glare viciously at Ye Xiu and wait for him to explain.

“I understand your reaction as a crazy fan, but from the actual content of the match, your reaction is too exaggerated.” Ye Xiu said.

“If everyone’s like you. Where’s the fun in watching a match?” Chen Guo curled her lips.

“That’s why I’m a pro and you’re a spectator.” Ye Xiu said bluntly.

Chen Guo lost again…….

Chen Guo was beginning to feel conflicted for the second and third round. Excellent Era was a team she didn’t like, but the team had players she liked. For a moment, she wasn’t sure whether she should be hoping for Excellent Era to win or lose. Previously, when she didn’t watch Excellent Era’s matches, she didn’t have this type of conflict. But now that she was looking at one, she didn’t know what she should be feeling. The match made Chen Guo feel vexed.

During her moments of trouble, Excellent Era lost two times in a row. Chen Guo immediately made a conclusion and looked down on the two Excellent Era matches that had come out, while praising Su Mucheng.

The group arrangement for the Group Arena was standard. The two team’s players with Han Wenqing and Sun Xiang last as the anchors.

The competition quickly began. This time, Excellent Era’s two players who went up didn’t give a chance for Chen Guo to look down on them. Their performance was exceptional. Not only did they defeat their opponents, they even acquired a huge advantage. In the third round, they fought against Han Wenqing and were able to take down half of the health of Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust.

Next was Sun Xiang’s turn. This matchup was something that everyone had been looking forward to, but with Han Wenqing’s Desert Smoke only with half of his health left, the disadvantage for Han Wenqing was too great. Sun Xiang used this advantage to form a steady strategy. In the end, Sun Xiang defeated Han Wenqing and won his team the Group Arena victory.

However, beating a half health Han Wenqing didn’t make any of the Excellent Era fans satisfied with the revenge. They only felt like Sun Xiang had done something that should have been done. In order to appease their resentment, it would have to be Sun Xiang at half health beating a Han Wenqing at full health.

As a result, everything depended on the final team competition.

Chapter 409 – Excellent Era Is Just That

So far, Tyranny had won two points, while Excellent Era had won three points. However, Excellent Era fans weren’t happy. For the current Excellent Era, points were no longer significant. Playoffs wasn’t possible and their standings weren’t so bad that they were at risk of falling to the last two places and getting eliminated from the Alliance.

Excellent Era fans hoped to see a moving match. In reality, they didn’t even need to win versus Tyranny, but they had to give Tyranny trouble. For Excellent Era, which no longer cared for their standings, their fans only wanted to enjoy the match and no longer cared for the results.

The break before the team competition was always relatively long. The commentator Pan Lin and honored guest Li Yibo discussed this issue. These two experiences professionals understood the two teams’ situations quite clearly.

The audience in Happy Internet Cafe were also in a discussion. The atmosphere in the past when broadcasting Excellent Era games had somewhat reappeared. Truthfully, Chen Guo missed this type of atmosphere. Seeing the customers joining forces to support Excellent Era, Chen Guo showed a reminiscent expression.

After a 20 minute break, the team competition finally began. Both sides sent out the arrangement they usually used for the team competition.

Happy Internet Cafe quickly began growing excited, shouting and cheering for Team Excellent Era. But who could have thought that this team competition was like a splash of cold water to Excellent Era fans.

At the start of the match, Team Excellent Era charged forward, giving their fans a sense of confidence and spirit. But after a few minutes of fighting, anyone who knew even a little bit about Glory could see that Exellent Era was at a complete disadvantage.

Tactics!

The decisive factor for this match wasn’t spirit, confidence, mechanics, performance, or experience, but tactics.

It goes without saying that the person to look out for was Team Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie.

Tactics wasn’t something that was easy to see from a direct observation like an amazing play that was seen in two or three seconds, instantly pumping up the crowd. There was more to see in tactics. It’s like a story filled with foreshadowing. The beginning might be dull and tedious, but once everything came together, the true importance of tactics would be revealed. The unceasing attacks from then on would cause the crowd to think back to the dull and tedious parts in the beginning and figure out what their purpose was.

The match turned out to be just like this. The first few minutes seemed like a normal confrontation, but after getting past this point, Tyranny began to continuously gain the advantage. The commentator and honored guest had been analyzing possible tactical intent at the start, but once the moment arrived, they connected the moves from the first few minutes and thoroughly analyzed the tactical plan.

“This is what you call brilliant.” Ye Xiu praised.

“You’re right.” Chen Guo nodded her head. Because she had already abandoned her identity as an Excellent Era fan, she wasn’t as dispirited and downcast as the other Excellent Era supporters in the Internet Cafe and appreciated Zhang Xinjie’s tactical plan objectively.

“A lone wolf like Sun Xiang fears this type of preparation and fears strategy and tactics with direction to them. Don’t look at how Tyranny was never worse than Excellent Era in terms of strength. Even Thunderclap might be able to gobble up Excellent Era.” Ye Xiu said.

‘Because they have Xiao Shiqin.” Chen Guo obviously knew the names of the four famous Master Tacticians.

“Correct.”

“What about the current Excellent Era? Is there anyone there good at tactics?” Chen Guo asked.

There might not be anyone in the entire Alliance who could answer this question with more authority than Ye Xiu. After a few seconds of silence, Ye Xiu slowly shook his head.

“Hmph…… retribution.” Chen Guo said impolitely. Excellent Era originally had a Master Tactician. Ye Xiu was one of them, but after Excellent Era kicked him out, a lot of problems arose. Chen Guo obviously felt happy about it because she no longer liked them anymore.

“For this season, Excellent Era is just that.”

As Ye Xiu made this remark, the team competition ended with Tyranny winning. If the results were looked at on paper, it looked like Tyranny only barely won with only two of their players left at the end. But as long as one saw how the match progressed, one would know that the results may have been close, but it was a closeness that had been predetermined. It’s not like it mattered how many players were alive at the end of the match. This was why sometimes, trading blows to end the match could be a very direct and effective strategy.

In the news briefing after the match, the briefing expressed how rare it was for the two bitter enemies to not have a tense fight, but those were only words for appearance purposes.

Tyranny gave a few simple words towards the match and then talked about the end goal for this season and their plans for playoffs. These were all things that Excellent Era didn’t have for this season. A few reporters believed there was another meaning behind these words and felt that Tyranny was trying to say that Excellent Era was not at the same level as them, so it was beneath them to talk about Excellent Era.

Excellent Era had less of a voice as the losers. Excellent Era politely praised Tyranny’s incredible tactics and then added in as if by accident that it was because they were playing on Tyranny’s home grounds that Tyranny was able to prepare such fine tactics. Then, they said how it was a pity that they wouldn’t have any more chances to fight against Tyranny this season and hoped that next season, the two teams would have another intense match.

The reporters once again noticed that their statement implied that Excellent Era was like a nobleman taking revenge, even ten years wouldn’t be too late.

Excellent Era understood what their fans were feeling and didn’t want to recklessly make a call. A loss was a loss. Still making remarks like a dead duck was very unclassy. Even though Excellent Era hadn’t touched the Championship Cup in four years, they still had the glorious record of having three Championship titles to their name and had always considered themselves as the number one team in the Pro Alliance.

The news briefing ended peacefully and Happy Internet Cafe’s broadcast also ended. The crowd began to disperse as well. Seeing how all of them looked so dejected, Chen Guo really wanted to go up and ask them: “Do you miss Ye Qiu?”

In the end, Chen Guo decided not to do so because Ye Xiu was sitting right there! She felt like standing out like that wouldn’t make anyone feel grateful towards her. It was much more likely that they would hate her.

After sending off a large batch of customers, Ye Xiu and Chen Guo returned to the game. Today, the Cafe had gotten loud for a bit because of the match, but then the business returned to the usual. The later it got, the fewer customers there were. There weren’t really any new customers that came. When it was almost midnight, there wasn’t even a single person left in the Internet Cafe. Before and after this, a lot of young kids without any proof of identity came to go on the computers. Chen Guo naturally shooed them away. At 11 o’clock, a large group of youths came and discussed with Chen Guo the conditions for an all nighter at the Internet Cafe.

Chen Guo refused to budge and just like everyone else, if they didn’t have any proof of identity, then they would have to leave. There was no room for negotiation. When the last customer left, she rolled down the shutters and closed the door.

During the long vacation, she had fun with her idol and played the game with her. Even though Chen Guo didn’t always accompany them for an all nighter, her usual sleep schedule had been broken. Right now it was 12 o’clock. In the past, she would already be in bed, but she currently didn’t feel like sleeping.

What should she do? There was only Glory……

She tidied up the front desk with Ye Xiu and then the two sat at their usual computers and played on their accounts.

“How’s it going? Has anything happened recently?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo shook her head and then turned around to look at Ye Xiu’s screen: “What level are you?”

“Level 49. I’ll rush to 50 tonight.” Ye Xiu said.

The time for history to be made had finally arrived. Chen Guo decided that she wouldn’t sleep today in order to remember this moment of glory.

“What do you plan on doing after getting to Level 50?” Chen Guo asked.

“I’ll do the quest chan first and then wait for everyone else to level up.” Ye Xiu said.

“What a waste of time…….” Chen Guo sighed. Normal players often had to repeat the content in the quest chain several times before succeeding, which was why they usually felt that it took so long. But for Ye Xiu, Chen Guo was certain that he would be able to pass it on his first try. He wouldn’t need to repeat anything and finish it step by step. The quest chain for the Heavenly Domain challenge wouldn’t take too long. However, for the Arena portion, he would have to wait for the majority of the playerbase to reach Level 50, which would usually take about a month. Right now there were events for the Spring Festival. However, most players wouldn’t be like Ye Xiu and play all day everyday, so their leveling speed couldn’t compare to Ye Xiu’s. Even with the event going on, the majority of the players would still need half a month. During this half a month, Ye Xiu would have nothing to do.

That night, Chen Guo didn’t sleep. As she did quests, she paid attention to Lord Grim’s experience bar. Finally, she personally witnessed this historical event. Under the white light from the computer screen, Lord Grim reached Level 50, becoming the first in the tenth server to get to Level 50.

Due to the nature of the Spring Festival, the accounts from the top guilds weren’t being played on 24/7. In the past few days, Ye Xiu actually played more than them. With Chen Guo helping Ye Xiu level, while he was sleeping, during these seven days of vacation, Lord Grim had become the tenth sever’s number one player.

But unfortunately, the tenth server didn’t have any event for begin the highest level. Even though Lord Grim was the first to reach Level 50, he didn’t get any rewards. He only received a few gasps of admiration from a few players.

Chapter 410 – Heavenly Domain Challenge, Start!

Apart from the Thousand Chance Umbrella, the other equipment on the Level 50 Lord Grim was very ordinary. Because he didn’t have a class, he couldn’t wear class-specific sets, so he simply switched equipment whenever he found it convenient to. Ye Xiu had more than enough money to buy these common equipment.

As a result, he had equipment of all different kinds and of all different levels. This was what other experienced players did as well though. Before reaching max level, very few players cared to buy the best equipment for themselves. The reason the top guilds would do this was because one, they needed the best conditions for challenging the dungeon records and two, they had many players and plenty of resources. Most of the resources didn’t need to be spent on the majority of the guild members, so the guild could allocate a bit of it to buy the most optimal equipment for their elites.

But now that Lord Grim was Level 50 and Ye Xiu had plenty of time to spare, he could carefully prepare a set of good equipment for himself. There was no need to get the best, but finding a proper set of equipment could increase his Level 50 battle strength by quite a lot.

Ye Xiu went to the main city and began searching the market.

The tenth server had opened for two months and the market could be considered as stable now. The new players that had come at the opening of the server had played for two months now and the majority of them weren’t as nooby as before. They had a basic understanding of the prices for different types of equipment and which equipment were useful. As for uncommon materials, which was always in need, even idiots knew that these materials weren’t trash.

When Lord Grim leveled to 50, it was already the latter half of the night. The market was still bustling with activity though. However, most of the characters at the vendor stalls weren’t active. Players would often go to sleep and leave their characters in the game with a vendor stall.

Ye Xiu obviously knew this, so as he moved through the market, he wouldn’t bother haggling over any prices that weren’t too ideal. He simply skimmed through the stalls as he walked. With the production capability of over ten million players, apart from items dropped by wild BOSSes, which only spawned a certain amount of times per week, there was more supply than demand. As long as one had patience, one could find anything in the market. Ye Xiu wasn’t looking for anything too great and understanding this idea, he patiently scoured around. He opened his money bag again and again, buying equipment after equipment.

After walking through one street, the equipment on Lord Grim looked completely new now. Ye Xiu opened up his stats page and nodded his head in satisfaction.

“What’s the logic behind your equips?” Chen Guo asked. She had been quietly watching Ye Xiu buy equipment the entire time. She had wanted to speak several times, but she never did because she wanted to rely on her own knowledge to figure out why. However, after observing the whole times, she couldn’t understand, so she could only ask.

Ye Xiu turned his head to look at Chen Guo and said: “By a price to stat ratio……”

Chen Guo had lost again. A price to stat ratio……. was a very practical reason. It was just that Chen Guo had thought that a top-tier God would look at things from an overall perspective. However, looking at things based on a price to stat ratio wouldn’t be good for that purpose, which was why Chen Guo hadn’t thought that Ye Xiu would choose equipment based on that logic. Even when she saw Ye Xiu buy an individual equipment and thought of this, she threw away that thought every time. Who would have thought that it really was just like that. A great top tier God bought equipment based off of its price to stat ratio. Chen Guo felt like Ye Xiu was unworthy of his treasure trove of uncommon materials.

“This is good enough for the Heavenly Domain Challenge.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?” Chen Guo was surprised, but quickly understood: “Are you comparing the price based on the difficulty of the challenge?”

“Mm.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. He went around the city, preparing his equipment, and received all of the quests for the Heavenly Domain Challenge.

Arena.

Quest chain.

There were two parts to it.

As a result, when Ye Xiu passed by the Arena entrance, he had Lord Grim look around even though he clearly knew he was the only Level 50 character in the tenth server. It could be seen that even God Ye Xiu was a person. Even he hoped that pie would fall from the sky sometimes.

In the end, there was nothing to be found in the Arena, so he began the quest chain.

There were many steps in the quest chain. The first step was to return to the Beginner Village and find the NPC to receive the quest and help him find his money bag, which he lost in the creek nearby.

It was a very common quest. After receiving it, the player simply followed the directions given by the NPC and then the player would reach the quest scenario.

The Heavenly Domain quest scenario were actually dungeon-like in nature. However, it had to be completed alone, so there was no need to worry about anyone else messing up your Challenge and there was also no need to try asking others for help.

Finding the money bag sounded cute, but in reality, it tested the player’s ability to jump.

The scenario was set in rapid flowing water. The player could only jump on the rocks to move forward. If the player accidentally jumped into the water, the player would immediately be carried by the water to shore and the player would have to try again. The money bag was located on one of the rocks in the creek.

The arrangement of the rocks and the money bag’s location was random. This made it so that it wasn’t possible to make a guide for it. The player could only rely on his own strength to jump around and find it.

Chen Guo had been stuck on this quest for a long time, when she was attempting the Heavenly Domain Challenge. She had fallen into the water countless times, but in the end, she was able to find the money bag. Now that there was a God in front of her, Chen Guo obviously wanted to watch him play. She saw Ye Xiu get to the scenario, charge towards the river bank, and then directly jump, without stopping to look.

He never paused. By looking at Ye Xiu’s screen, Chen Guo could see just how fluid and quick Ye Xiu was with these movements. His screen was never in the same place for even one second. His camera constantly turned. Chen Guo didn’t know if he was looking for the money bag or looking for a place to land. His character jumped non-stop. Chen Guo no longer knew which direction he was heading in.

After three minutes, Lord Grim jumped back onto shore and then left.

Chen Guo was dumbstruck. She stared at the screen dumbly and after a minute, she confirmed that Ye Xiu was heading back to the Beginner Village. She asked in astonishment: “You’re done?”

“Done!” Ye Xiu said.

“The money bag?”

Ye Xiu opened up his inventory. Because the money bag was a quest item, the name was in a different color, so it was easy to distinguish it from the other items.

“When did you pick it up?” Chen Guo hadn’t seen it.

“That…….” Ye Xiu felt that it was hard to describe.

“I didn’t see it at all!” Chen Guo said.

“If you told me earlier, I could have gone slower……” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was speechless all the way until Ye Xiu handed over the money bag and started the second quest.

The second quest was a battle, but there were restrictions. Only normal attacks could be used. No skills were allowed.

At that time, this quest had made Chen Guo cough up blood. For Gunners, normal attacks were a type of style. Even though they could be fired in all sorts of positions and movements, the only way to do damage was to hit the opponent with the shots.

A Gunner without skills was like playing a game of Counter Strike.

It was a 1v100 game. You only had one life bar. If you died, you had to start over. The only good thing was that if you died, there was no penalty. If there were penalties for dying in the Heavenly Domain Challenge, the Glory company would certainly be under terrorist attacks.

This 1v100 quest had a storyline to it, but Ye Xiu obviously didn’t care. He took the quest and skipped all of the talking.

Chen Guo switched positions and prepared to admire a performance by a God, but very quickly, tears streaked her cheeks.

She had used Lord Grim before. How could she have forgotten about the Thousand Chance Umbrella?

One class only had one set of normal attacks, but Lord Grim had six sets. Every form of the Thousand Chance Umbrella was another set.

Melee and ranged attacks, all around attacks, even shield attacks.

The 100 enemies weren’t BOSSes. In reality, they didn’t even have the strength of Level 70 monsters. Lord Grim was only Level 50 though, so against 100, from a level comparison, he was at a disadvantage.

But apart from the Thousand Chance Umbrella, Ye Xiu was also a beast.

What was a small difference in levels to him? They were just trash, that’s all they were.

Ye Xiu’s Thousand Chance Umbrella continuously switched forms. Every change wasn’t like how when Chen Guo used it; she sometimes just changed forms for fun.

For Ye Xiu, every change of form had a purpose. After switching forms, the weapon would immediately use an appropriate attack to deal with the enemy.

On his screen’s quest list, the 100 number kept decreasing.

Lord Grim’s health also continued to decrease.

But Chen Guo knew that it wasn’t because Ye Xiu couldn’t hang on, it was because he didn’t care. He had more than enough health to wipe out the 100 monsters. He didn’t need to care about his health. It wasn’t like the system cared how much health he had left at the end.

The second scenario was quickly passed. Chen Guo looked at the time. His progress compared to hers at that time were like night and day.

Ye Xiu directly entered the third scenario.

The third scenario was also a battle, but this was a one versus one with no restrictions.

But the opponent was a BOSS.

The Midnight Phantom Cat, Green Forest’s hidden BOSS. Of course, it wasn’t Level 10 like the one encountered in Green Forest. If it really was Level 10, even if it was a hidden BOSS, it would be obliterated by any Level 70 player.

The Midnight Phantom Cat had grown to Level 70.

A Level 70 hidden BOSS against a Level 50 character, but the player was a top-tier expert in Glory. In any case, it was a very unusual match up.

Chen Guo held her breath and watched Ye Xiu fight without any hesitation.

The Level 70 Midnight Phantom Cat was like a crying mouse in front of Ye Xiu. Chen Gou could even hear the cat’s shrieks and cries.

“The system has no way of stopping him…….” Chen Guo quietly thought as she watched the fight.

Chapter 411 – A True God

Ye Xiu passed the third test with ease. This was something that didn’t surprise Chen Guo. Soloing a Level 70 hidden BOSS sounded too excessive even as a test to enter the Heavenly Domain. If it really was as difficult as it sounded, the Heavenly Domain would be a dead server.

The Midnight Phantom Cat really was a Level 70 hidden BOSS and had the strength and power of a Level 70 hidden BOSS. The only thing it didn’t have was a BOSS’s health.

Health was a BOSS’s greatest advantage. A BOSS without a second bar behind its first health bar could hardly be considered a BOSS.

The Midnight Phantom Cat of the third test was this type of BOSS. His health value couldn’t be put together with the other BOSSes.

The Level 50 Lord Grim had a 20 level suppression facing the Level 70 monster. Who knew how many times weaker his attacks and skill effects were. In the end, Ye Xiu still defeated it quickly. The Cat rarely had the chance to hit back before becoming a corpse. The corpse became a quest item and was thrown into Ye Xiu’s inventory.

The third test was complete.

Ye Xiu was as calm as ever, while Chen Guo was indescribably excited.

Seeing Ye Xiu roll through the Heavenly Domain Challenge that gave other players headaches trying to beat it made Chen Guo feel delighted. It was like if she had been bullied by some big kid for a long time and then someone else came and beat the kid up in one punch.

It was such a thrilling feeling of justice!

If it wasn’t just the two of them and clapping wildly would look stupid, Chen Guo would have already started clapping.

“The fourth test, the fourth test.” Chen Guo urged Ye Xiu to hurry up.

The fourth test was given just before leaving the Beginner Village. The quest was a delivery.

The fourth test was set up along the delivery route and took place along a narrow, rugged mountain road. On both sides were bottomless abysses. If the character fell, the character would die. This test tested the player’s ability to move precisely. For this test, Chen Guo had moved one step at a time, slowly crawling forward. Even with this, she had fallen to her death countless times.

Chen Guo was confident that Ye Xiu would beat it in a few minutes again.

But the way he passed it was even more astonishing than what Chen Guo had imagined.

On such a narrow and rugged path, one slight misstep would cause the player to miss the road and fall. Ye Xiu actually had the nerves to use Aerial Fire. Chen Guo couldn’t even imagine how it was possible to use Aerial Fire so precisely. Every landing he made was completely on point.

Speaking of this, Ye Xiu had played as a Battle Mage! Why was he so skilled at using Gunner techniques? Chen Guo didn’t doubt that Ye Xiu was proficient with every class, but having such proficiency was a bit too much, no? Chen Guo felt like even a pro Gunner might not have the confidence to use Aerial Fire to move along this road. In addition, he flew forward without ever stopping.

It has to be known that this scenario was just like the first scenario in that the road was created at random. The curves along the road were different for everyone. So not only was it impossible to use a guide, it wasn’t possible to practice along the same road. It completely depended on how proficient the player was at using Aerial Fire.

Chen Guo stared at Ye Xiu inconceivably. She had thought that she wouldn’t look at the God this way ever again. She had thought that she understood just how great the God was. Now from the looks of it, his skill seemed bottomless.

When the fourth test was passed, Chen Guo was completely speechless.

Ye Xiu also let out a sigh of relief. He got up, went to get a drink of water, and lit up a cigarette. After walking around and finished smoking, he returned to his seat.

“Let me try a test!” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu. She suddenly had the urge to do one.

“Go ahead!” Ye Xiu didn’t mind.

As a result, Chen Guo switched to Ye Xiu’s computer and began controlling Lord Grim.

For the Heavenly Domain Challenge, many players repeated every test many many times before eventually passing it, so they all had a deep impression of it. Chen Guo didn’t need any reminders. Her memory of the entire quest chain was excellent and she quickly received the fifth test.

The content for this test wasn’t a battle. Chen Guo didn’t think that she was good enough to beat a Level 70 opponent with just a Level 50 character. If she had that type of skill, she wouldn’t have thought that completing the Heavenly Domain Challenge at Level 50 was inconceivable. This inconceivability was mostly towards the battles. The running and jumping wasn’t any different for a Level 50 and a Level 70 character

The fifth test was another one that tested the player’s technical skills. This time, the main technique that would be tested was rolling.

Many of the obstacles in the scenario were too high to directly walk past. Crouching and walking was too slow. Lying down and crawling…… was even slower, so it could only be done with rolling.

This test shared the same design as the previous one. The player couldn’t miss a single one.

For this test, if the rolling wasn’t timed correctly such as if the player hit the obstacle, the player would immediately be killed and would have to start again.

At that time, Chen Guo had passed this test by herself. Ye Xiu passing the past four tests in one try made him look so mighty and powerful. She also wanted to try and see if she could show such might herself.

Reality proved that this wasn’t a possibility.

Even though Chen Guo had passed the tests before, it was clear that Ye Xiu had passed these tests entirely relying on his skill, while normal players partially relied on luck. They didn’t completely pass through with ease. They had gotten through a few parts by coincidence.

If they tried again, unless their mechanics had actually improved, they could only pray that they were lucky again.

As for Chen Guo, not only was she unlucky, her condition wasn’t great either.

Staying up all night wasn’t one of her strengths. It was already late at night and she was already tired. Apart from that, Ye Xiu was watching on the side too, so she was also a bit nervous.

“Don’t look!” Chen Guo turned her head.

“When was I looking?” Ye Xiu asked back.

Chen Guo was speechless. Ye Xiu really hadn’t been looking. He was playing on her Chasing Haze!

Suddenly, Chen Guo felt like she wanted Ye Xiu to look. But she had just said “Don’t look”, so changing her mind was a bit embarrassing. She could only try again.

“Failed.”

“Failed.”

“Failed……”

Chen Guo continued to fail. She had gotten through only six obstacles on her best run.

Chen Guo stole a glance at Ye Xiu, who was playing quite happily on her Chasing Haze account. He really wasn’t paying attention at all. Chen Guo continued to try and continued to fail. In the end, she wasn’t able to take it anymore.

“Hey!” Chen Guo shouted.

“Hm? You’re done?” Ye Xiu turned his head to ask.

Chen Guo cried: “I couldn’t pass it.”

“Then let me try.” Ye Xiu and Chen Guo switched seats. After two and half minutes, Lord Grim exited the scenario. Chen Guo only hated how she didn’t have the Sharingan and couldn’t copy Ye Xiu’s gaming skill.

“Do you want to try the next one?” Ye Xiu showed his care for Chen Guo.

“I’m going to sleep!” Chen Guo got up and decided that she wouldn’t anger herself.

“You’re going to sleep?” Ye Xiu looked at the time, “Is the Internet Cafe opening today?”

“Yes!”

“When?” Ye Xiu asked.

“At noon.” Chen Guo said. Because the Internet Cafe didn’t have many customers in the morning anyways, Chen Guo didn’t force her employees to wake up early and hurry over to work after the break. As a result, she decided to open up the business again at noon.

“Are you going to be able to get up at noon? Do you need me to stay until noon to open up the doors?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No need.”

“Okay.” Ye Xiu nodded his head and continued to play the game.

Chen Guo began to hesitate again. In reality, she wanted to watch Ye Xiu do the Heavenly Domain Challenge. Seeing the God crush the missions that gave normal players an unbearably difficult time was very exciting. She had decided to sleep because she had been somewhat upset, but now she felt like it would be a waste to sleep and it would be better to keep watching. But Ye Xiu reminded her that they had to start the business at noon. This was a big issue for her.

Business would always be there, but there was only one chance to see Ye Xiu do these quests.

In the end, Chen Guo persuaded herself with this reasoning and came back to watch.

Seeing Ye Xiu look at her incredulously, Chen Guo glared at him: “What are you looking at? I don’t feel like sleeping, is that not okay!”

“Then what do you want to do?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Watch you do the quests.” Chen Guo said before noticing that Ye Xiu had logged out of the game. On his screen was a video of a Glory match.

“Huh? Why aren’t you doing the quests?” Chen Guo asked.

“There’s no hurry!” Ye Xiu said, “There’s plenty of time to do it.”

“What video are you watching?” Chen Guo was curious. After looking at it for a moment, she was surprised: “Wasn’t that tonight’s match between Tyranny and Excellent Era?”

“Yeah!”

“Team competition?”

“Mm.”

“Didn’t you already see it?” Chen Guo was puzzled.

“I want to study it again.” Ye Xiu said.

This was another difference between a casual and a professional. A casual would see it once and be done. A professional would see each match as a material to study. Observing the opponents and studying them. Even though Ye Xiu wasn’t in the Pro Alliance right now, he still did this.

“Tell me what there is to see in this match.” Chen Guo said.

“Are you sure? With your aptitude……”

“What are you saying!” Chen Guo was unable to restrain her anger.

“It’s like this. See, last night, Li Yibo said that the diagonal charge forward by Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was when Tyranny began reaping gains from their tactics. That actually isn’t correct.” Ye Xiu said.

“Mmhm.” Chen Guo nodded his head.

“What are you mmhming for? You don’t actually remember do you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I remember!” Chen Guo shouted. She didn’t have any way to prove she did, so she could only use her voice as justification.

“Okay, that’s good. Then look. In reality, Tyranny began holding the advantage from here. See Immovable Rock’s position? Do you see it?”

“Zhang Jiexi’s Immovable Rock.” Chen Guo nodded her head.

“I asked if you see his position.”

“I saw it!”

“Then what does this position tell you?”

“Isn’t that what you’re supposed to be explaining?”

“You can’t think about it for yourself?”

“With my aptitude……” Chen Guo darkened.

“Oh, that’s right……” Ye Xiu said with a face that implied “I know.”

Chapter 412 – Team Secret

The stifled Chen Guo still watched the match between Tyranny and Excellent Era again with Ye Xiu. This time, she wasn’t watching for fun nor was she enjoying the atmosphere with other passionate fans. This time, she was appreciating the match and studying it.

Ye Xiu explained the reasoning behind the position of Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock in detail. Chen Guo suddenly felt like a new world had opened before her.

When they watched, they didn’t watch it all the way through to the end in one breath. Ye Xiu often paused during several moments and rewound to watch it again, looking at the scene from a different viewpoint. Only then did Chen Guo realize that Ye Xiu wasn’t watching the direct VOD of the broadcasted match, but the VOD uploaded after the match onto the game’s spectating interface.

The spectating interface was the same as the one in the Arena. By using the spectating features in Glory, the viewpoint could be switched freely. If one were to study a match, these features were necessary.

However, this type of VOD would have to be downloaded. The size of the file wasn’t small either. As soon as Chen Guo had left, Ye Xiu had begun watching it. This meant that he had downloaded the file much earlier. He had planned on studying the match beforehand. It wasn’t something he had done on a whim.

He really deserves to be called a professional……. Chen Guo quietly thought. Her mind sometimes wandered off. This was because in some of the places where Ye Xiu rewound, he didn’t say anything. Chen Guo watched on the side, but had no idea what she was supposed to be looking for. Seeing Ye Xiu look so serious, she felt bad bothering him, so she thought about other things.

When Ye Xiu finished watching a section, he would sometimes explain what he analyzed to Chen Guo, but sometimes he wouldn’t say anything and just continue on. Chen Guo didn’t say too much. She listened when Ye Xiu explained and didn’t ask when Ye Xiu didn’t say anything.

And just like this, Ye Xiu took an hour to finish watching the 24 minute match from beginning to end. He wasn’t done either. After watching the conclusion, he went back to several moments and watched those again.

Chen Guo was feeling many different emotions right now. She had originally thought that she was quite familiar with Glory and felt that the only difference between her and a pro player was in mechanics. But after hearing Ye Xiu analyze the match in such detail, Chen Guo deeply felt that her original thoughts were too simple.

She suddenly thought of when Ye Xiu said to Tang Rou: If you want to surpass me, then you have to at least know how large the gap between us is!

Chen Guo discovered that these words applied to her too. It would be applicable to many Glory veterans. The difference between players who played for fun and professionals who played for a living was unimaginable.

“Okay, that’s enough.” Ye Xiu nodded his head after re-watching several details.

“You’re done studying it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Pretty much!” Ye Xiu said. He created a word document and titled it “Tyranny vs Excellent Era”. Then, he added the date in parentheses and wrote down a few things.

Chen Guo watched for a bit and saw that he was doing a summary of the match. Ye Xiu also wrote down some of the things he had explained to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo learned that being a pro player was much more difficult than she had imagined. Pros didn’t just play the game all day to practice and then go on stage for the match when the time came.

Chen Guo accompanied him without saying a word. After Ye Xiu finished writing what he wanted on the word document, he saved it. Then, he clicked on the folder where he would put it in. The folder astonished Chen Guo. There were countless documents inside with the team names and their match dates.

“These……”

“The matches from the past two months.” Ye Xiu said.

“You watched all of them?”

“Not all of them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Can I look at them?” Chen Guo asked.

“Sure!” Ye Xiu let her sit in his seat. Chen Guo sat down and clicked on a few of the documents in the folder.

They were just like the one Ye Xiu had just completed. In these documents were details he had analyzed from the matches, from tactics to movements, even what the players might have been thinking at that moment.

“This really is too…… too……” Chen Guo couldn’t find the right words to express what she was feeling.

“It’s nothing. It’s a job.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is there anything I can do to help?” Chen Guo realized how difficult being a pro was. If they really were going to form a team, then Ye Xiu would only have more work to do. Chen Guo hoped that she could help share the responsibility.

“Later, when there’s more. You can help me organize them. Organizing, while learning from them. When your skill level is higher, you can try do some analysis.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m not good enough…..” Chen Guo immediately said.

“Not now obviously. I’m saying that if you really want to learn, doing this sort of thing will be helpful.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then I’ll give it a try!” Chen Guo was very confident in herself. It was just that in Glory, she didn’t have much confidence when compared to Ye Xiu.

“It’s late already. Go take a rest! You still have to open up the Cafe at noon!” Ye Xiu said.

“Mm, I’ll go to sleep. What about you?”

“I’m going to rest for a bit too.” Ye Xiu said. He looked a bit tired. In Chen Guo’s eyes, as long as he was playing Glory, he would always be full of energy. Did anything unusual happen today? He had done a few of the Heavenly Domain tests and analyzed a match. From the looks of things, these were quite a bit more tiring than leveling up.

After the two cleaned up, they both went to sleep. They naturally slept until noon. When Ye Xiu woke up, Chen Guo was already gone. He tidied up his room and went downstairs. The Internet Cafe had already opened up. Business was slow in the afternoon, so it wasn’t too busy. When Ye Xiu came down, the employees who had just come back from a long vacation greeted Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu looked around and saw Chen Guo was at their computer stations, telling someone to do something. Ye Xiu recognized this person. He was a computer repair technician. He wasn’t usually around at the Internet Cafe and was called over whenever there was a problem with a computer.

“What’s wrong with the computers?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’m planning on running a network cable that’s separate from the server network to the computer.” Chen Guo said.

“Why?” Ye Xiu didn’t understand.

“Because these computers contain information gathered up by our team. We can’t be careless.” Chen Guo explained.

“Are you joking?” Ye Xiu wasn’t sure.

“Of course not. Only this computer has your documents downloaded onto it. I’ve just added a password to it too. I’ll tell it to you in a bit.” Chen Guo whispered.

“Aren’t you being a bit excessive?” Ye Xiu also whispered.

“This is an Internet Cafe, after all. It’s not like your former Club, so we have to be more careful.” Chen Guo cautiously glanced around as if right now, the ones sitting at the Internet Cafe weren’t customers, but spies looking for secret information.

“Oh so it’s like that……” Ye Xiu nodded his head. He didn’t say anything more. Chen Guo’s actions were quite reasonable. The teams in the Pro Alliance considered their equipment, strategies, tactics, and analysis of opponents as secrets. They wouldn’t be revealed so easily. Even though their Team Happy only existed in words, it wasn’t bad to prepare.

“Is Little Tang coming back today?” Ye Xiu watched technician tinker with the computer, while saying to Chen Guo.

“She called me today and she said that she’d be back tomorrow.” Chen Guo said.

“She’s been playing quite a lot these past few days.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah. You guys have taken advantage of the Spring Festival event.” Chen Guo said.

During the Spring Festival, it couldn’t be said that there weren’t many players online, but there truly weren’t many elites from the top guilds that were online. It wasn’t hard to explain this. For normal players, when they had a break, they would take some time to play and have some fun. It was very normal. But for the guild elites, the game was their work, so during the Spring Festival, they wouldn’t play games during vacation. As a result, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Tang Rou could be considered as having been online for a long time. The rewards from the Spring Festival were good and after the seven days of break ended, the three were the top three players on the tenth server level standings.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was placed first. He was already Level 50. Next was Tang Rou’s Soft Mist and then Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist. Both were Level 49, but their experience bars were at different stages.

“Are these three characters going to be our team members in the future?” Chen Guo asked. She was considering the idea of a team more and more seriously now.

“I hope so!” Ye Xiu said.

“Which one of them aren’t you too certain about?” Chen Guo asked.

“Little Tang!” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying Mu Mu will definitely join us?” Chen Guo began growing excited.

“I think she’d be quite happy with that.” Ye Xiu said.

“Little Tang…… I’ll have a chat with her when there’s a chance to……” Chen Guo said.

“Mm…..” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“That’s only three people though. It won’t be enough.” Chen Guo said.

“We’ll take it slowly!” Ye Xiu said.

“Are there enough of these types of characters?”

“Players need time to improve. Characters also need time to grow stronger. If we’re just looking at these right now, there are too many things that we don’t have enough. We don’t even have enough players!” Ye Xiu said.

“Is a year and half enough time?” Chen Guo said.

“Starting a team from scratch….. Is something I have experience with!” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Tell me your plan!” Chen Guo said.

“Our current problem is that we’re lacking players. There are two ways to find players. One way is to search for talent yourself and train them. The second way is to look for already matured players from other teams. The second way can’t be accomplished before we enter the Alliance, so let’s start with those around us first! Speaking of this, you’ve been playing Glory for awhile and you’ve been managing the Internet Cafe for so long. Is there anyone you know that you feel is pretty good?” Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo.

Chapter 413 – Spectator

Ye Xiu used his position to ask Chen Guo if she had any recommendations. Chen Guo had been managing the Internet Cafe and playing Glory for many years. Playing the game also made it easier for her to get along with the customers. During these two months, Ye Xiu had noticed that all sorts of people acted very familiar with her. They were only Internet Cafe customers and Glory players too. Among these, were there any experts, beginners, or players with talent?

Ye Xiu would sometimes take a glance at other customers playing Glory when he had nothing to do, but he didn’t see anything particularly noteworthy. However, Chen Guo definitely knew more about this than he did. Unfortunately, most of these people were Excellent Era fans. After Chen Guo refused to project Excellent Era’s match that day, she had offended many of them. In the end, the relationship between the two sides was simply that they recognized each other. Neither sides really had any mutual feelings for each other and could turn hostile faster than one could flip a page.

“This…… I really haven’t discovered any. Even if there were, it’s already too late.” Chen Guo replied.

“Why?”

“We’re right next to Team Excellent Era, so even if there were talents, they would have already tried getting into Team Excellent Era. Why would they wait for you to find them?” Chen Guo said.

“Are you reliable?” Ye Xiu asked.

“If I’m not reliable, why would you ask me?” Chen Guo didn’t reply nicely.

“Are there any plausible ones? Let me evaluate them myself.” Ye Xiu said.

“As if! All of the people I know are at my level at best.” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu sighed helplessly: “It looks like asking you won’t get me anywhere.”

“What do you mean? How else did Little Tang come about?” Chen Guo said.

“Oh…… that…….” Ye Xiu had made a mistake. He just realized that he had already found one talent through Chen Guo. Tang Rou was a talent that Wang Jiexi had tried to pull into the team. For Ye Xiu to happen to bump into a talent like this in an Internet Cafe was already very lucky of him. Glory had tens of millions of players and there were only a few hundred pro players. Talent could only be found by chance and not by searching for it.

“When will the computer be done?” Because talent could only be found by chance, there was no point thinking about it too much, so Ye Xiu could only concern himself with what was in front of him.

“It’ll be done soon.” Chen Guo said.

Just as she finished saying this, the computer technician stood up and patted the computer: “It’s done.”

“Go test it out.” Chen Guo told Ye Xiu to go.

Ye Xiu tried out Glory. He logged into the game. Everything went smoothly like normal, so he nodded his head. Chen Guo went over and told him where she put the folder with all of his researched documents and then whispered to him the password. With the way she was acting, it looked like the two of them were hackers conspiring something bad.

“Okay, I got it.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. Immediately afterwards, Chen Guo sent off the technician. This type of service obviously wasn’t free. After doing his work, the technician waited for Chen Guo to pay him.

Ye Xiu really didn’t feel anything different when he used the computer. He had Lord Grim continue doing the Heavenly Domain Challenge. On the road, he checked the level standings and found that he was still the only one who had reached Level 50. He sighed and closed it.

Chen Guo immediately ran back after paying the technician. She knew that for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, besides doing the Heavenly Domain Challenge, there wasn’t anything else to do. A Level 50 unspecialized player wouldn’t be able to gain any more experience whether he dungeoned, quested, or killed wild monsters.

When she went over and looked, Ye Xiu was doing the Challenge, just as she expected.

Yesterday, he had passed five tests. His efficiency made Chen Guo sigh in admiration. Before Ye Xiu came, in Happy Internet Cafe, passing two tests in a single day was enough to brag. For the Heavenly Domain Challenge, many players glared at their computer screens with red eyes and wanted to smash their computers in frustration.

Some studios offered services to complete the Heavenly Domain Challenge and earned quite a profit that way. But these studios couldn’t complete the Challenge with ease either. Even they had the urge to smash their computers sometimes as they did their business.

In the early days, the Heavenly Domain was truly a gathering of elite players. But nowadays, more and more players were able to enter the Heavenly Domain by luck or other methods. Regardless, the skill level of the players in the Heavenly Domain were definitely higher on average than players in normal servers. Not only was it difficult to complete the Challenge, if you didn’t have any skill, the harsh environment in the Heavenly Domain was even more rage inducing than the Challenge.

A major difference between the Heavenly Domain and the normal servers was that player killing didn’t have any penalties whatsoever.

Normal servers had red names. Even though the penalties weren’t so bad, it was still a status that restricted players. In the Heavenly Domain though, there were no penalties for killing a player and the losses for dying were much more severe as well. Because of this, one could easily imagine how chaotic the environment was.

In such chaos, if you were a noob, you’d definitely be bullied around all day. If you didn’t hurry and improve, you’d be cut down every time you walked out. The harsh environment of the Heavenly Domain caused many noobs to grow quickly and violently.

While Chen Guo was thinking about all of this, Ye Xiu passed the six test. Chen Guo was just about to say something, when someone nearby cried: “D*MN!”

Chen Guo turned her head and saw that there was someone standing behind her. His face held a look of astonishment as he stared dumbly at Ye Xiu’s screen.

When Ye Xiu turned his head, this person regained his composure, but his expression of shock couldn’t be wiped away. He stared with wide eyes as he said: “Brother, is this the Heavenly Domain Challenge?”

“Yes……” Ye Xiu nodded his head. This couldn’t be hidden. When the Heavenly Domain Challenge was being done, there was a clear sign on the interface. It was obvious at a glance.

“This this this…… is too amazing. How many tries did it take you?” This person had clearly seen Ye Xiu finish the sixth test in one breath. He thought that Ye Xiu had experienced hundreds of failures before being able to clear it with such ease.

“Many times. I lost count.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“But it doesn’t matter how many times it took you. It’s still very amazing. What test are you? I don’t think I saw a time limit!” This person said.

“The sixth test.”

“The sixth test? The sixth test……” This person recalled, ‘The sixth test…… the sixth test doesn’t have a time limit does it?”

“It doesn’t……”

“No time limit……” This person froze again. The sixth test was a test without fighting, but it was a more comprehensive test. The test had different types of terrain and obstacles. It required the player to use different movements in order to pass through it. When normal players did it, they did it step by step, cautiously and slowly. But Ye Xiu just passed it in a single breath without stopping.

“Brother, what server are you in?” This person asked.

“Tenth server.”

“Tenth server??” The person said in shock, “It’s only been two months since the tenth server. You’re already Level 70??”

“Nope. I’m Level 50. I’m just starting early!” Ye Xiu didn’t dare say that he was going to complete the entire challenge at Level 50. This brother’s eyes kept on growing wider. If he got even more excited, Ye Xiu was afraid his eyes would pop out.

“Amazing!” The person praised.

‘Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Brother, are you going to try the next test?” This person was quite familiar with the quest chain and was able to guess what Ye Xiu was planning on doing from his character’s movements.

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu said.

“Do you mind if I watch?” The person was quite polite.

“I don’t mind.”

As a result, the person sat down where Tang Rou usually sat and watched Ye Xiu play.

The seventh test was a battle with a BOSS and a mob of monsters. After a minute, the person’s jaw had dropped and couldn’t close.

“That….. What is that?” He was curious about the Thousand Chance Umbrella.

“Silver weapon.” Ye Xiu said.

“Silver….. Silver…… silver weapon?” After saying “Silver” two times, he lowered his voice. He was quite considerate. If he had blurted out “Silver weapon”, it would immediately gather a huge crowd. This had already happened once before. That time, many of the people in the crowd were tenth server players who had even added Lord Grim as a friend. They could often be seen online too. These players obviously noticed Ye Xiu’s rise in the tenth server. Those who still came to Happy Internet Cafe would pay their respects if they saw that Ye Xiu wasn’t busy.

Of course, these people didn’t know of Ye Xiu’s true identity. They just thought he was a very good player. In addition, due to the nature of working as a manager, he had a lot of time to play, so it made sense. After all, those who played in the tenth server were just normal players, so they wouldn’t think too much of it.

As for those more experienced players? They had been astonished by the Silver weapon, but it was only a Level 5 Silver weapon, so they didn’t pay too much attention to it. Because they were in different servers, they didn’t know of Lord Grim’s fame in the tenth server. It was true that those tenth server players knew of it and despite being in the same Internet Cafe, they played on their own and didn’t really interact with one another. As a result, Ye Xiu was still left alone and didn’t garner too much attention.

This brother was more careful. He didn’t blurt it out loud and gasped to himself. Besides the Silver weapon, he had discovered something else during that one minute.

“Brother, you haven’t changed classes yet?”

“Yeah, I haven’t.”

“What’s the reason for that?” This brother didn’t understand.

“Unspecialized. You haven’t heard of it?” Ye Xiu said.

“I know what an unspecialized is, but you…….” He clearly wasn’t too experienced. He only understood that a character was unspecialized before Level 20, but didn’t know that long ago, unspecialized players were considered a class in Glory.

“I’ll level to 70 just like this.” Ye Xiu said.